[{"value": {"id": 1847718, "askingMemberId": 5329, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87608", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of expanding the definition of vulnerable residents when identifying priority cohorts for fire and rescue services", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4976, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-11-07T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Fire Safety (Residential Evacuation Plans) (England) Regulations 2025 mandate Residential Personal Emergency Evacuation Plans (Residential PEEPs) for all high-rise residential buildings and residential buildings over 11 metres in height that operate a...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Housing: Fires", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847718", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847576, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87295", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what discussions she has had with her Estonian counterpart on reports that Russian jets entered Estonian airspace.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4264, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-11-07T00:00:00", "answerText": "I refer the Hon. Member to the answer provided to question 81195 on 20 October 2025.", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Russia: Military Aircraft", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847576", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847925, "askingMemberId": 4673, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87377", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, whether she plans to establish a formal recognition scheme for British (a) citizens and (b) organisations undertaking (i) humanitarian and (ii) medical work in Ukraine.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4264, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-11-07T00:00:00", "answerText": "We are proud of the fast, flexible and responsive support provided to Ukrainians living through Russia's invasion, including by British nationals, British organisations, and through projects initiated or funded by the UK. We pay tribute to the humanitaria...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ukraine: Humanitarian Aid", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847925", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847692, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87318", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the answer of 20 October 2025 to Question 78232 on MHCLG: Remote Working, for what reason junior civil servants have a lower office workplace requirement than senior ", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4976, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-11-07T00:00:00", "answerText": "Senior Civil Servants in MHCLG have a higher expectation for Office Attendance than other employees as they have a key leadership role in the Department and have a responsibility to be visible and accessible to their colleagues. Office Attendance expectat...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government: Remote Working", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847692", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847644, "askingMemberId": 5270, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87566", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many residential buildings have been decanted due to (a) unsafe cladding and (b) other fire safety defects in each year since the passage of the Building Safety Act 2022.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4976, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-11-07T00:00:00", "answerText": "Building decants arise in one of two ways \u2013 either in a planned way as part of a schedule of works or in an emergency situation due to emerging safety concerns. Not all decants are reported to the Department, particularly if they are planned. Emergency de...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Housing: Fire Prevention", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847644", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847713, "askingMemberId": 5288, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87580", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to improve fire service workforce resilience in (a) Surrey and (b) Surrey Heath constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4976, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-11-07T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Government acknowledges the vital contributions made by fire and rescue services. Decisions on how their resources are best deployed are a matter for each Fire and Rescue Authority (FRA) as the employer, based on its analysis of risk and local circums...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Fire and Rescue Services: Surrey", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847713", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848032, "askingMemberId": 5362, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87679", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether her Department is supporting research into potential methods for reducing the environmental impact of fish farm escapes on wild fish populations.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": ["87676", "87677", "87678"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 491, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-11-07T00:00:00", "answerText": "In line with our membership of the North Atlantic Salmon Conservation (NASCO), the UK is committed to minimising adverse interactions between farmed and wild salmon. From 2027 each of the UK\u2019s Governments will report annually to NASCO on the number of esc...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Fish Farming", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "87676", "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "87677", "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "87678", "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848032", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848026, "askingMemberId": 5362, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87678", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of interbreeding between escaped farmed fish and wild fish on the genetic integrity of wild populations.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": ["87676", "87677", "87679"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 491, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-11-07T00:00:00", "answerText": "In line with our membership of the North Atlantic Salmon Conservation (NASCO), the UK is committed to minimising adverse interactions between farmed and wild salmon. From 2027 each of the UK\u2019s Governments will report annually to NASCO on the number of esc...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Fish Farming", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "87676", "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "87677", "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "87679", "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848026", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848025, "askingMemberId": 5362, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87677", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to help reduce the risk of fish escaping from aquaculture sites due to (a) infrastructure failures, (b) human error and (c) severe weather events.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": ["87676", "87678", "87679"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 491, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-11-07T00:00:00", "answerText": "In line with our membership of the North Atlantic Salmon Conservation (NASCO), the UK is committed to minimising adverse interactions between farmed and wild salmon. From 2027 each of the UK\u2019s Governments will report annually to NASCO on the number of esc...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Fish Farming", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "87676", "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "87678", "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "87679", "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848025", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848022, "askingMemberId": 5362, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87676", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the (a) prevalence of fish farm escapes and (b) potential impact of fish farm escapes on wild fish populations.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": ["87677", "87678", "87679"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 491, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-11-07T00:00:00", "answerText": "In line with our membership of the North Atlantic Salmon Conservation (NASCO), the UK is committed to minimising adverse interactions between farmed and wild salmon. From 2027 each of the UK\u2019s Governments will report annually to NASCO on the number of esc...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Fish Farming", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "87677", "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "87678", "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "87679", "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848022", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847677, "askingMemberId": 5353, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87644", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether her Department is taking steps to distribute the fishing quota in a way that incentivises (a) lower impact and (b) selective fishing.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 491, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-11-07T00:00:00", "answerText": "As set out in response to PQ 83899, there are a number of mechanisms in place to incentivise lower impact and selective fishing. In terms of quota distribution, in England we have been running a trial since 2024 called the Quota Application Mechanism (QAM...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Fisheries: Quotas", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847677", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847662, "askingMemberId": 5288, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87578", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to safeguard the welfare of (a) pigs and (b) piglets on farms in (i) Surrey and (ii) Surrey Heath constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 491, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-11-07T00:00:00", "answerText": "All pigs are protected by comprehensive and robust animal health and welfare legislation, and potential breaches of the law are taken very seriously. Any allegations of poor animal welfare are investigated by the Animal and Plant Health Agency, and where ...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Pigs: Animal Welfare", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847662", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847780, "askingMemberId": 4844, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87449", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment her Department has made of the potential impact of the reduction in the sheep population over the last three years on wildfire risk.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 491, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-11-07T00:00:00", "answerText": "Defra has made no assessment of the potential impact of the reduction in the sheep population over the last three years on wildfire risk. The sheep sector is an important component of our rural landscape. The size of the flock changes year to year and she...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Sheep", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847780", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847633, "askingMemberId": 4403, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87348", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether her Department has made an assessment of the potential merits of implementing an employer pays principle to help tackle (a) debt bondage and (b) labour exploitation of workers ", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 491, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-11-07T00:00:00", "answerText": "Together with the Seasonal Worker Scheme Taskforce, Defra jointly funded an independent investigation into the feasibility of applying the \u2018employer pays principle\u2019 to the horticulture sector, to understand how financial risks faced by workers can be miti...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Agriculture: Seasonal Workers", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847633", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847892, "askingMemberId": 4591, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87367", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the UK's franchising framework.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 5076, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-11-06T00:00:00", "answerText": "The self-regulation of franchising through the British Franchise Association has generally served the UK well, with the franchise sector contributing significantly to our economy.However, the government is not complacent and is concerned to maintain fairn...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Franchises: Standards", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847892", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847603, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87249", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps she has taken with relevant stakeholders to help tackle illegal car sales.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4943, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-11-06T00:00:00", "answerText": "While the Driver and Vehicle Licensing Agency (DVLA) has no powers to govern how cars are bought and sold, it does play a key role in maintaining accurate records of vehicles and their registered keepers to support wider efforts to tackle vehicle-related ...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cars: Sales", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847603", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847730, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87236", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to improve children's palliative care services in Lincolnshire.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4359, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-11-06T00:00:00", "answerText": "Palliative care services, including children\u2019s palliative care services, are included in the list of services an integrated care board (ICB) must commission. To support ICBs, including the Lincolnshire ICB, in this duty, NHS England has published statutor...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Palliative Care: Children", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847730", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847880, "askingMemberId": 227, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87231", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment her Department has made of the potential impact of a ban on farrowing crates on pig production capacity.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 491, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-11-06T00:00:00", "answerText": "We remain firmly committed to maintaining and improving animal welfare and want to work closely with the farming sector to deliver high standards. The use of farrowing crates for pigs is an issue which we are currently considering very carefully, includin...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Pigs: Animal Welfare", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847880", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847634, "askingMemberId": 5335, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87610", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to help ensure that patients who are digitally excluded can retain (a) telephone and (b) in-person routes to book GP appointments.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4359, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-11-06T00:00:00", "answerText": "We know that some patients may struggle or prefer not to use digital options. We are committed to ensuring that patients who are digitally excluded can retain telephone and in-person routes to book general practice (GP) appointments, by mandating that GPs...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "General Practitioners", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847634", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847795, "askingMemberId": 227, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87229", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions her Department has had with counterparts in (a) Austria, (b) Sweden, (c) Switzerland, (d) Norway, (e) Germany, and (f) New Zealand on their (i) banning and (ii) phasin", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 491, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-11-06T00:00:00", "answerText": "We have regular engagement with counterparts in other countries on farmed animal welfare issues, including on cages and other close confinement systems.", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Pigs: Animal Welfare", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847795", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847761, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87623", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of updating section 8.1.1 of her Department's guidance entitled MOT inspection manual: cars and passenger vehicles, updated on 11 August 2025, to make it man", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4943, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-11-06T00:00:00", "answerText": "Excessive vehicle noise can be a serious disruption to people\u2019s lives. This is why it is included in the MOT as an inspection of exhaust silencers and noise deafening material as well as a subjective assessment of excessive noise upon revving the vehicle....", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Motor Vehicles: Testing", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847761", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847789, "askingMemberId": 4844, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87458", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent discussions she has had with the Environment Agency on the regulation of hazardous waste storage at industrial sites in Teesside.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4645, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-11-06T00:00:00", "answerText": "Industrial sites must only store hazardous waste in accordance with an environmental permit.", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Hazardous Substances: Waste Disposal", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847789", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847923, "askingMemberId": 4368, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87331", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to increase flood resilience in (a) Bermondsey and Old Southwark constituency and (b) other flood-prone areas.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4645, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-11-06T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Government, through the Environment Agency (EA), is investing \u00a32.65 billion between 2024/25 and 2025/26 to build and maintain flood and coastal defences, better protecting around 52,000 properties from flooding. The Thames Barrier and tidal wall defen...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Flood Control", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847923", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847941, "askingMemberId": 221, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87225", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what progress his Department has made on improving flood defences.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4645, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-11-06T00:00:00", "answerText": "This Government is investing at least \u00a310.5 billion until 2036 \u2013 the largest flood programme in history \u2013 a record investment that\u2019s projected to better protect nearly 900,000 properties. We are already making a difference. We delivered 151 schemes in our...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Flood Control: Standards", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847941", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847671, "askingMemberId": 5353, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87639", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what steps his Department is taking to help ensure Royal Mail complies with its legal obligations on the delivery of post.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 5076, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-11-06T00:00:00", "answerText": "The Universal Service Obligation requires Royal Mail to deliver letters six days a week and parcels five days a week to every address in the UK at a uniform price.Ofcom, as the independent regulator of postal services, is responsible for monitoring Royal ...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Royal Mail: Standards", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847671", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848041, "askingMemberId": 1409, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87245", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what recent steps she has taken to help eradicate polio in (a) Afghanistan and (b) Pakistan.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 5148, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "I refer the Hon. Member to the answer provided to question 76022 on 17 September 2025.", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Afghanistan and Pakistan: Polio", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848041", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847842, "askingMemberId": 345, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87235", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what recent diplomatic steps she has taken with international counterparts to help ensure the protection of Christian communities in Yemen.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 5148, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "The UK remains committed to freedom of religion or belief for all. We are concerned about the situation facing minority communities in Yemen, including Christians, particularly in areas under Houthi control. Reports indicate that minorities cannot practis...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Yemen: Christianity", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847842", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848018, "askingMemberId": 5141, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87516", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether she plans to publish an update to the National Travel Attitudes Study statistics.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4943, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "answerText": "The National Travel Attitudes Study (NTAS) is currently paused whilst the department explores options for its future. ", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Travel: Statistics", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848018", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847760, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87622", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many MOT centres in England in (a) 2022-2023, (b)2023-2024 and (c)2024-2025 assessed for exhaust noise as per section 8.1.1. of the MOT inspection manual: cars and passenger vehicles.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": ["87621"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4943, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "answerText": " It is a mandatory requirement for all MOT centres in England to assess for exhaust noise when conducting an MOT. During the emissions test the tester is required to use their judgement to assess the exhaust noise, either as part of the emissions test or ...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Motor Vehicles: Testing", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "87621", "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847760", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847759, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87621", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many vehicles which passed their MOT in (a) 2022-2023, (b) 2023-2024 and (c) 2024-2025 were assessed for exhaust noise as per section 8.1.1. of the MOT inspection manual: cars and passenger vehicles.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": ["87622"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4943, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "answerText": " It is a mandatory requirement for all MOT centres in England to assess for exhaust noise when conducting an MOT. During the emissions test the tester is required to use their judgement to assess the exhaust noise, either as part of the emissions test or ...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Motor Vehicles: Testing", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "87622", "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847759", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849286, "askingMemberId": 5304, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "906328", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he plans to allocate funding to innovative diagnostics to tackle antimicrobial resistance.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849286", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849284, "askingMemberId": 5109, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-13T00:00:00", "uin": "906313", "questionText": "To ask the Solicitor General, what steps she is taking to help ensure the effective prosecution of people smugglers.", "answeringBodyId": 88, "answeringBodyName": "Attorney General", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849284", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849285, "askingMemberId": 39, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-13T00:00:00", "uin": "906287", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will have discussions with the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs on the potential merits of reversing recent changes to agricultural property relief and business property relief.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849285", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849287, "askingMemberId": 5332, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "906245", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions she has had with Cabinet colleagues on the use of catapults as offensive weapons.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849287", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849022, "askingMemberId": 5359, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88559", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to help reduce veteran homelessness in Poole constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Veterans: Homelessness", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849022", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849019, "askingMemberId": 5359, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88558", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what steps his Department is taking to support (a) pubs, (b) restaurants and (c) other food outlets in Poole constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Hospitality Industry: Poole", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849019", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848900, "askingMemberId": 5359, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88557", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of membership of the ECHR.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "European Court of Human Rights", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848900", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849122, "askingMemberId": 5356, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "88556", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether the implementation of Windsor Framework rules governing the distribution of veterinary medicines in Northern Ireland from 1 January 2026 will impact (a) GB online retailers sel", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849122", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848871, "askingMemberId": 5356, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "88555", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what her Department's policy is on the sale of goods bearing Not for EU labels in Northern Ireland to visitors who reside in the Republic of Ireland.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848871", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849167, "askingMemberId": 5353, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88554", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to provide support for Child and Adolescent Mental Health Services to improve early intervention for children with emerging mental health difficulties.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Mental Health Services: Children and Young People", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849167", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849166, "askingMemberId": 5353, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88553", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to reduce waiting times for Child and Adolescent Mental Health Services in South East Cornwall constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Mental Health Services: South East Cornwall", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849166", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849162, "askingMemberId": 5353, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88552", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what information his Department holds on the number of women born in the 1950s who have died since 21 March 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "State Retirement Pensions: Women", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849162", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849146, "askingMemberId": 5351, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88551", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of levels of Community Infrastructure Levy in the Borough of Waverley on the supply of new (a) residential and (b) commercial ", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Community Infrastructure Levy: Waverley", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849146", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849043, "askingMemberId": 5348, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "88550", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what recent steps her Department's atrocity prevention specialists have taken in Sudan; and whether they have been surged to the region.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849043", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849140, "askingMemberId": 5346, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "88549", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of the (a) financial structure and (b) governance arrangements of (i) Blenheim Estates and (ii) the Blenheim Charitable Foundation.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849140", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849137, "askingMemberId": 5346, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "88548", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of Planning Inspectorate and Nationally Significant Infrastructure Project processes in evaluating the financial viability of funding commitme", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849137", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849068, "askingMemberId": 5346, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "88547", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what assessment he has made of the financial viability of SolarFive Ltd and Photovolt Development Partners to undertake the development of Botley West Solar Farm.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849068", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849067, "askingMemberId": 5346, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "88546", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, whether his Department has sought the advice of the office of the Financial Sanction Implementation on reported Russian-linked funding associated with the proposed Botley West Solar Farm.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849067", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849066, "askingMemberId": 5346, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "88545", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of (a) the Planning Inspectorate and (b) Nationally Significant Infrastructure Project processes to safeguard against national security risks ", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849066", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848864, "askingMemberId": 5345, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88544", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what his expected timetable is for publication of the Government\u2019s response to the consultation on strengthening the standards and conduct framework for local authorities in Engl", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Local Government: Conduct and Standards", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848864", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848867, "askingMemberId": 5343, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "88543", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he plans to provide financial support to local authorities seeking to rename (a) streets and (b) roads currently named after Prince Andrew where there is support from local re", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848867", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849004, "askingMemberId": 5342, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88542", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, whether her Department has made provisions for the recovery of public funds from contractors who fail to deliver on Building Digital UK contracts.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Building Digital UK: Contracts", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849004", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849024, "askingMemberId": 5340, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88541", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will make it her policy to (a) reduce and (b) freeze tobacco excise duty.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Tobacco: Excise Duties", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849024", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849023, "askingMemberId": 5340, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88540", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment her Department has made of the potential impact of the tobacco excise regime on smoking prevalence since 2021.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Smoking", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849023", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849021, "askingMemberId": 5340, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88539", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether (a) her Department and (b) the Office for Budget Responsibility has made an assessment of the potential impact of levels of tobacco duty on smoking prevalence statistics.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Smoking", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849021", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849020, "askingMemberId": 5340, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88538", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether she has considered moving the uprating of excise duty from Retail Price Index to Consumer Prices Index.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Excise Duties", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849020", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849113, "askingMemberId": 5329, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88537", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department has made an assessment of the potential impact of repealing S2(4) of the Law Reform (Personal Injuries) Act 1948 on NHS costs.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "NHS: Negligence", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849113", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849112, "askingMemberId": 5329, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88536", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information his Department holds on the number of claims for clinical negligence in each NHS Trust in the most recent period for which data is available.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "NHS: Negligence", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849112", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849110, "askingMemberId": 5329, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88535", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate his Department have made of potential savings of the implementation of Fixed Recoverable Costs for clinical negligence claims valued up to (a) \u00a325,000, (b) \u00a3100,000 and (c) \u00a3250,000.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "NHS: Negligence", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849110", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849109, "askingMemberId": 5329, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88534", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what (a) organisations and (b) individuals has David Lock KC had discussions with as part of his review into the legal costs of clinical negligence.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "NHS: Negligence", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849109", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849107, "askingMemberId": 5329, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88533", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether David Lock KC\u2019s review of the legal costs of clinical negligence will be published.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "NHS: Negligence", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849107", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848860, "askingMemberId": 5327, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "88532", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether she has made an assessment of the potential impact of HMRC's Child Benefit verification checks on the timelines of Self Assessment tax repayments.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848860", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848859, "askingMemberId": 5327, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "88531", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether she has made an assessment of the potential impact of (a) delays in HMRC Self Assessment tax repayments and (b) the non-fulfilment of published complaint response timeframes on taxpayers awaiting refunds.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848859", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848983, "askingMemberId": 5322, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88530", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the potential impact of the trial of extending the move on period for refugees from 28 to 56 days on the number of refugees who were rough sleeping during th", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Refugees: Housing", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848983", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848982, "askingMemberId": 5322, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88529", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the potential merits of extending the move-on period for refugees from 28 to 56 days.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Refugees: Housing", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848982", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848857, "askingMemberId": 5314, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88528", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 15 October 2025 to Question 80755 on High Rise Flats: Fires, what steps his Department is taking to monitor the adequacy of legislation on the communica", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "High Rise Flats: Fires", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848857", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848925, "askingMemberId": 5313, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88527", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will introduce a minimum 4 per cent annual uplift in core spending power for local authorities with Adults and Children\u2019s Services responsibilities.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Social Services: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848925", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848843, "askingMemberId": 5301, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88526", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when the Medicines and Healthcare products Regulatory Agency plans to open its Early Access Service for innovative technologies in areas of unmet clinical need.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Medical Treatments: Innovation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848843", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848890, "askingMemberId": 5288, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88525", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if his Department will publish a breakdown of how business rates tax collected by Surrey Heath Borough Council is (a) allocated and (b) used by the Treasury.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Business Rates: Surrey Heath", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848890", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849111, "askingMemberId": 5284, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88524", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether she will review the Public Service Vehicles Accessibility Regulations which limiting local authorities ability to offer paid seats on non-compliant vehicles with more than 22 seats for school transport.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Buses: Schools", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849111", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849103, "askingMemberId": 5284, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88523", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether negotiations on a Common Sanitary and Phytosanitary (SPS) Area with the EU has begun.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Agricultural Products: UK Trade with EU", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849103", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849003, "askingMemberId": 5252, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88522", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps her Department is taking to help tackle  delays in processing re-applications to the DVLA following the voluntarily surrender of driving licences on medical grounds.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Driving Licences: Applications", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849003", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849080, "askingMemberId": 5242, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "88521", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to her Department\u2019s publication entitled Annual statistics of scientific procedures on living animals, Great Britain 2024, published on 23 October 2025, what assessment she has made of ", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849080", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849018, "askingMemberId": 5234, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "88520", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the cost to the public purse was of constructing Glenart Castle Mess in Longbridge.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849018", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849135, "askingMemberId": 5226, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88519", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what steps his Department is taking to ensure online retailers clearly disclose (a) international return locations and (b) costs before purchase.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Retail Trade: Internet", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849135", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849056, "askingMemberId": 5223, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "88518", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when further details on the Structures Fund will be announced.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849056", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848882, "askingMemberId": 5212, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88517", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of extending the inheritance tax exemption for payments made by infected blood compensation schemes to cover payments received by the surviving spouse of a dece", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Infected Blood Compensation Scheme: Inheritance Tax", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848882", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848918, "askingMemberId": 5198, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "88516", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to (a) Section 51(2) of the Children and Families Act 2014 and (b) the powers of the First-tier Tribunal (Special Educational Needs and Disability) to issue binding orders following appeal hearings", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848918", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848917, "askingMemberId": 5198, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88515", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what (a) monitoring and (b) reporting arrangements his Department has put in place to ensure that repeated non-compliance by local authorities in the First-tier Tribunal (Special Educational Needs and Disability)", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Special Educational Needs: First-tier Tribunal", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848917", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848916, "askingMemberId": 5198, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88514", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether any barring orders have been made by the Special Educational Needs and Disability Tribunal under Rule 8 of the Tribunal Procedure (First-tier Tribunal) (Health, Education and Social Care Chamber) Rules 20", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Special Educational Needs: First-tier Tribunal", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848916", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848905, "askingMemberId": 5198, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "88513", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many notices of intention under Rule 7(3) have been issued by the First Tier Tribunal (Health, Education and Social Care Chamber) by local authority in each of the last three year.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848905", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849204, "askingMemberId": 5191, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88512", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to support Avon and Somerset Police to increase levels of community policing in communities in Yeovil constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Neighbourhood Policing: Yeovil", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849204", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849104, "askingMemberId": 5182, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88511", "questionText": "TTo ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what assessment his Department has made of the potential impact of the Digital Markets, Competition and Consumers Act on existing Gift Aid regulations.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Gift Aid", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849104", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849102, "askingMemberId": 5182, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88510", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, if he will take legislative steps to exclude charity subscriptions from the Digital Markets, Competition and Consumers Act 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Charities: Subscriptions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849102", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848936, "askingMemberId": 5182, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88509", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 4 November 2025 to Question 85516 on Marine Protected Areas: Bottom Trawling, when she plans to publish (a) the summary of that consultation and (b) her Depar", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Marine Protected Areas: Bottom Trawling", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848936", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848931, "askingMemberId": 5182, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88508", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 5 November to Question 85518 on General Practitioners: Ely and East Cambridgeshire, if he will commission research to examine the workload of GPs.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "General Practitioners: Ely and East Cambridgeshire", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848931", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848928, "askingMemberId": 5182, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88507", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the accessibility of GP appointments for the digitally excluded in areas with poor signal (a) coverage and (b) capacity.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "General Practitioners", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848928", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848926, "askingMemberId": 5182, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88506", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 5 November 2025 to Question 85520 on General Practitioners, what steps he is taking to improve access to GPs for people who are solely reliant on telephone bookings.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "General Practitioners", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848926", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849017, "askingMemberId": 5177, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "88505", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, with reference to the oral contribution of the Minister of State for Energy during the Westminster Hall debate on Coal Tip Safety and Prohibition of New Coal Extraction Licences on 22 October", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849017", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849159, "askingMemberId": 5169, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88504", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps her Department is taking to communicate the implications of inheritance tax reforms to business and agricultural property relief to family business owners.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Agriculture and Business: Inheritance Tax", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849159", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849158, "askingMemberId": 5169, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88503", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what guidance her Department plans to issue to family business owners on inheritance tax reforms to agricultural and business property relief from April 2026.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Agriculture and Business: Inheritance Tax", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849158", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849027, "askingMemberId": 5168, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88502", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make a comparative assessment of the adequacy of funding for research and innovation for (a) less survivable cancers and (b) other cancer types.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cancer: Research", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849027", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849117, "askingMemberId": 5163, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88501", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she plans to mandate antisemitism awareness education for (a) children and (b) teachers.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Schools: Antisemitism", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849117", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849121, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88500", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department plans to review data-sharing systems between the Prison Service and immigration\u00a0enforcement.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "HM Prison Service: Information Sharing", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849121", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849094, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88499", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what communications protocols exist between his Department and the Home Office to prevent the erroneous release of asylum-seeker prisoners.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prisoners' Release: Asylum", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849094", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849092, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88498", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of foreign national offenders released in error were awaiting deportation at the time\u00a0of\u00a0release in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prisoners' Release: Foreign Nationals", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849092", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849091, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88497", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether the public is notified when a foreign national offender is mistakenly released from custody.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prisoners' Release: Foreign Nationals", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849091", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849090, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88496", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether his Department tracks the locations of foreign national offenders following release.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prisoners' Release: Foreign Nationals", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849090", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849089, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88495", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the the mistaken release of asylum seekers convicted of criminal offences on public safety.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prisoners' Release: Asylum", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849089", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849087, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88494", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many officials in his Department have faced disciplinary action following the mistaken release of asylum seekers convicted of criminal\u00a0offences in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prisoners' Release: Asylum", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849087", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849086, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88493", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what processes are in place to prevent the accidental release of foreign national offenders from prisons.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prisoners' Release: Foreign Nationals", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849086", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849085, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88492", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many foreign nationals have been released from prison in error in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prisoners' Release: Foreign Nationals", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849085", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849193, "askingMemberId": 5152, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "88491", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will take steps to ensure that the National Cancer Plan for England includes measures that improve (a) early diagnosis and (b) outcomes for people with (i) myeloma and (ii) other blood cancer", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849193", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849128, "askingMemberId": 5152, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "88490", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether he has made an assessment of the potential impact of taper rates on young people living in supported accommodation who take on paid work; and if he will bring forward proposals to ensure that th", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849128", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849065, "askingMemberId": 5152, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "88489", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of creating a national fostering strategy.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849065", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849033, "askingMemberId": 5147, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-17T00:00:00", "uin": "88488", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department has made an assessment of the potential merits of requiring Disclosure and Barring Service checks for tattoo artists as part of the local authority licensing process.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849033", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849015, "askingMemberId": 5138, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88487", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many procurement contracts exceeding \u00a35 million have been issued by his Department in the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Department of Health and Social Care: Procurement", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849015", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848846, "askingMemberId": 5138, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88486", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will require NHS employers to provide ongoing (a) education, (b) training and (c) health surveillance for staff who (i) handle and (ii) may be exposed to hazardous medicinal products.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Health Professions: Hazardous Substances", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848846", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849095, "askingMemberId": 5133, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88485", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, if she will consider adding Sudan as a focus country within the Women Peace and Security National Action Plan.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Conflict Resolution: Women", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849095", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848927, "askingMemberId": 5122, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88483", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that the Environmental Land Management Scheme Landscape Recovery tier continues beyond the current round.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Landscape Recovery Scheme", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848927", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848870, "askingMemberId": 5122, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88482", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what her planned timetable is for publication of the rapid review of the Environmental Improvement Plan.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Environment Protection", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848870", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848869, "askingMemberId": 5122, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88481", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs what assessment she has made of the potential impact of uncertainty about future rounds of the Landscape Recovery tier of Environmental Land Management schemes on farmers\u2019 willingness t", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Landscape Recovery Scheme", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848869", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848868, "askingMemberId": 5122, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88480", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that the Environmental Land Management Landscape Recovery tier continues beyond the current funding round to deliver nature recovery at la", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Landscape Recovery Scheme", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848868", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848866, "askingMemberId": 5115, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88479", "questionText": "To ask the Solicitor General, what steps she is taking to help increase prosecution rates in cases of violence against women and girls.", "answeringBodyId": 88, "answeringBodyName": "Attorney General", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Gender Based Violence: Prosecutions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848866", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848978, "askingMemberId": 5111, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88478", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of requiring vape liquid and vapes to be sold separately.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Electronic Cigarettes: Sales", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848978", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848990, "askingMemberId": 5110, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88477", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether her Department has emergency contingency plans in the event of remote de-activation of buses by a foreign manufacturer.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Buses: National Security", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848990", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848987, "askingMemberId": 5110, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88476", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of Chinese ownership of critical transport infrastructure on national security.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Transport: China", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848987", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848922, "askingMemberId": 5110, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88475", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment she has made with Cabinet colleagues of the potential security implications of the operation of buses that have been bought from China that can potentially be remotely deactivated.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Buses: China", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848922", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849195, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88474", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what was the availability of the F-35 fleet in (a) 2023, (b) 2024 and (c) 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "F-35 Aircraft", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849195", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849082, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88473", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how the stealth characteristics of the UK's F-35 aircraft are measured.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "F-35 Aircraft", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849082", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849081, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88472", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to paragraph 11 of the Fifty-First Report of the Committee of Public Accounts, entitled The UK\u2019s F-35 stealth fighter capability, HC 1232, for what reason the UK F-35 fleet achieved two-fifths of t", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "F-35 Aircraft", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849081", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849079, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88471", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to paragraph 11 of the Fifty-First Report of the Committee of Public Accounts, entitled The UK\u2019s F-35 stealth fighter capability, HC 1232, for what reason the UK F-35 fleet achieved approximately o", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "F-35 Aircraft", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849079", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849078, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88470", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what progress he has made on including a UK weapon in the F-35 Joint Programme Office digital accelerator.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "F-35 Aircraft", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849078", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849077, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88469", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 20 October 2025 to Question 79460 on UK Space Command, what the (a) name and (b) scope is of the project for new detection technology.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "UK Space Command", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849077", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849076, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88468", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 20 October 2025 to Question 79617 on Military Bases, what disused bases are earmarked for disposal in this Parliament.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Military Bases: Sales", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849076", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849075, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88467", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 20 October 2025 to Question 79669 on Police National Database, what options for future delivery of the Police National Database transformation programme she is considering.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Police National Database", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849075", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849074, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88466", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 20 October 2025 to Question 79669 on Police National Database, when the (a) platform upgrade and (b) transition to the cloud will take place.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Police National Database", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849074", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849073, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88465", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many new prison places have been approved since 5 July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prison Accommodation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849073", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849072, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88464", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, in what locations he plans to create new prison places.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prison Accommodation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849072", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849071, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88463", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 20 October 2025 to Question 79742 on Railways: Mobile Broadband, by what date mainline trains will be fitted with Low Earth Orbit satellite technology.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Railways: Mobile Broadband", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849071", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848915, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "88462", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 20 July 2025 to Question 69517 on Typhoon Aircraft: Decommissioning, what planned block upgrades there are to the Typhoon programme after 2035.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848915", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848989, "askingMemberId": 5085, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "88461", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps her Department is taking to help reduce the time taken to issue remaining (a) Remediable Service Statements and (b) Remedial Pension Saving Statements to people affected by the McCloud remedy.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848989", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848988, "askingMemberId": 5085, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "88460", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, when she plans to issue remaining (a) Remediable Service Statements and (b) Remedial Pension Saving Statements to people affected by the McCloud remedy.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848988", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848986, "askingMemberId": 5085, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "88459", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent discussions she has had with the Welsh government on the (a) implementation of and (b) planned timelines for the McCloud remedy for public sector pensions in Wales.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848986", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848985, "askingMemberId": 5085, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "88458", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether her Department has received information from relevant Departments on their plans to issue remaining (a) Remediable Service Statements and (b) Remedial Pension Saving Statements to all people affected by the ", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848985", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849131, "askingMemberId": 5081, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-08T00:00:00", "uin": "88457", "questionText": "To ask the Leader of the House, whether he has made an assessment of the potential merits of improving parliamentary scrutiny procedures for international trade agreements.", "answeringBodyId": 34, "answeringBodyName": "Leader of the House", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849131", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849119, "askingMemberId": 5081, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88456", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what recent assessment his Department has made of the potential impact of investor-state dispute settlement provisions on the UK's climate targets.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Climate Change: Standards", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849119", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849116, "askingMemberId": 5081, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88455", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions her Department has had with relevant stakeholders on tackling harassment on public transport against women and girls in the North East.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Public Transport: North East", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849116", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849115, "askingMemberId": 5081, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88454", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment the Department has made of the potential merits of continuing the use of Education, Health and Care Plans to support children with Special Education Needs and Disabilities with a guaranteed righ", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Special Educational Needs: North East", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849115", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849114, "askingMemberId": 5081, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88453", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of the Plan for Neighbourhoods on communities in the North East.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Plan for Neighbourhoods: North East", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849114", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849012, "askingMemberId": 5081, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88452", "questionText": "To ask the Solicitor General, what discussions her Department has had with relevant stakeholders in the North East on the Rape Action Plan.", "answeringBodyId": 88, "answeringBodyName": "Attorney General", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Rape: North East", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849012", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849010, "askingMemberId": 5081, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88451", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions her Department has had with relevant stakeholders on the proposed ban on trail hunting.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Hunting", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849010", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849009, "askingMemberId": 5081, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88450", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with relevant stakeholders on its manifesto commitment to extend the ban on trail hunting.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Hunting", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849009", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849008, "askingMemberId": 5081, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88449", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent discussions he has had with relevant stakeholders on providing support to victims of rape and sexual violence through the court system in the North East.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Sexual Offences: Victim Support Schemes", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849008", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849007, "askingMemberId": 5081, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88448", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department is taking to tackle backlogs in the courts in the North East.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Courts: North East", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849007", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849006, "askingMemberId": 5081, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-04T00:00:00", "uin": "88447", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions she has had with relevant stakeholders on tackling harassment on trains against women and girls in Hexham constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849006", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849005, "askingMemberId": 5081, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-03T00:00:00", "uin": "88446", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussion her Department is having with relevant stakeholders to help tackle harassment against women and girls on trains in the North East.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849005", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849002, "askingMemberId": 5081, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-02T00:00:00", "uin": "88445", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to help support community cohesion in Hexham constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849002", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849001, "askingMemberId": 5081, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-12-01T00:00:00", "uin": "88444", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what recent discussions his Department has had with relevant stakeholders on the use of the Community Recovery Fund in the North East.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849001", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849000, "askingMemberId": 5081, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88443", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions her Department has had with relevant stakeholders on the role of a freelance champion in the North East.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Arts: Self-employed", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849000", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848999, "askingMemberId": 5081, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88442", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of reduced electricity costs for employers on employment growth in energy- intensive sectors in Hexham constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Energy Intensive Industries: Hexham", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848999", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848981, "askingMemberId": 5081, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88441", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what steps the Office for Investment is taking to help increase private sector investment in Hexham constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Investment: Hexham", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848981", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848980, "askingMemberId": 5081, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88440", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what discussions his Department has had with relevant stakeholders on ensuring that vulnerable pensioners in the North East are protected from online benefit scams.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Social Security Benefits: Fraud", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848980", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848977, "askingMemberId": 5081, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88439", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many parents with three and four- year-olds from (a) Hexham constituency, (b) Northumberland, (c) Newcastle and (d) the North East have used their entitlement to 15 hours of free childcare in each of the la", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Childcare: North East", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848977", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848865, "askingMemberId": 5080, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88438", "questionText": "To ask the Solicitor General, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of the Crown Prosecution Service's performance in the North East.", "answeringBodyId": 88, "answeringBodyName": "Attorney General", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Crown Prosecution Service: North East", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848865", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849190, "askingMemberId": 5078, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88437", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what steps his Department is taking to prioritise the development of small modular reactors as load following sources.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Small Modular Reactors", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849190", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849063, "askingMemberId": 5070, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88436", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether her Department has considered streamlining adoption processes for (a) sewers and (b) drainage systems where (i) easements and (ii) multiple landownerships delay adoption by wat", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Sewers: Private Sector", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849063", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849062, "askingMemberId": 5070, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88435", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to reduce the time taken for the adoption of (a) highways and (b) drainage infrastructure on completed housing developments.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Housing: Sewers and Unadopted Roads", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849062", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849061, "askingMemberId": 5070, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88434", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to support (a) local authorities and (b) residents where housing developments cannot be adopted because developers have gone into liquidation.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Property Development: Insolvency", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849061", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849060, "askingMemberId": 5070, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88433", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she plans to update guidance for police forces on the investigation of (a) false and (b) malicious allegations as potential criminal offences.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Criminal Investigation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849060", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849059, "askingMemberId": 5070, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88432", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether he plans to review housing allocation guidance to ensure that care leavers\u2019 (a) welfare and (b) community ties are taken into account when determining (i) local connectio", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Housing: Care Leavers", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849059", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849058, "askingMemberId": 5070, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88431", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to ensure that care leavers are able to remain in areas they have (a) links to and (b) family connections in.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Housing: Care Leavers", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849058", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849057, "askingMemberId": 5070, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88430", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of support provided to care leavers transitioning to independent living (a) in general and (b) housed outside their home local authority.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Care Leavers", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849057", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849055, "askingMemberId": 5070, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88429", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, whether he plans to support the development of new hydroelectric projects in the North West.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Hydroelectric Power: North West", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849055", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849054, "askingMemberId": 5070, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88428", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what guidance his Department has provided to NHS dentists on monitoring patients on orthodontic waiting lists to ensure that their (a) oral health and (b) treatment priority status are kept under r", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Dental Services: Waiting Lists", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849054", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849052, "askingMemberId": 5070, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88427", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how her Department plans to support integrated care boards to meet demand for NHS orthodontic services within existing budgets before April 2026.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Dental Services: Integrated Care Boards", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849052", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849051, "askingMemberId": 5070, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88426", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent estimate she has made of average waiting times for NHS orthodontic treatment for children and young people; and what steps her Department is taking to reduce waiting times.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Dental Services: Children and Young People", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849051", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849050, "askingMemberId": 5070, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88425", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that motorway and service station operators provide a sufficient number of accessible parking bays for disabled motorists.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Motorway Service Areas: Disability", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849050", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848834, "askingMemberId": 5068, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88424", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will take steps to review NHS communications to ensure that language on (a) pregnancy and (b) breast feeding reflects biological sexes.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Maternity Services: Sex", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848834", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848995, "askingMemberId": 5066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "88423", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps her Department is taking to help support the tourism industry in the South West.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848995", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848965, "askingMemberId": 5066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88422", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the potential impact of low-cost, unregulated online beauty courses on (a) public safety and (b) professional standards.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Personal Care Services: Education", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848965", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848964, "askingMemberId": 5066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88421", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department plans to (a) review and (b) update the national (i) curriculum and (ii) accreditation frameworks for nail and beauty qualifications.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Disease Control: Personal Care Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848964", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848963, "askingMemberId": 5066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88420", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that (a) training and (b) accreditation for nail and beauty professionals reflect modern (i) hygiene and (ii) safety standards.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Disease Control: Personal Care Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848963", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848962, "askingMemberId": 5066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88419", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department has considered adopting (a) mandatory sterilisation equipment, (b) spot checks, (c) minimum qualification standards and (d) other international best practices for nail and be", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Disease Control: Personal Care Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848962", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848961, "askingMemberId": 5066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88418", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department has made a comparative assessment of the regulation of nail and beauty salons in (a) the UK and (b) other European countries.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Disease Control: Personal Care Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848961", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848959, "askingMemberId": 5066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88417", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department has considered the introduction of (a) mandatory hygiene protocols and (b) licensing requirements for nail and beauty salons.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Disease Control: Personal Care Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848959", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848958, "askingMemberId": 5066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88416", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to monitor (a) cases of (i) parasitic infections and (ii) chemical sensitisation and (b) infection rates associated with poor hygiene practices in nail and beaut", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Disease Control: Personal Care Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848958", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848994, "askingMemberId": 5055, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "88415", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many National Fraud Intelligence Bureau 1D dating scam offences were recorded in the (a) 2024-25, (b) 2023-24. (c) 2019-20 and (d) 2014-15 financial year.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848994", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848993, "askingMemberId": 5055, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "88414", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what information her Department collects on romance fraud.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848993", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848835, "askingMemberId": 5055, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88413", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if she will hold discussions with train companies on enforcing rules relating to quiet carriages.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Railways: Standards", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848835", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848833, "askingMemberId": 5055, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88412", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if his Department will make an assessment of the potential impact of the level of SEND diagnoses on levels of welfare spending.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Social Security Benefits: Special Educational Needs", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848833", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849016, "askingMemberId": 5054, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88411", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if her Department will take steps to ensure that banks enable prospective customers to open bank accounts using (a) Digital ID and (b) eVisas.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Bank Services: Proof of Identity", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849016", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849168, "askingMemberId": 5052, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88410", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will make alternative funding available for community organisations after the UK Shared Prosperity Fund comes to an end in March 2026.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "UK Shared Prosperity Fund", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849168", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849165, "askingMemberId": 5052, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88409", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to ensure that funding for alternative learning and skills provision will be available after UK Shared Prosperity Fund comes to an end in March 2026.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "UK Shared Prosperity Fund", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849165", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849189, "askingMemberId": 5050, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88408", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether his Department has made an assessment of the potential impact of offering publicly funded (a) services and (b) activities to asylum seekers on local community cohesion.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Asylum: Community Relations", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849189", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849188, "askingMemberId": 5050, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88407", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment she has made of the potential impact of (a) illegal waste dumping and (b) fly-tipping on rural communities.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Fly-tipping: Rural Areas", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849188", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849187, "askingMemberId": 5050, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88406", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners released early under automatic release provisions have subsequently been reconvicted.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prisoners' Release: Reoffenders", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849187", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849186, "askingMemberId": 5050, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88405", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what data his Department holds on the number of newly built homes purchased by non-UK nationals in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Housing: Construction", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849186", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849185, "askingMemberId": 5050, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88404", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether her Department holds data on (a) taxes paid and (b) the cost of public services used by migrants who have arrived in the UK within the last 10 years.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Social Security Benefits and Taxation: Immigration", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849185", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849184, "askingMemberId": 5050, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88403", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much was spent on benefit payments to foreign nationals in the 2024-2025 financial year.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Social Security Benefits: Foreign Nationals", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849184", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849183, "askingMemberId": 5050, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88402", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the projected fiscal impact of net migration on public spending over the next five years.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Migration: Economic Situation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849183", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849182, "askingMemberId": 5050, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88401", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate she has made of the cost to the NHS of providing healthcare to (a) asylum seekers and (b) refugees in the last financial year.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Health Services: Asylum", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849182", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849181, "askingMemberId": 5050, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88400", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the number of individuals working without the legal right to do so in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Undocumented Workers", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849181", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849180, "askingMemberId": 5050, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88399", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many recorded offences involved individuals with pending asylum applications in the last 12 months.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Asylum: Offenders", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849180", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849179, "askingMemberId": 5050, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88398", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department plans to publish more detailed statistics on criminal convictions among people with pending asylum claims.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Asylum: Convictions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849179", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849175, "askingMemberId": 5047, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88397", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that the Child Maintenance Service do not send arrears letters to people who pay on time.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Child Maintenance Service", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849175", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849172, "askingMemberId": 5047, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88396", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to help reduce Child Maintenance Service (a) response and (b) decision times.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Child Maintenance Service: Standards", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849172", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849170, "askingMemberId": 5047, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88395", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to ensure the Child Maintenance Service provides proof, if requested, of calculations of collection fees.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Child Maintenance Service: Fees and Charges", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849170", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849163, "askingMemberId": 5047, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88394", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make and assessment of the adequacy of funding for the voluntary sector through the Crisis Resilience Fund.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Crisis and Resilience Fund: Civil Society", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849163", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849161, "askingMemberId": 5047, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88393", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to (a) research the causes of ankyloglossia and (b) improve early diagnosis of that condition.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Tongue-tie: Babies", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849161", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849160, "askingMemberId": 5047, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88392", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department has made an assessment of the potential merits of publishing a national strategy for (a) palliative and (b) end of life care.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Palliative Care", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849160", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848875, "askingMemberId": 5034, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "88391", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of mandating a minimum aftercare period for trees planted as a condition of planning permissions for new homes.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848875", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848874, "askingMemberId": 5034, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "88390", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if his Department will make an assessment of the number of new trees required as part of planning permissions which are (a) never planted and (b) not maintained for the required ", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848874", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848873, "askingMemberId": 5034, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88389", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to help protect kelp forests in UK waters.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Kelp: Conservation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848873", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848872, "askingMemberId": 5034, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "88388", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment her Department has made of the potential impact of rhododendron sales on woodland (a) management and (b) restoration.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848872", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849101, "askingMemberId": 5029, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "88387", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment her Department has made of the potential economic cost of value of road freight travel time due to delays at Moor Farm roundabout in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849101", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849100, "askingMemberId": 5029, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "88386", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment her Department has made of the value of road freight travel time through Moor Farm roundabout in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849100", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849099, "askingMemberId": 5029, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88385", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment her Department has made on the value of road freight journeys through Moor Farm roundabout in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "A19: Freight", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849099", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849098, "askingMemberId": 5029, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "88384", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many holding objections have been issued by National Highways on applications in the North East of England due to the potential impact on Moor Farm roundabout.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849098", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849096, "askingMemberId": 5029, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "88383", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many holding objections have been issued by National Highways in (a) England and (b) the North East of England in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849096", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849118, "askingMemberId": 4942, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88382", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to improve (a) transparency and (b) communication in cases of alleged armed forces pension overpayments.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Armed Forces: Workplace Pensions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849118", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849108, "askingMemberId": 4934, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88381", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to improve the speed of arrhythmia diagnoses in integrated care systems.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Heart Diseases: Diagnosis", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849108", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849106, "askingMemberId": 4934, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88380", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his department has made of trends in the levels of variation in integrated care systems in access to prolonged ambulatory ECG monitoring.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Heart Diseases: Screening", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849106", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849105, "askingMemberId": 4934, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88379", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department has made an assessment of the potential impact of longer duration ambulatory ECG monitoring on stroke prevention.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Strokes: Health Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849105", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849035, "askingMemberId": 4934, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88378", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to increase (a) awareness of the symptoms, (b) diagnosis and (c) treatment of ovarian cancer in Shropshire.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ovarian Cancer: Shropshire", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849035", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849124, "askingMemberId": 4918, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-17T00:00:00", "uin": "88377", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how the 10 year Workforce Plan will help tackle regional variations in access to specialist care for people with (a) long-term and (b) complex conditions.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849124", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849123, "askingMemberId": 4918, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-17T00:00:00", "uin": "88376", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if his Department will publish detailed independent workforce modelling ahead of publication of the 10 Year Workforce Plan.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849123", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849120, "askingMemberId": 4918, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88375", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that child maintenance calculations adequately reflect disparities in parents' earning, regardless of custody arrangements.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Children: Maintenance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849120", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849149, "askingMemberId": 4864, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88374", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether the Leasehold and Commonhold Reform Bill will include provisions to grant leaseholders of houses the same Right of First Refusal as leaseholders of flats.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Leasehold: Reform", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849149", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849148, "askingMemberId": 4864, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88373", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether he plans to introduce legislative measures to prevent freeholders from demanding disproportionate payments from leaseholders for historic breaches of leasehold covenants.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Freehold", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849148", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849147, "askingMemberId": 4864, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88372", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what discussions he has had with the Solicitors Regulation Authority (SRA) on steps to help reduce investigation times by the SRA.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Solicitors Regulation Authority", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849147", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849130, "askingMemberId": 4864, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "88371", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether he has made an assessment of the potential merits of prohibiting freeholders from seeking financial redress for breaches of leasehold covenants that occurred prior to the", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849130", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849129, "askingMemberId": 4864, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "88370", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether he has made an assessment of the potential merits of a statutory time limit within which freeholders may seek financial redress for alleged breaches of leasehold covenant", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849129", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849070, "askingMemberId": 4853, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88369", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether protocols are in place to ensure that victims of crimes are contacted if the perpetrator is mistakenly released from prison.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prisoners' Release: Victims", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849070", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849127, "askingMemberId": 4827, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88368", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assessment she has made of the implications for her polices of reports that UK weapons are being used in the Sudanese conflict.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Sudan: Arms Trade", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849127", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849126, "askingMemberId": 4827, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88367", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what steps she is taking to conduct due diligence when licensing arms transfers to the United Arab Emirates to prevent weapons being diverted to Sudan.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Sudan: Arms Trade", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849126", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849125, "askingMemberId": 4827, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88366", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, if she will take diplomatic steps to secure guarantees that humanitarian (a) assistance will be delivered safely and (b) corridors will be opened for civilians in Sudan.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Sudan: Humanitarian Aid", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849125", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848848, "askingMemberId": 4827, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88365", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will take steps to remove unpaid carers in Northern Ireland from the scope of the Timms Review.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Personal Independence Payment Assessment Review", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848848", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848979, "askingMemberId": 4824, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "88364", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the number of prison officers subject to dismissal following recent changes to Skilled Worker visa salary thresholds; and what assessment he has made of the potential impact of those ", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848979", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848856, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88363", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment she has made of the relative operational cost increases for (a) rail freight and (b) road freight during the period from 2011 when fuel duty was first frozen for HGVs.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Freight: Fuels Excise Duties", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848856", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848855, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88362", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what protections exist to protect land and operations afforded to rail freight from (a) the risks of redevelopment and (b) other legal and commercial challenges; and what assessment she has made of the adequacy", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Railways: Freight", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848855", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848854, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "88361", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent estimate she has made of the potential impact of (a) her rail reform policies and (b) the establishment of Great British Railways on costs to the public purse.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848854", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848853, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88360", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many civil servants are working on rail reform.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Railways: Civil Servants", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848853", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848852, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88359", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions (a) she and (b) the Minister for Rail has had with the rail freight industry on the Railways Bill.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Railways: Freight", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848852", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848851, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "88358", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when she plans to publish a (a) draft licence for Great British Railways and (b) consultation on the licence terms.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848851", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848850, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88357", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when she plans to publish a (a) draft access and usage policy for Great British Railways and (b) consultation for this policy.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Great British Railways", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848850", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848842, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88356", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much (a) their Department and (b) its arm\u2019s length bodies have spent on (i) installing electric vehicle charging facilities and (ii) purchasing electric vehicles since 4 July 2024; and what estimate", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Department for Work and Pensions: Electric Vehicles", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848842", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848841, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88355", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much (a) their Department and (b) its arm\u2019s length bodies have spent on (i) installing electric vehicle charging facilities and (ii) purchasing electric vehicles since 4 July 2024; and what estimate their Dep", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ministry of Defence: Electric Vehicles", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848841", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848840, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88354", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, how much (a) their Department and (b) its arm\u2019s length bodies have spent on (i) installing electric vehicle charging facilities and (ii) purchasing electric vehicles since 4 ", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office: Electric Vehicles", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848840", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848839, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88353", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much (a) their Department and (b) its arm\u2019s length bodies have spent on (i) installing electric vehicle charging facilities and (ii) purchasing electric vehicles since 4 July 2024; and what estimate their De", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cabinet Office: Electric Vehicles", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848839", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848838, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88352", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much (a) their Department and (b) its arm\u2019s length bodies have spent on (i) installing electric vehicle charging facilities and (ii) purchasing electric vehicles since 4 July 2024; and what estimate their Depart", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Treasury: Electric Vehicles", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848838", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848837, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88351", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 24 February 2025 to Question 31540 on Entry Clearances: Overseas Students, whether her Department has considered using (a) Programme for International Student Assessment resu", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Entry Clearances: Overseas Students", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848837", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848984, "askingMemberId": 4805, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88350", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether her Department has made an assessment of the potential impact of increasing Statutory Maternity Pay to the level of the National Living Wage on women\u2019s labour market (a) participation and (b) re", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Maternity Pay: Living Wage", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848984", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848849, "askingMemberId": 4804, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "88349", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will list each meeting her Department has had with Wealden District Council as a planning authority in relation to placing asylum seekers at the Crowborough Training Camp.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848849", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849036, "askingMemberId": 4790, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88348", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what steps she is taking to increase UK humanitarian aid to protect (a) women and (b) children targeted by sexual violence in Sudan.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Sudan: Humanitarian Aid", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849036", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849034, "askingMemberId": 4790, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88347", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions she has had with the British Library on resolving the industrial action by the Public and Commercial Services Union.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "British Library: Industrial Disputes", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849034", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848923, "askingMemberId": 4787, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88346", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to his oral answer on 21 October 2025, Official Report, col 789, what proportion of the increase in NHS budget was provided to the Queen Elizabeth Hospital King's Lynn Trust.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Queen Elizabeth Hospital King's Lynn NHS Foundation Trust: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848923", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849026, "askingMemberId": 4785, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-13T00:00:00", "uin": "88345", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if she will make an assessment of the potential impact of the Transport (Duty to Cooperate) Bill on the economy.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849026", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849049, "askingMemberId": 4764, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88344", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assessment she has made of the potential (a) economic and (b) diplomatic merits of ratifying the UK\u2013Cuba Political Dialogue and Cooperation Agreement.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cuba: Foreign Relations", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849049", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849048, "askingMemberId": 4764, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88343", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what is the planned timetable for the ratification of the UK\u2013Cuba Political Dialogue and Cooperation Agreement.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cuba: Foreign Relations", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849048", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849047, "askingMemberId": 4764, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88342", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what progress she has made on concluding the inter-departmental consultation process on the UK\u2013Cuba Political Dialogue and Cooperation Agreement.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cuba: Foreign Relations", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849047", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849046, "askingMemberId": 4764, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88341", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, whether she has had discussions with the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care on potential scientific exchange programmes with Cuba on (a) maternal health and (b) si", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cuba: Maternity Services and Sickle Cell Diseases", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849046", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849045, "askingMemberId": 4764, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88340", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to support countries in determining their own healthcare partnerships without external interference.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Development Aid: Health Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849045", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849044, "askingMemberId": 4764, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88339", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, whether she has made representations to her US counterpart on the imposition of visa restrictions on officials of third countries who cooperate with Cuba in the provision of ", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cuba: Visas", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849044", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849042, "askingMemberId": 4764, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88338", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the potential impact of the enhanced pre-donation testing process pilot on reducing the number of deferrals for low Hb levels.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Blood: Donors", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849042", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849041, "askingMemberId": 4764, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "88337", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what demographic data his Department considered when choosing blood donation centres to pilot the post donation testing for advanced Hb assessment.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849041", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849040, "askingMemberId": 4764, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "88336", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, which blood donation centres have begun a trial of the Post Donation Testing for advanced Hb assessments.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849040", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849039, "askingMemberId": 4764, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "88335", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what guidance her Department has issued to police departments on appropriate use of live facial recognition technology.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849039", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849038, "askingMemberId": 4764, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "88334", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment her Department has made of the impact of the real-terms freeze in the annual Cash ISA allowance on (a) pensioners and (b) other low-risk savers.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849038", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849037, "askingMemberId": 4764, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "88333", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment her Department has made of the potential impact of the household income threshold for childcare support on (a) labour market participation and (b) associated reductions in local economic activity.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849037", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849136, "askingMemberId": 4743, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88332", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what data his Department holds on how many people resident outside the UK received medical treatment on the NHS in each of the last three years.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Health Services: Foreign Nationals", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849136", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849134, "askingMemberId": 4743, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88331", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what data his Department holds on the cost to the public purse of treatment for people who came to Britain only for (a) health and (b) medical treatment in each of the last three years.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Health Services: Foreign Nationals", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849134", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849069, "askingMemberId": 4743, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88330", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will reinstate the winter fuel payment in full.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Winter Fuel Payment", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849069", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848862, "askingMemberId": 4736, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-13T00:00:00", "uin": "88329", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what discussions he has had with his Ministerial colleagues on the \u00a39.2 million Scottish Government funding for (a) skills and (b) training in BAE.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848862", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848992, "askingMemberId": 4698, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88328", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of defendants over the age of 18 who have been remanded by the police are released by the court at the first hearing on (a) sentence, (b) bail and (c) for other reasons.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Offenders", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848992", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848991, "askingMemberId": 4698, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88327", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of defendants under the age of 18 who have been remanded by the police are released by the court at the first hearing on (a) sentence, (b) bail and (c) for other reasons.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Young Offenders", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848991", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849203, "askingMemberId": 4679, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88326", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the annual budget was for the (a) National Institute for Health and Care Excellence and (b) Medicines and Healthcare products Regulatory Agency in each year since 2005.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Medicines and Healthcare Products Regulatory Agency and National Institute for Health and Care Excellence: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849203", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849202, "askingMemberId": 4679, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88325", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the annual budget was for the (a) Care Quality Commission, (b) UK Health Security Agency and (c) the Food Standards Agency in each year since 2005.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": " Department of Health and Social Care and Food Standards Agency: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849202", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849201, "askingMemberId": 4679, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88324", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people have been employed by (a) the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence and (b) the Medicines and Healthcare products Regulatory Agency in each year since 2005.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Medicines and Healthcare Products Regulatory Agency and National Institute for Health and Care Excellence: Staff", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849201", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849200, "askingMemberId": 4679, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88323", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people have been employed by (a) the Care Quality Commission, (b) the UK Health Security Agency and (c) the Food Standards Agency in each year since 2005.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Department of Health and Social Care and Food Standards Agency: Staff", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849200", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849198, "askingMemberId": 4679, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88322", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what the annual budget was for the (a) Competition and Markets Authority and (b) Financial Reporting Council in each year since 2005.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Competition and Markets Authority and Financial Reporting Council: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849198", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849196, "askingMemberId": 4679, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88321", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, how many people have been employed by the (a) Competition and Markets Authority and (b) Financial Reporting Council in each year since 2005.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Competition and Markets Authority and Financial Reporting Council: Staff", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849196", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848957, "askingMemberId": 4679, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88320", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the annual budget was for the (a) Pensions Regulator and (b) Health and Safety Executive in each year since 2005.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Health and Safety Executive and Pensions Regulator: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848957", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848956, "askingMemberId": 4679, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88319", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people were employed by the (a) Pensions Regulator and (b) Health and Safety Executive in each year since 2005.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Health and Safety Executive and Pensions Regulator: Staff", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848956", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848955, "askingMemberId": 4679, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88318", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the annual budget was for the (a) Payment Systems Regulator and (b) Financial Ombudsman Service in each year since 2005.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Financial Ombudsman Service and Payment Systems Regulator: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848955", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848953, "askingMemberId": 4679, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88317", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the annual budget was for the (a) Financial Conduct Authority and (b) Prudential Regulation Authority in each year since 2005.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Financial Conduct Authority and Prudential Regulation Authority: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848953", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848952, "askingMemberId": 4679, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88316", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people were employed by the (a) Payment Systems Regulator and (b) Financial Ombudsman Service in each year since 2005.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Financial Ombudsman Service and Payment Systems Regulator: Staff", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848952", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848950, "askingMemberId": 4679, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88315", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people were employed by the (a) Financial Conduct Authority and (b) Prudential Regulation Authority in each year since 2005.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Financial Conduct Authority and Prudential Regulation Authority: Staff", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848950", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848948, "askingMemberId": 4679, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88314", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what the annual budget was for the (a) Office of Communications and (b) Information Commissioner\u2019s Office in each year since 2005.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Information Commissioner's Office and Ofcom: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848948", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848946, "askingMemberId": 4679, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88313", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, how many people were employed by the (a) Office of Communications and (b) Information Commissioner\u2019s Office in each year since 2005.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Information Commissioner's Office and Ofcom: Staff", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848946", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848944, "askingMemberId": 4679, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88312", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the annual budget was for the (a) Water Services Regulation Authority and (b) Forestry Commission in each year since 2005.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Forestry Commission and Ofwat: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848944", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848942, "askingMemberId": 4679, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88311", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the annual budget was for (a) Natural England, (b) the Environment Agency, and (c) the Office for Environmental Protection in each year since 2005.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848942", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848941, "askingMemberId": 4679, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88310", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many people have been employed by (a) the Water Services Regulation Authority and (b) the Forestry Commission in each year since 2005.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Forestry Commission and Ofwat: Staff", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848941", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848938, "askingMemberId": 4679, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88309", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many people have been employed by (a) Natural England, (b) the Environment Agency, and (c) the Office for Environmental Protection in each year since 2005.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs: Staff", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848938", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848933, "askingMemberId": 4679, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88308", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what the annual budget was for the (a) Office of Gas and Electricity Markets, (b) Office for Nuclear Regulation and (c) Nuclear Decommissioning Authority in each year since 2005.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Public Bodies: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848933", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848932, "askingMemberId": 4679, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88307", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, how many people were employed by the (a) Office of Gas and Electricity Market, (b) Office for Nuclear Regulation and (c) Nuclear Decommissioning Authority in each year since 2005.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Public Bodies: Staff", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848932", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849011, "askingMemberId": 4630, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "88306", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference her Department's policy paper entitled Finance: Interministerial Standing Committee \u2013 17 October 2025, what options were discussed for enhancing the fiscal flexibilities available to devolved Governme", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849011", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848863, "askingMemberId": 4630, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88305", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 9 April 2025 to Question 43325 on Deposit Return Schemes: VAT, for what reason her Department is considering applying VAT to unredeemed deposits in the deposit return scheme in the context ", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Deposit Return Schemes: VAT", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848863", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848861, "askingMemberId": 4630, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88304", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 3 April 2025 to Question 42630 on Employers' Contributions: Welsh Government, what mechanism her Department will use to provide compensation for public services in Wales for the increase in", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Employers' Contributions: Welsh Government", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848861", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849132, "askingMemberId": 4613, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88303", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, when the Prime Minister plans to respond to the letter from the hon. Member for Brentwood and Ongar of 15 August 2025 on Lord Mandelson; and when she plans to formally respon", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prime Minister: Correspondence", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849132", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849133, "askingMemberId": 4612, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88302", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what the (a) scope and (b) expected timetable for Great British Energy \u2013 Nuclear\u2019s assessment of Scotland\u2019s capability for new nuclear power stations.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Nuclear Power Stations: Scotland", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849133", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848847, "askingMemberId": 4569, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88301", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 21 November 2024 to Question 13425 on Budget October 2024, whether its definition of working people has changed.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Budget October 2024", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848847", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848832, "askingMemberId": 4569, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88300", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of sewage discharges in the North West on (a) social and (b) economic well-being.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Sewage: North West", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848832", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848831, "askingMemberId": 4569, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88299", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of year-round fireworks displays by commercial venues (a) in and (b) near residential areas on social well-being.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Fireworks: Housing", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848831", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848830, "askingMemberId": 4569, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88298", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of grassroots football on (a) social well-being and (b) contribution to economic value; and what support she has made available to (a) AVRO FC", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Football", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848830", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848829, "askingMemberId": 4569, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88297", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment her Department has made of the (a) social and (b) economic benefits of theatres in towns; and what support the Department has provided to help secure the future of the Oldham Coli", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Theatres", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848829", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848828, "askingMemberId": 4569, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88296", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many people travelled by bus in Greater Manchester for each year from 2010 to date; and what assessment has her Department made of trends in the level of bus travel during the current spending period.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Bus Services: Greater Manchester", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848828", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848827, "askingMemberId": 4569, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88295", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment her Department has made of the potential impact of the proposed Metrolink tram extension in Greater Manchester; and if it plans to fund further (a) feasibility and (b) business case studies for ", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Trams: Greater Manchester", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848827", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849191, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "88294", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 22 April 2025 to Question 45056 on Artillery: Procurement, what he expects the in service date for RCH155 to be.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849191", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849084, "askingMemberId": 4510, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "88293", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what amount of UK ODA is projected to be allocated to tuberculosis (a) prevention and (b) treatment in Malawi in each of the next three financial years.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849084", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849083, "askingMemberId": 4510, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "88292", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, how much official development assistance funding was allocated for tuberculosis (a) prevention and (b) treatment in Malawi in each financial year since 2015-16.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849083", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849157, "askingMemberId": 4462, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88291", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much revenue has been raised by the introduction of VAT on schools; and how much has been spent on student transfers from public to state schools in the same period.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Private Education: VAT", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849157", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849156, "askingMemberId": 4462, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88290", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether her Department plans to support Kent County Council with levels of admissions following the introduction of VAT on private schools.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Private Education: VAT", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849156", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849155, "askingMemberId": 4462, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88289", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what correspondence she has had with (a) primary and (b) secondary schools to evaluate the impact of pupil transfers on (i) admissions, (ii) SEND provisions for existing students and (iii) SEND provisions for n", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Private Education: VAT", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849155", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849154, "askingMemberId": 4462, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88288", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many pupils have transferred from public to state schools since July 2024; and what discussions she has had with schools on the impact of those transfers on student to teacher ratios in classrooms.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Private Education: VAT", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849154", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849152, "askingMemberId": 4462, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88287", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many new teachers were appointed and funded directly from VAT receipts on public school fees since 1 January 2025 by (a) region and (b) local authority.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Private Education: VAT", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849152", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848998, "askingMemberId": 4436, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88286", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when he plans to respond to the letter dated 21 July 2025 and re-sent on 7 October 2025 from the hon. Member for Lancaster and Wyre and nine other hon. Members on Sodium Valproate.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Members: Correspondence", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848998", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849144, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88285", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 15 September 2025 to Question 75028 on France: Military Alliances, what his Department's policy on the procurement of (a) low-yield and (b) air-launched nuclear weapons to use on the bat", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Nuclear Weapons: Procurement", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849144", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848845, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88284", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Cabinet Office Freedom of Information Act response with reference FOI2025/12575, published on 5 September 2025. whether Ministerial flights on the (a) Envoy IV, (b) Voyager are carbon-offset", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Military Aircraft: Ministers", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848845", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848844, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88283", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the whether Simon Case is being remunerated for his work on the Team Barrow Delivery Board.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Simon Case", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848844", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849164, "askingMemberId": 4368, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88282", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade,  if he will take legislative steps to provide for an excluded contract waiver for charitable memberships in proposed secondary legislation on subscription contracts under the Digital Markets, Competiti", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Charities: Subscriptions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849164", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848858, "askingMemberId": 4368, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88281", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department plans to take to (a) monitor and (b) report on the operational impact of drones supplied to the Ukrainian armed forces; and what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the steps taken", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ukraine: Unmanned Air Systems", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848858", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849178, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88280", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will publish the submission for a May 2026 election pilot from the London Borough of Tower Hamlets; and whether the Best Value Envoys were consulted on or have reviewed tha", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Elections: Tower Hamlets", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849178", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849177, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88279", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 30 October 2025 to Question 84643 on Infrastructure: Planning Permission, if he will publish a list of planning applications that have been submitted in", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Infrastructure: Planning Permission", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849177", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849176, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88278", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the incidence of unauthorised travellers frustrating Temporary Stop Notices by subdividing land into multiple plots.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Travellers: Caravan Sites", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849176", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849174, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88277", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 30 October 2025 to Question 84636 on Eden Project: Morecombe, if he will publish the Memorandum of Understanding; and what proportion of the \u00a350 million", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Eden Project: Morecambe", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849174", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849173, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88276", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 30 October 2025 to Question 84635 on English Devolution and Community Empowerment Bill, if he will list each organisation that the Government discussed ", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Mayors and Police and Crime Commissioners: Elections", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849173", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849171, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88275", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 20 October 2025 to Question 78283 on Councillors: Misconduct, and with reference to the Cabinet Office consultation principles, for what reason the Gove", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Councillors: Misconduct", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849171", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849169, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88274", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, which types of asylum seekers accommodation provided under section 95 of the Immigration and Asylum Act 1999 are subject to (a) council tax and (b) business rates; and what exemp", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Asylum: Housing", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849169", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849032, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88273", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 27 June 2025 to Question 61182 on Litter: Codes of Practice, and with reference to paragraphs 78 and 79 of the Pride in Place strategy, published on 25 Septem", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Fly-tipping and Litter", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849032", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849031, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88272", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 27 June 2025 to Question 61182 on Litter: Codes of Practice, whether guidance has been given to local authorities on issuing fines under the Section 33 of the", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Sewers: Waste Disposal", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849031", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849030, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88271", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what are the internal areas within the proposed Chinese Embassy that would be exempt from UK inspection and verification.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Chinese Embassy: Planning Permission", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849030", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849028, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88270", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what is his Department\u2019s policy on commissioning publicity material in foreign languages aimed at individuals who permanently reside in the UK.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government: Publicity", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849028", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848976, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88269", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what steps she is taking to safeguard budgets for Monitoring, Evaluation and Learning within aid programmes.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Development Aid", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848976", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848975, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88268", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, to what extent (a) uranium fuel used at Sizewell B and (b) Britain\u2019s nuclear energy supply chain relies on imports from (i) Rosatom and (ii) its subsidiaries; and what steps he is taking to e", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Rosatom: Sanctions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848975", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848974, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88267", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what discussions she has had with (a) other donor countries and (b) the private sector on encouraging further pledges to the Global Fund.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Global Fund to Fight AIDS, Tuberculosis and Malaria", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848974", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848973, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88266", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, when the final pledging event for the Global Fund\u2019s eighth replenishment will take place; and what the UK\u2019s anticipated contribution is.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Global Fund to Fight AIDS, Tuberculosis and Malaria", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848973", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848972, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88265", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what (a) monitoring and (b) evaluation mechanisms are in place to measure the impact of UK-supported programmes under the Global Fund on mortality rates for (i) AIDS, (ii) tu", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Global Fund to Fight AIDS, Tuberculosis and Malaria: Research", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848972", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848971, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88264", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what plans she has to enable UK life-sciences (a) companies and (b) researchers to participate in the Global Fund\u2019s efforts to tackle (i) AIDS, (ii) tuberculosis and (iii) ma", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Global Fund to Fight AIDS, Tuberculosis and Malaria: Research", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848971", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848970, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88263", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what safeguards are in place to ensure that UK funding to (a) UNRWA and (b) other multilateral agencies is used (i) responsibly and (ii) effectively.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Development Aid", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848970", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848969, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88262", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what discussions she has had with (a) her US counterpart and (b) other international partners on the future role of UNRWA in Gaza.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Gaza: UNRWA", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848969", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848968, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88261", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what consideration her Department has given to exploring new minilateral partnerships to deliver aid.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Development Aid", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848968", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848967, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88260", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what recent assessment she has made of the potential impact of Official Development Assistance-funded programmes in countering (a) disinformation and (b) destabilisation effo", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Development Aid: National Security", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848967", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848966, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88259", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what coordination mechanisms exist between her Department, the Ministry of Defence and the Home Office to align aid spending with (a) defence, (b) resilience and (c) counter-", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Development Aid: Departmental Coordination", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848966", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848889, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88258", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment her Department has made of the potential impact of the Extended producer responsibility scheme on inflation for consumers in the (a) food and (b) retail sectors.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Recycling: Inflation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848889", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848888, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88257", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment her Department has made of the impact of the extended producer responsibility scheme on (a) glass manufacturing and (b) the jobs it supports.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Glass: Recycling", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848888", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848887, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88256", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what discussions he has had with the Mayor of the West Midlands on the resilience of supply chains in the West Midlands.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Supply Chains: West Midlands", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848887", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848886, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88255", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, pursuant to the Answer of 27 Oct 2025 to Question 83835, if he will publish a list of (a) businesses and (b) sectors in Walsall Borough with whom they consulted.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Manufacturing Industries: West Midlands", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848886", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848885, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88254", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 29 October 2025 to Question 83834, what discussions his Department has had with the Department of Health and Social Care on the potential impact on NHS workforce (a) recruitmen", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Nurses: Training", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848885", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848884, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88253", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 29 October 2025 to Question 83834, what assessment his Department has made of the (a) short and (b) medium term impact of this policy on the number of nurses in training betwee", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Nurses: Training", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848884", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848883, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88252", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 29 October 2025 to Question 83834, with reference to his Department\u2019s decision to withdraw funding for Level 7 apprenticeships from January 2026, what evidence from Skills Engl", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Nurses: Training", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848883", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848881, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88251", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions has she had with HM Treasury on reinstating funding for Aldridge train station.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Railway Stations: Aldridge", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848881", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848880, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88250", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions she has had with the Mayor of the West Midlands on reinstating funding for Aldridge train station.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Railway Stations: Aldridge", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848880", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849199, "askingMemberId": 4320, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "88249", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many cases awaiting trial are related to non-payment of the BBC license fee by (a) age and (b) sex.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849199", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849197, "askingMemberId": 4320, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "88248", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many cases awaiting trial are related to non-payment of the BBC license fee.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849197", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848997, "askingMemberId": 4267, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88247", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if his Department will take steps to review the outcomes of Family Court cases where experts unregulated by the Health and Care Professions Council were used; and to ensure that children removed from their mother", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Family Courts: Expert Evidence", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848997", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848996, "askingMemberId": 4267, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88246", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment his Department has made of the potential impact of experts unregulated by the Health and Care Professions Council (a) diagnosing parental alienation and (b) advising courts on residence transfers ", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Family Courts: Expert Evidence", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848996", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848894, "askingMemberId": 4126, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88245", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to support kinship carers in Newcastle upon Tyne East and Wallsend constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Kinship Care: Newcastle upon Tyne East and Wallsend", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848894", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849064, "askingMemberId": 4107, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "88244", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps she is taking to support car dealers in Northern Ireland unable to access the UK market for vehicles due to manufacturers choosing not to dual approve under the UK\u2013NI type approval system.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849064", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848878, "askingMemberId": 4084, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88243", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to ensure provisions in the Children's Wellbeing and Schools Bill maintain data protection requirements.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Children's Wellbeing and Schools Bill", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848878", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848877, "askingMemberId": 4084, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88242", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what consultation her Department undertook with parents of home educated children on the Children's Wellbeing and Schools Bill.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Home Education", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848877", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848876, "askingMemberId": 4084, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88241", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the increase to Employer's National Insurance Contributions on rape crisis centres.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Rape Crisis Centres: Employers' Contributions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848876", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848954, "askingMemberId": 4066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88240", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether he has made an assessment of the potential impact of cancelling of the A12 widening scheme on sites of proposed housing developments in local plans in local authorities i", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "A12: Repairs and Maintenance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848954", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848951, "askingMemberId": 4066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88239", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when her Department notified the Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government of its plan to cancel the A12 widening scheme.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "A120: Repairs and Maintenance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848951", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848949, "askingMemberId": 4066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88238", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment her Department has made of the cost-benefit ratio for the proposed A120 dualling scheme.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "A120: Repairs and Maintenance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848949", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848947, "askingMemberId": 4066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88237", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 14 October 2025 to Questions 77047 on East Anglia Rail Franchise: Nationalisation, when she will publish the services agreement.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "East Anglia Rail Franchise: Nationalisation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848947", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848945, "askingMemberId": 4066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88236", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when she will publish the full comparative benefit cost ratios of the transport schemes which she announced as (a) approved and (b) cancelled on 8 July 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Transport: Cost Benefit Analysis", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848945", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848943, "askingMemberId": 4066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88235", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what his expected timetable is for when the Norwich to Tilbury Great Grid upgrade will be fully operational.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "National Grid: East of England", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848943", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848940, "askingMemberId": 4066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88234", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, on what date she expects to publish the UK-EU treaty text on Gibraltar.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Gibraltar: UK Relations with EU", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848940", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848939, "askingMemberId": 4066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88233", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, from which budget within her Department's resources she expects to fund her Department's contributions for payments to Mauritius under the UK-Mauritius Treaty.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Chagos Islands: Sovereignty", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848939", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848937, "askingMemberId": 4066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88232", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, by what date has the Government of Mauritius requested that the first payment be made under the UK-Mauritius Treaty.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Chagos Islands: Sovereignty", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848937", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848935, "askingMemberId": 4066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88231", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, whether Mauritius have notified her of contact with (a) India and (b) other third countries to coordinate visits to the Chagos Archipelago.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Chagos Islands: Visits Abroad", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848935", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848934, "askingMemberId": 4066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88230", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, whether Mauritius has notified her of (a) plans for a future Marine Protected Area for the Chagos Archipelago and (b) measures to permit fishing.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Chagos Islands: Marine Protected Areas", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848934", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848920, "askingMemberId": 4051, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88229", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 5 November 2025 to Question 85743 on Infected Blood Inquiry, how much remuneration the Chair of the Infected Blood Inquiry receives for his work on that inquiry each year.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Infected Blood Inquiry", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848920", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848919, "askingMemberId": 4051, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88228", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 4 November 2025 to Question 85742 on Infected Blood Inquiry, when he expects the report for the Infected Blood Inquiry for the financial year 2024-2025 to be published.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Infected Blood Inquiry", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848919", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849014, "askingMemberId": 4032, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-13T00:00:00", "uin": "88227", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment the UK Health Security Agency has made of the fatality rate associated with invasive Candidozyma auris infection.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849014", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849013, "askingMemberId": 4032, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-13T00:00:00", "uin": "88226", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, for what reason Candidozyma auris was added to schedule 2 of the Health Protection (Notification) Regulations in April 2025;and if he will publish any public health risk assessments informing that ", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849013", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848914, "askingMemberId": 1591, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88225", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to ensure farmers receive support for instances of flooding in winter 2025-26.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Agriculture: Floods", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848914", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848913, "askingMemberId": 1591, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88224", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to fund flooding defence systems in winter 2025-26.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Flood Control: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848913", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848912, "askingMemberId": 1591, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88223", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much funding the Environment Agency received for river and stream maintenance in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Rivers: Repairs and Maintenance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848912", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848911, "askingMemberId": 1591, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "88222", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much funding the Environment Agency received in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848911", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848910, "askingMemberId": 1591, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88221", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether her Department holds data on the estimated cost of flood losses for (a) insured properties and (b) uninsured properties in each year since 2015.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Housing: Floods", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848910", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848909, "askingMemberId": 1591, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "88220", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether her Department holds data on the number of properties in each flood risk zones that does not have insurance.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848909", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848908, "askingMemberId": 1591, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "88219", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether her Department holds data on the average insurance premiums for properties in each flood risk zone in each of last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848908", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848907, "askingMemberId": 1591, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "88218", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many new homes were built within areas classified as flood zone 3 in 2024-2025.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848907", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849145, "askingMemberId": 1506, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88217", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of\u00a021 October 2025\u00a0to Question 82284\u00a0on Russia: Sudan, what steps she is taking with international partners to (a) monitor and (b) respond to the invol", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Russia: Sudan", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849145", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849143, "askingMemberId": 1506, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88216", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 21 October 2025\u00a0to Question 82283\u00a0on Sudan: Arms Trade, what assessment she has made of the (a) role of the UAE in supplying weapons to warring part", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Sudan: Arms Trade", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849143", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849142, "askingMemberId": 1506, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88215", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent steps he has taken to help (a) increase the proportion of people with asthma that receive annual check-ups and (b) decrease preventable deaths from asthma.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Asthma: Health Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849142", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849141, "askingMemberId": 1506, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88214", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent steps he has taken to promote early detection of treatable diseases amongst (a) the public and (b) healthcare workers.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Diseases: Diagnosis", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849141", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849139, "askingMemberId": 1506, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88213", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent steps he has taken to help reduce (a) regional and (b) wealth inequalities in access to NHS dentistry services.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Dental Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849139", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849138, "askingMemberId": 1506, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88212", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to increase awareness of the (a) signs and (b) symptoms of mouth cancer.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Mouth Cancer: Health Education", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849138", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849153, "askingMemberId": 1491, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-13T00:00:00", "uin": "88211", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to ensure adequate access to free immigration advice in (a) Bristol and (b) the South West.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849153", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848960, "askingMemberId": 1491, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-13T00:00:00", "uin": "88210", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will ensure early diagnosis of primary bone cancer is included in the National Cancer Plan.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848960", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848929, "askingMemberId": 1491, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "88209", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to raise awareness among renters about the provisions of the Renters\u2019 Rights Act ahead of its implementation date.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848929", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848924, "askingMemberId": 1491, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "88208", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what his Department's timetable is for implementing the Renters\u2019 Rights Act (2025).", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848924", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848921, "askingMemberId": 1491, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "88207", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to ensure the availability of housing-related advice services in Bristol.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848921", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849029, "askingMemberId": 1409, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "88206", "questionText": "To ask the hon. Member for Blaenau Gwent and Rhymney, representing the House of Commons Commission, if the Commission will review the selection process for Oral Questions to identify ways to minimise the grouping of identical Questions.", "answeringBodyId": 18, "answeringBodyName": "House of Commons Commission", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849029", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848893, "askingMemberId": 1409, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "88205", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether all 48 F-35 aircraft ordered from Lockheed Martin under Tranche 1 been delivered.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848893", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848892, "askingMemberId": 1409, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "88204", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions he has had with NHS England on the level of risk of vaping on (a) fertility and (b) pregnancy.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848892", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848891, "askingMemberId": 1409, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "88203", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department has taken to improve its search procedures, in the context of the research and analysis entitled Security Investment Programme Evaluation, published by his Department on 5 September 2024", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848891", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848879, "askingMemberId": 1409, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "88202", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what changes have been made in the past twelve months to the monitoring of animal health disease under the Animal Health and Welfare Framework.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848879", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849053, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88201", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if she will take steps to help tackle (a) violence and (b) verbal abuse towards public transport workers in (i) Lincolnshire and (ii) other rural areas.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Public Transport: Crimes of Violence", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849053", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849025, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88200", "questionText": "To ask the hon. Member for Blaenau Gwent and Rhymney, representing the House of Commons Commission, for what purposes Parliamentary officials have used AI in the last 12 months.", "answeringBodyId": 18, "answeringBodyName": "House of Commons Commission", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "House of Commons: Artificial Intelligence", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849025", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848906, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88199", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will list the titles of all the events organised by Civil Service networks in her Department since 2017.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Department for Education: Equality", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848906", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848904, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88198", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, if she will list the titles of all the events organised by Civil Service networks in her Department since 2017.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office: Equality", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848904", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848903, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88197", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will list the titles of all the events organised by Civil Service networks in his Department since 2017.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Department of Health and Social Care: Civil Service", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848903", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848902, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88196", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will list the titles of all the events organised by Civil Service networks in his Department since 2017.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs: Equality", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848902", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848901, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88195", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many (a) single sex and (b) gender neutral bathroom facilities her Department provides in its premises.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Department for Transport: Sanitation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848901", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848899, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88194", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many (a) single sex and (b) gender neutral bathroom facilities his Department provides in its premises.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Department of Health and Social Care: Sanitation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848899", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848898, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88193", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) single sex and (b) gender neutral bathroom facilities her Department provides in its premises on Whitehall.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Home Office: Sanitation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848898", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848897, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88192", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) single sex and (b) gender neutral bathroom facilities his Department provides in its premises.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ministry of Justice: Sanitation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848897", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848896, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88191", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, how many (a) single sex and (b) gender neutral bathroom facilities his Department provides in its premises.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero: Sanitation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848896", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848895, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88190", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, how many (a) single sex and (b) gender neutral bathroom facilities his Department provides in its premises.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Department for Business and Trade: Sanitation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848895", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849194, "askingMemberId": 242, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "88189", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what has been the cost to the public purse of the indemnity to pharmaceutical companies in the context of Covid-19 vaccines.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849194", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849192, "askingMemberId": 242, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "88188", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many data subject access requests were received by the NHS in England in the last year for which figures are available; and how many of those requests were responded to with the requested data ", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849192", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849151, "askingMemberId": 242, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88187", "questionText": "To ask the hon. Member for Blaenau Gwent and Rhymney, representing the House of Commons Commission, for what reason the escalator from the House of Commons Members' car park does not cut off automatically when not in use.", "answeringBodyId": 18, "answeringBodyName": "House of Commons Commission", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "House of Commons: Escalators", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849151", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849150, "askingMemberId": 242, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88186", "questionText": "To ask the hon. Member for Blaenau Gwent and Rhymney, representing the House of Commons Commission, for how many days lift number 77 in the Palace of Westminster has been out of order this year; for what reason it remains out of order; and when it is expe", "answeringBodyId": 18, "answeringBodyName": "House of Commons Commission", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Palace of Westminster: Lifts", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849150", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849097, "askingMemberId": 242, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "88185", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 4 November to Question 86603, whether the \u00a3500 facilitation payment given to Hadush Kebatu was paid under the (a) Voluntary Returns Service or (b) Facilitated Return Scheme; ", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849097", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849093, "askingMemberId": 242, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "88184", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, pursuant to the Answer of 4 November to Question 86604, how many full time equivalent staff are employed in his office to (a) answer invitations and (b) answer Parliamentary Questions.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849093", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1849088, "askingMemberId": 242, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "88183", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many recipients of Personal Independence Payment are aged (a) 16, (b) 17 and (c) 18; how many of those are in full time education; and how many of those are in each constituency in England.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1849088", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848836, "askingMemberId": 178, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88182", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of the level of funding that her Department provides to the British Library, in the context of its industrial dispute with the Public and Commercial S", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "British Library: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848836", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848613, "askingMemberId": 5362, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88181", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will make an assessment of the potential impact of increasing public access to free, impartial financial guidance on (a) financial wellbeing and (b) household financial resilience.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Finance: Advisory Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848613", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848446, "askingMemberId": 5362, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88180", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to (a) improve water efficiency and (b) reduce leaks in the public water supply network.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Water Supply", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848446", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848445, "askingMemberId": 5362, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88179", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of unqualified operatives performing gas works on levels of public safety.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Natural Gas: Repairs and Maintenance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848445", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848444, "askingMemberId": 5362, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88178", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to help tackle unsafe gas works in homes.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Housing: Natural Gas", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848444", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848338, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88177", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, pursuant to the Answer of 31 October 2025 to Question 84448 on Timesharing: Regulation, whether his Department is considering taking steps to (a) require licensing and bonding of management companies, ", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Timesharing: Regulation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848338", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848322, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88176", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, pursuant to the Answer of 31 October 2025 to Question 84448 on Timesharing: Regulation, whether his Department plans to (a) review and (b) extend the 14 day exit right in the Timeshare, Holiday Product", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Timesharing: Regulation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848322", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848247, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-19T00:00:00", "uin": "88175", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 20 October 2025 to Question 81148 on Leasehold: Ground Rent and to the Answer of 15 September 2025 to Question 74455 on Ground Rent: Newcastle upon Tyne", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848247", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848221, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88174", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information his Department holds on (a) the cost to the public purse of providing NHS services to non-UK nationals and (b) what proportion of this cost the NHS Health surcharge covers.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Health Services: Migrants", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848221", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848220, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88173", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department plans to review the price of the NHS Health surcharge for visa applications.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Health Services: Migrants", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848220", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848219, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88172", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department plans to review the circumstances in which non-UK nationals can use the NHS free of charge.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Health Services: Foreign Nationals", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848219", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848507, "askingMemberId": 5359, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88171", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans her Department has to ensure that children with SEND have access to a GCSE curriculum irrespective of their educational setting.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Special Educational Needs: GCSE", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848507", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848498, "askingMemberId": 5359, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88170", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether she plans to create a Young Futures Hub for young people in Poole constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Young Futures Hubs: Poole", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848498", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848494, "askingMemberId": 5359, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88169", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what discussions his Department is having with relevant stakeholders on supporting small and medium sized businesses to provide apprenticeship schemes in Poole constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Small Businesses: Apprentices", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848494", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848207, "askingMemberId": 5359, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88168", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will take steps to ensure that NHS bank shifts are paid at the same rate as contracted overtime.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "NHS: Agency Workers", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848207", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848206, "askingMemberId": 5359, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88167", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what measures are in place to enable those parts of the country with a surplus of water to redistribute it to those areas in need.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Water Supply", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848206", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848568, "askingMemberId": 5356, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88166", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 10 July 2025 to Question 83716 on Food Labelling, will vegan sausages made in Great Britain and sold in Northern Ireland require packing that describes the pr", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Food: Labelling", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848568", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848418, "askingMemberId": 5356, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88165", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to paragraph 27 of her Department's policy paper entitled Protecting Animal Health: The The Government\u2019s Approach to Veterinary Medicines in Northern Ireland, updated on", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Veterinary Services: Northern Ireland", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848418", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848413, "askingMemberId": 5356, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88164", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to para 23 of her Department's policy paper entitled Protecting Animal Health: The Government\u2019s Approach to Veterinary Medicines in Northern Ireland, updated on 19 June ", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Veterinary Services: Northern Ireland", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848413", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848176, "askingMemberId": 5350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88163", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if her Department will make an assessment of the potential impact of abolishing the Vehicle Excise Duty exemption for classic cars on owners of (a) classic and (b) heritage vehicles.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Motor Vehicles: Excise Duties", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848176", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848621, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88162", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if the Government will publish the date for the planned full rollout targeted lung screening as recommended by the UK National Screening Committee.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Respiratory Diseases: Screening", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848621", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848619, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88161", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the (a) National Cancer Plan and (b) 10 Year Workforce Plan on the capacity for cancer diagnostic services to meet the (i) current workforce s", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cancer: Health Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848619", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848355, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88160", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what support his Department is offering to people affected by alleged sexual abuse relating to medical checks carried out between the 1970s and 2016 British Army recruitment processes.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Army: Sexual Offences", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848355", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848354, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88159", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to support families impacted by the Chinook ZD576 crash.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Chinook Helicopters: Accidents", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848354", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848353, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88158", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to learn from the Ministry of Defence\u2019s handling of the Chinook ZD576 crash.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Chinook Helicopters: Accidents", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848353", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848352, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88157", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will undertake a full review of the (a) technical, (b) legal and (c) regulatory failures that led to the Chinook ZD576 crash.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Chinook Helicopters: Accidents", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848352", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848351, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88156", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will meet with the families impacted by the Chinook ZD576 crash.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Chinook Helicopters: Accidents", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848351", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848350, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88155", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans his Department has to support the development of (a) accredited training routes and (b) apprenticeships for advice and information roles.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Advisory Services: Apprentices and Training", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848350", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848349, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88154", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what quantities of unprocessed plutonium remain within discharged irradiated spent nuclear fuel at (a) nuclear reactor sites and (b) Sellafield.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Plutonium", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848349", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848348, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88153", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what the current volume is of the civil plutonium stockpile in tonnes.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Plutonium", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848348", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848347, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88152", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what quantity of plutonium was added to the civil plutonium stockpile in the last year.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Plutonium", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848347", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848346, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88151", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps she is taking to decarbonise refrigerated transport.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Transport: Refrigeration", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848346", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848344, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88150", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment she has made of the environmental benefits of decarbonising refrigerated transport.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Transport: Refrigeration", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848344", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848343, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88149", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to increase regenerative farming.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Agriculture", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848343", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848342, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88148", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will set out a plan with (a) clear aims for stakeholders and (b) other steps to tackle issues facing chalk streams.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Rivers: Environment Protection", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848342", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848341, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88147", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to improve Catchment partnerships for chalk streams.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Rivers: Environment Protection", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848341", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848511, "askingMemberId": 5335, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88146", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the cost of (a) implementation for GP practices and (b) operation of the online appointment booking system introduced for GP practices in October 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "General Practitioners: Internet", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848511", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848443, "askingMemberId": 5335, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88145", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the minimum (a) English and (b) maths requirements are to complete (i) apprenticeships and (ii) vocational courses; and whether he plans to review those requirements.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Apprentices and Vocational Education: Qualifications", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848443", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848433, "askingMemberId": 5335, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88144", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of the support available to young people up to the age of 25 with education, health and care plans who are no longer accessing education.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Special Educational Needs: Young People", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848433", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848420, "askingMemberId": 5335, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88143", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of criteria for (a) parental and (b) professional involvement in decision-making for young people who lack the capacity to make the appropriate decisions", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Young People: Mental Capacity", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848420", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848419, "askingMemberId": 5335, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88142", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of support available for the transition into adulthood at age 18 for young people who were in care during early childhood before being (a) adopted or (b) placed unde", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Children in Care", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848419", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848172, "askingMemberId": 5330, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-13T00:00:00", "uin": "88141", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if his Department will review the covid-19 vaccination eligibility criteria for (a) frontline workers and (b) carers to ensure that (i) those who work in high-risk environments, (ii) those who prov", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848172", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848149, "askingMemberId": 5330, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-13T00:00:00", "uin": "88140", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the impact of pandemic-related delays on asylum seekers\u2019 eligibility for Indefinite Leave to Remain; and whether transitional provisions will be introduced to ensure th", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848149", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848261, "askingMemberId": 5329, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88139", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, if he will make an assessment of the potential implications for his policies of the Channel 4 Fact Check report entitled Value of UK arms imported by Israel, published on 29 September 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Arms Trade: Israel", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848261", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848492, "askingMemberId": 5327, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88138", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that Ofsted inspections are carried out in accordance with standardised procedures across childcare settings.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Childcare", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848492", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848169, "askingMemberId": 5327, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88137", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he has made an assessment with Secretary of State for Education of the potential impact of amending Schedule 17, Part 1, Paragraph 12(b) of The Human Medicines Regulations 2012 to enable sc", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Allergies: Children", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848169", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848607, "askingMemberId": 5321, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88136", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what steps his Department is taking to support small businesses in Northern Ireland by (a) simplifying guidance, (b) reducing administrative burdens and (c) assisting firms trading under the Windsor Fr", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Small Businesses: Northern Ireland", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848607", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848594, "askingMemberId": 5321, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88135", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, whether his Department has a timetable for implementing the recommendations of the Independent Review of the Windsor Framework by the Rt Hon Lord Murphy, published on 4 September 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 21, "answeringBodyName": "Northern Ireland Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Independent Review of the Windsor Framework", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848594", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848590, "askingMemberId": 5321, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88134", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what steps he is taking to ensure that projects funded by the Government through the City and Growth Deals initiative in Northern Ireland are delivered effectively; how progress will be monitored; and wh", "answeringBodyId": 21, "answeringBodyName": "Northern Ireland Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "City Deals and Local Growth Deals: Northern Ireland", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848590", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848586, "askingMemberId": 5321, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88133", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what steps he is taking to (a) reduce the potential impact of the Not for EU labelling requirement on GB goods sold in Northern Ireland on costs for businesses and (b) ensure that the (i) Duty Reimbursem", "answeringBodyId": 21, "answeringBodyName": "Northern Ireland Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "UK Internal Trade: Northern Ireland", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848586", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848372, "askingMemberId": 5320, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88132", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential implications for his policies of the report from the Royal College of Anaesthetists entitled Anaesthetic Workforce Census 2025: Key Interim Findings, pu", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Anaesthetics", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848372", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848417, "askingMemberId": 5319, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88131", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 4 November 2025 to Question 85623 on Bovine Tuberculosis: Vaccination, for what reason Northern Ireland was not included in the marketing authorisation.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Bovine Tuberculosis: Vaccination", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848417", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848208, "askingMemberId": 5319, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88130", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the Farming Profitability Review, which stakeholders in Northern Ireland gave evidence to the Review.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Farming Profitability Review: Northern Ireland", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848208", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848431, "askingMemberId": 5314, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88129", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether she has made an assessment of the potential merits of increasing the amount of protection provided on single-item purchases under section 75 of the Consumer Credit Act 1974.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Consumers: Protection", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848431", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848427, "askingMemberId": 5314, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88128", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the implications for his Department's policies of Turn2us's report entitled From stigma to support, published in October 2025; and what steps he is taking to increase the ", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Employment: Advisory Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848427", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848426, "askingMemberId": 5314, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88127", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether she will publish environmental impact assessments for plans to expand (a) Heathrow, (b) Luton and (c) Gatwick airports that include Scope 3 greenhouse gas emissions.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Airports: Greenhouse Gases", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848426", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848425, "askingMemberId": 5314, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88126", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the environmental impact assessment for the review of the Airports National Policy Statement will include Scope 3 greenhouse gas emissions.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Airports: Greenhouse Gases", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848425", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848422, "askingMemberId": 5314, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88125", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment her Department has made of the potential merits of international rail and sail through-ticketing that includes rail and ferry services.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ferries and Railways: Fares", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848422", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848168, "askingMemberId": 5314, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88124", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans her Department has to (a) contain, (b) clean up and (c) remediate radioactivity in the (i) air and (ii) sea as a result of (A) potential incidents and (B) accidents involvin", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Radioactive Materials: Shipping", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848168", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848439, "askingMemberId": 5310, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88123", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment her Department has made of the potential merits of extending Orchestra Tax Relief to (a) vocal performance groups and (b) choirs.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Choirs: Tax Allowances", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848439", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848438, "askingMemberId": 5310, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88122", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of late-night pharmacy provision in Newbury constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Pharmacy: Newbury", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848438", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848437, "askingMemberId": 5310, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88121", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of the Digital Services Tax; and whether she plans to review the rate at which it is set.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Digital Technology: Taxation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848437", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848436, "askingMemberId": 5310, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88120", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of risk-stratified screening on improving early detection of prostate cancer.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prostate Cancer: Screening", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848436", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848435, "askingMemberId": 5310, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88119", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to improve support for children with speech and language challenges in schools.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Special Educational Needs: Speech and Language Disorders", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848435", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848387, "askingMemberId": 5310, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88118", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment her Department has made of the potential impact of changes to the business rates system from 1 April 2026 on businesses in the horseracing industry.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Business Rates: Horse Racing", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848387", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848386, "askingMemberId": 5310, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88117", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment her Department has made of the potential impact of ending temporary business rates reliefs for retail, hospitality and leisure businesses from 1 April 2026 on racehorse training yards.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Business Rates: Horse Racing", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848386", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848549, "askingMemberId": 5302, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-13T00:00:00", "uin": "88116", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of further investment in agricultural supply chains in northern Nigeria to help promote the region\u2019s (a) climate resilien", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848549", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848323, "askingMemberId": 5301, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-18T00:00:00", "uin": "88115", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, pursuant to the Answer of 28 October 2025 to Question 80709 on Churches: Aerials, what estimate she has made of the average change in rents paid to (a) churches, (b) local authorities, ", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848323", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848452, "askingMemberId": 5300, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88114", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what steps her Department is taking with (a) the World Health Organization, (b) Gavi and (c) the Global Polio Eradication Initiative to help eradicate polio.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Polio: Disease Control", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848452", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848518, "askingMemberId": 5296, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88113", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer received on 23 October 2025 to Question 83549 on utilities: repairs and maintenance, what the evidential basis is to suggest potential misuse of emergency repair provisions by utilities i", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Utilities: Repairs and Maintenance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848518", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848516, "askingMemberId": 5296, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88112", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of the 23 October 2025 to Question 83549 on utilities: repairs and maintenance, what steps her Department is taking to improve regulations governing emergency repairs by utilities that di", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Utilities: Repairs and Maintenance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848516", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848513, "askingMemberId": 5296, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88111", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to reduce reliance on (a) voluntary and (b) charitable organisations to deliver core mental health services for older people; and what steps his Department plans to take to ", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Mental Health Services: Older People", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848513", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848512, "askingMemberId": 5296, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88110", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure that the goals for to older people's mental health services in the 10-Year Plan for the NHS are met in relation to (a) prevention, (b) early intervention, (c) acce", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Mental Health Services: Older People", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848512", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848510, "askingMemberId": 5296, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88109", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 1 July 2025 to Question 63264 on Reforms to Bathing Water Regulations 2013 and with reference to the Written Statement Reform of 28 October 2025 on The Bathin", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Water: Standards", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848510", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848429, "askingMemberId": 5289, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88108", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of UK humanitarian aid at reaching (a) remote and (b) isolated communities in Jamaica following Hurricane Melissa.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Jamaica: Hurricanes and Tornadoes", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848429", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848428, "askingMemberId": 5289, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88107", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, whether she plans to work with (a) local organisations and (b) diaspora communities in the UK to support long-term recovery projects for areas most affected by Hurricane Meli", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Caribbean: Hurricanes and Tornadoes", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848428", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848622, "askingMemberId": 5288, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88106", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that Civil Service (a) internships and (b) graduate recruitment programmes are (i) inclusive and (ii) accessible to candidates from all socioeconomic backgrounds.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Civil Service", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848622", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848532, "askingMemberId": 5283, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88105", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many 16 to 19 year olds are currently enrolled on each Level 3 qualification.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Further Education: Admissions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848532", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848409, "askingMemberId": 5283, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88104", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many carers have Carer\u2019s Allowance overpayment debts as a result of breaching the earnings limit in (a) England, (b) Wales, (c) Scotland and (d) Northern Ireland in the last six years for which data", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Carer's allowance: Overpayments", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848409", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848407, "askingMemberId": 5283, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88103", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many (a) men and (b) women are in debt to his Department through overpayments of Carers Allowance in relation to earnings.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Carer's allowance: Overpayments", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848407", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848406, "askingMemberId": 5283, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88102", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many Carer\u2019s Allowance overpayments there have been in relation to earnings in each year for the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Carer's allowance: Overpayments", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848406", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848403, "askingMemberId": 5283, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88101", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many overpayments of Carer\u2019s Allowance in relation to earnings there are in the value brackets (a) \u00a30.01.00 - \u00a3500.00, (b) \u00a3501.00 - \u00a31000.00, (c) \u00a31,001.00 - \u00a35,000.00, (d) \u00a35,000.01 - \u00a320,000 and ", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Carer's allowance: Overpayments", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848403", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848368, "askingMemberId": 5281, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88100", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to encourage privatised water companies to increase their financial transparency.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Water Companies: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848368", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848448, "askingMemberId": 5278, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88099", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to reduce wait times for adult gender services.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Gender Dysphoria: Health Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848448", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848447, "askingMemberId": 5278, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88098", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to support mass atrocity prevention in Sudan.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Sudan: Armed Conflict", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848447", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848497, "askingMemberId": 5272, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88097", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what progress has been made regarding on the manifesto commitment to roll out a direct entry scheme for detectives to boost investigation skills.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Police: Recruitment", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848497", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848496, "askingMemberId": 5272, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88096", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if it remains her policy to move to a multi-year police settlement model.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Police: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848496", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848495, "askingMemberId": 5272, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88095", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what role she plans for policing to play in achieving the objective of halving violence against women and girls in a decade.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Gender Based Violence", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848495", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848470, "askingMemberId": 5270, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88094", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to reduce court delays in relation to hearings for possession orders for anti-social behaviour.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Repossession Orders: Anti-social Behaviour", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848470", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848462, "askingMemberId": 5270, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88093", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of (a) reducing the threshold for a further closure order when a closure order under the Anti-social Behaviour, Crime and Policing Act 2014 has b", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Anti-social Behaviour", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848462", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848395, "askingMemberId": 5270, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88092", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what her planned timetable is for announcing further details on the regulation of private electric scooters, as indicated in the Advanced Manufacturing Sector Plan.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Electric Scooters: Regulation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848395", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848288, "askingMemberId": 5250, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88091", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimates his Department has made of the time it will take to get all service family accommodation up to the Decent Homes Standard.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Armed Forces: Housing", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848288", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848311, "askingMemberId": 5249, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88090", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of trends in levels of anaesthetic workforce availability on elective surgery waiting times.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Anaesthetics", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848311", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848230, "askingMemberId": 5249, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88089", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the guidance entitled Suitability: non-conducive grounds for refusal or cancellation of entry clearance or permission, published on 19 January 2024, whether Elon Musk would meet the ", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Elon Musk", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848230", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848218, "askingMemberId": 5249, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88088", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure a sustainable funding settlement for hospice and palliative care in (a) Herefordshire and (b) the country.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Hospices and Palliative Care: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848218", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848557, "askingMemberId": 5239, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88087", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether she has made an assessment of the potential merits of increasing the (a) Plastic Packaging Tax rate and (b) recycled content requirement to promote domestic recycling.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Plastics: Taxation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848557", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848556, "askingMemberId": 5239, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88086", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent progress she has made on the introduction of the Deposit Return Scheme in 2027.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Deposit Return Schemes", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848556", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848555, "askingMemberId": 5239, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88085", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will review the plastic waste export regime to help increase levels of domestic recycling.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Plastics: Waste", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848555", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848552, "askingMemberId": 5239, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88084", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to support access to (a) affordable minimally processed foods and (b) UK-grown fruit, vegetables and legumes in (i) Wiltshire and (ii) other rural areas.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Food: Prices", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848552", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848551, "askingMemberId": 5239, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88083", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of (a) ultra-processed foods, (b) palm oil and (c) single-use plastics on the environment impacts associated with supply chains; an", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Environment Protection: Supply Chains", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848551", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848548, "askingMemberId": 5239, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88082", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether (a) the healthy schools rating scheme and (b) similar programmes consider the degree of food processing in assessing school performance on healthy eating.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Schools: Processed Food", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848548", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848547, "askingMemberId": 5239, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88081", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will (a) collect and (b) publish data on the proportion of ultra-processed foods in school meals (i) by region, (ii) by local authority and (iii) in Wiltshire.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Schools: Processed Food", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848547", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848546, "askingMemberId": 5239, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88080", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department takes through school food (a) standards and (b) guidance to tackle ultra-processed foods; and whether she has made an assessment of the potential merits of bringing forward further pro", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Schools: Processed Food", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848546", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848545, "askingMemberId": 5239, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88079", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether integrated care boards will be asked to report local baseline (a) data and (b) progress on reducing ultra-processed food consumption; and if he will publish a breakdown for (i) Wiltshire an", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Processed Food: Consumption", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848545", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848544, "askingMemberId": 5239, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88078", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he has made an assessment of the potential merits of setting a national target to reduce the proportion of ultra-processed foods in the UK diet by 2030.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Processed Food", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848544", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848543, "askingMemberId": 5239, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88077", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether data collected from the NHS Food Scanner app is shared with third parties.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Food: Labelling", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848543", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848542, "askingMemberId": 5239, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88076", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an assessment of the potential impact of awarding Good choice endorsements to (a) artificially sweetened drinks, (b) energy drinks and (c) highly processed snacks on children's heal", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Health: Children", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848542", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848540, "askingMemberId": 5239, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88075", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether the (a) NHS Food Scanner app and (b) Good choice badge take into account the level of (i) food processing and the (ii) presence of industrial additives when determining which foods are heal", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Food: Labelling", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848540", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848539, "askingMemberId": 5239, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88074", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what criteria are used to determine what food choices qualify NHS Food Scanner app users for a Good Choice badge.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Food: Labelling", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848539", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848404, "askingMemberId": 5238, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88073", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of introducing (a) national guidance and (b) regulations on setting a minimum age for body piercings.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Skin Piercing: Age", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848404", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848260, "askingMemberId": 5221, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88072", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to help support agricultural livelihoods in Gaza; and what steps the Government is taking to ensure that UK-funded support for agricultura", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Gaza: Agriculture", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848260", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848259, "askingMemberId": 5221, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88071", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what proportion of the humanitarian aid budget for (a) the Gaza conflict and (b) all global humanitarian crises is specifically allocated for (i) social protection mechanisms", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Humanitarian Aid: Older People", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848259", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848618, "askingMemberId": 5205, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88070", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what (a) operating system and (b) version of that operating system is used at (i) Sevington inland border facility and (ii) other border control posts.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Inland Border Facilities: Ashford", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848618", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848617, "askingMemberId": 5205, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88069", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when the IT system at Sevington inland border facility was last updated.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Inland Border Facilities: Ashford", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848617", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848616, "askingMemberId": 5205, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88068", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to help ensure Border Control facilities have back-up plans in place in case of IT (a) systems failures and (b) service provider outages.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Inland Border Facilities: ICT", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848616", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848615, "askingMemberId": 5205, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88067", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to ensure Border Control IT systems operate with full functionality.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Inland Border Facilities: ICT", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848615", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848567, "askingMemberId": 5202, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88066", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if she will provide an update on the Government\u2019s plans to address pavement parking; and if she will set out a timetable for when local authorities will be given further powers to tackle this issue.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Parking: Pedestrian Areas", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848567", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848509, "askingMemberId": 5197, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88065", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that where objections to a Geographical Indication (GI) application are upheld under assimilated Regulation (EU) 2019/787 the applicant bo", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Origin Marking", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848509", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848340, "askingMemberId": 5196, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88064", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much financial support his Department provides annually to children and young people with cancer and their families travelling for treatment.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cancer: Out of Area Treatment", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848340", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848339, "askingMemberId": 5196, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88063", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he has made an estimate of the\u00a0average (a) distance travelled and (b) cost incurred by (i) children and (ii) young people from Scotland when attending cancer\u00a0treatment\u00a0in England;\u00a0and what\u00a0", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cancer: Out of Area Treatment", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848339", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848332, "askingMemberId": 5196, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88062", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of Liquid Organic Hydrogen Carrier conversion projects being eligible for Net Zero Hydrogen Fund grant funding.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Net Zero Hydrogen Fund", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848332", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848331, "askingMemberId": 5196, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88061", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what steps his Department is taking to help support businesses to invest in (a) Liquid Organic Hydrogen Carriers and (b) other chemical hydrogen storage, including revenue certainty.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Hydrogen: Storage", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848331", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848330, "askingMemberId": 5196, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88060", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, if his Department plans to amend its Hydrogen Storage Business Model to include Liquid Organic Hydrogen Carrier storage.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Hydrogen: Storage", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848330", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848329, "askingMemberId": 5196, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88059", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what comparative assessment his Department has made of the costs of (a) Liquid Organic Hydrogen Carriers and (b) geological storage for hydrogen in the UK.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Hydrogen", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848329", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848328, "askingMemberId": 5196, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88058", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, whether the UK Hydrogen Strategy will consider the strategic potential of Liquid Organic Hydrogen Carriers.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Hydrogen", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848328", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848400, "askingMemberId": 5195, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88057", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what his planned timetable is for publishing the cross-government homelessness strategy.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Homelessness", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848400", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848313, "askingMemberId": 5186, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88056", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to ensure adherence to the Animals (Scientific Procedures) Act 1986 for the standards of (a) care and (b) accommodation for dogs; and how many times the Animals in ", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Animal Experiments: Dogs", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848313", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848390, "askingMemberId": 5182, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88055", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, whether funding for (a) immediate humanitarian needs and (b) crisis support is provided through the budget for Official Development Assistance.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Humanitarian Aid", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848390", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848389, "askingMemberId": 5182, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88054", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, when his Department last made an assessment of the effectiveness of the (a) planning practice guidance and (b) other aspects of the safety framework for grid-scale batteries.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Batteries: Storage", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848389", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848315, "askingMemberId": 5182, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88053", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 29 October to Question 84015 on Legal Aid Scheme: Ely and East Cambridgeshire, what criteria the Legal Aid Agency uses to assess the adequacy of access to legal aid services in Ely and E", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Legal Aid Scheme: Ely and East Cambridgeshire", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848315", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848314, "askingMemberId": 5182, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88052", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, when she plans to publish the findings from the consultation on the Equality (Race and Disability) Bill: mandatory ethnicity and disability pay gap reporting, which closed on 10 June 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 31, "answeringBodyName": "Women and Equalities", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Equal Pay: Disability and Ethnic Groups", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848314", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848310, "askingMemberId": 5182, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88051", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, pursuant to the Answer of 31 October 2025 to Question 84891 on Fuel Poverty: Ely and East Cambridgeshire, when he plans to publish regional fuel poverty figures for Ely and East Cambridgeshir", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Fuel Poverty: Ely and East Cambridgeshire", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848310", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848308, "askingMemberId": 5182, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88050", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 3 November to Question 85521 on Farmers: Mental Health and Productivity, for what reason the Department does not intend to undertake such research.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Farmers: Mental Health and Productivity", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848308", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848305, "askingMemberId": 5182, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88049", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 4 November 2025 to Question 85523 on Electoral Register: British Nationals Abroad, what steps he plans to take to ensure that overseas electors receive ", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Electoral Register: British Nationals Abroad", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848305", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848585, "askingMemberId": 5168, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88048", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure access to (a) diagnostic and (b) treatment options for women with heart valve disease.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Heart Diseases: Women", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848585", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848583, "askingMemberId": 5168, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88047", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the (a) number of referrals and (b) time taken to treat people with heart valve disease in each region.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Heart Diseases: Medical Treatments", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848583", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848312, "askingMemberId": 5164, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88046", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many times exchange of notes arrangements have been used in investigations relating to economic crime to share beneficial ownership information between the UK on the one hand and the Crown Depende", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Economic Crime: British Overseas Territories and Crown Dependencies", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848312", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848177, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88045", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate she has made of how much money was sent abroad in remittance payments in 2024 by destination country.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Remittances", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848177", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848284, "askingMemberId": 5154, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88044", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether he plans to review planning requirements for converting homes into houses in multiple occupation.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Multiple Occupation: Planning Permission", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848284", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848229, "askingMemberId": 5154, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88043", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what assessment his Department has made of the potential impact of small modular reactor projects on (a) long-term waste management and (b) decommissioning.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Small Modular Reactors", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848229", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848228, "askingMemberId": 5154, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88042", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many asylum claims were made by people holding student visas by nationality in the last 12 months; and what assessment she has made of the potential implications for her policies of trends in the ", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Asylum: Overseas Students", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848228", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848227, "askingMemberId": 5154, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88041", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when her Department plans to launch its consultation on the future of the British National (Overseas) 5+1 Indefinite Leave to Remain visa route.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Visas: British National (Overseas)", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848227", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848166, "askingMemberId": 5154, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-18T00:00:00", "uin": "88040", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether her Department plans to reform the (a) Packaging Recovery Note (PRN) and (b) Packaging Waste Export Recycling Note (PERN) system to (i) address market imbalances that disadvant", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848166", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848165, "askingMemberId": 5154, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-18T00:00:00", "uin": "88039", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment her Department has made of the potential merits of strengthening waste regulations (a) for the list of approved destinations of and (b) on the environmental standards f", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848165", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848270, "askingMemberId": 5151, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88038", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to make it easier for people who cannot use the telephone to communicate changes in their circumstances online.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Department for Work and Pensions: Internet", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848270", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848500, "askingMemberId": 5142, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88037", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what discussions she has had with her (a) officials leading the UK's geographic and atrocity prevention thematic response and (b) diplomatic counterparts on options for prote", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Darfur: Armed Conflict", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848500", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848499, "askingMemberId": 5142, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88036", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assessment she has made of the implications for her policies of RSF violence against civilians in El Fasher and across Darfur; and whether it remains her policy to uphol", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Darfur: Armed Conflict", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848499", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848282, "askingMemberId": 5126, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88035", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how his Department plans to consult people with lived experience of dementia on the Modern Service Framework for Frailty and Dementia.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Health Services: Dementia and Older People", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848282", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848515, "askingMemberId": 5122, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88034", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will publish a national strategy for palliative and end of life care.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Palliative Care", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848515", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848175, "askingMemberId": 5112, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88033", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 29 October to Question 79968 on Palestine: Education, what discussions his Department has had with the Palestinian Authority on seeking an independe", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Palestine: Education", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848175", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848577, "askingMemberId": 5111, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88032", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the two-child benefit cap on working class people in Newton Abbot constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Poverty: Children", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848577", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848383, "askingMemberId": 5111, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88031", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when his Department plans to respond to the Freedom of Information Act request of 7 October 2025 by the hon. Member for Newton Abbot regarding meetings between Boris Johnson and Peter Thiel.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Members: Correspondence", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848383", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848286, "askingMemberId": 5111, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88030", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if she will take steps to introduce a discounted ticketing scheme for schools who want to take the train for school trips.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Railways: Educational Visits", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848286", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848285, "askingMemberId": 5111, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88029", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 3 November 2025 to Question 86440 on Deposit Return Schemes, if she will take steps to ensure the deposit return scheme allows (a) bottles and (b) other depos", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Deposit Return Schemes", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848285", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848138, "askingMemberId": 5111, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88028", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 4 October 2024 to Question 6887 on Plastics: Pollution, if he will make an assessment of the adequacy of the plastic waste export regime in promoting domestic", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Plastics: Waste", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848138", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848130, "askingMemberId": 5111, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "uin": "88027", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 15 July to Question 65984 on NHS Databases, what assessment he has made of the challenges of hosting the NHS Federated Data Platform on cloud services.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "NHS: Databases", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848130", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848514, "askingMemberId": 5110, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88026", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment she has made of the recommendations of Project Willow on the HEFA Cap delay.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Renewable Fuels: Grangemouth", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848514", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848385, "askingMemberId": 5110, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88025", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what steps her Department is taking to encourage collaboration between the UK and its international partners in the R&D sector.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Research: International Cooperation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848385", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848205, "askingMemberId": 5110, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88024", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what discussions he has had with the Scottish Government on reducing veteran homelessness in Scotland.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Veterans: Homelessness", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848205", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848199, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88023", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the press release entitled First-time buyers to benefit from 40,000 new homes on brownfield railway land, published on 30 June 2025, whether these properties will be earmarked for first-time b", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Housing: Derelict Land", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848199", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848198, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88022", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how Great British Railways will work with (a) Mayoral transport agencies and (b) Transport for London.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Great British Railways", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848198", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848197, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88021", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps her Department has taken to make train journeys more affordable since July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Railways: Fares", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848197", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848196, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88020", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the press release entitled \u00a31 billion backed renewal of broken bridges, ruined roads and tired tunnels and new Thames Crossing cash, published on 16 June 2025, whether it is her Department\u2019s p", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Bridges: Large Goods Vehicles", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848196", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848195, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88019", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will make an estimate of the annual cost to the public purse of the Office for Value for Money.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Office for Value for Money", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848195", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848194, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88018", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she has made an assessment of the potential implications for her policies of the press release by the Mineral Products Association entitled Landfill Tax reforms could trigger shortages and damage growth ambitions", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Landfill Tax", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848194", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848192, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88017", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans she has to ensure that low paid workers have adequate income in retirement.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Low Pay: Retirement", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848192", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848191, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88016", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps she plans to take to encourage self-employed workers to pay into private pension funds.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Pensions: Self-employed", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848191", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848190, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88015", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to page 29 of the document by the OBR entitled Fiscal risks and sustainability, published on 8 July 2025, whether her Department has made its own assessment of the long-term sustainabilit", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "State Retirement Pensions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848190", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848189, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88014", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if she has made an estimate of the number of food delivery drivers who operate on a provisional motorcycle driving license.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Delivery Services: Driving Licences", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848189", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848188, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88013", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make an estimate of the cost to the public purse of (a) consultations and (b) reviews conducted by his Department since 4 July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Department for Work and Pensions: Public Consultation and Reviews", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848188", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848187, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88012", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will make an estimate of levels of wage growth in the (a) public sector and (b) private sector since 4 July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Private Sector and Public Sector: Pay", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848187", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848186, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88011", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, pursuant to the Answer to Question 50271 on Holiday Accommodation: Bedfordshire, when he expects to publish that impact assessment.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Holiday Accommodation: Bedfordshire", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848186", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848185, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88010", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, pursuant to the Answer to Question 50646 on Trade Agreements: USA, what progress his Department has made on trade talks with the United States.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Trade Agreements: USA", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848185", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848184, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88009", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, if he will make an estimate of the cost to the public purse of (a) consultations and (b) reviews conducted by their Department since 4 July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Department for Business and Trade: Public Consultation and Reviews", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848184", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848183, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88008", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, if he will publish the sectoral analysis his Department undertook before selecting the IS-8 sectors in the Modern Industrial Strategy, published on 23 June 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Industry", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848183", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848530, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88007", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) people have applied to and (b) applications have been approved for the UK/European Applicant Transfer Scheme since that scheme was established.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Asylum: France", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848530", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848471, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88006", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many and what proportion of UK F-35 aircraft have had their stealth characteristics measured.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "F-35 Aircraft", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848471", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848468, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88005", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Fifty First Report of the Committee of Public Accounts of Session 2024-26 on The UK\u2019s F-35 stealth fighter capability, HC 1232, published on 31 October 2025, what steps is he taking to addre", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "F-35 Aircraft: Procurement", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848468", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848467, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88004", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many planes was the F-35 training squadron reduced by in order to facilitate the recent deployment of the Carrier Strike Group.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "F-35 Aircraft: Procurement", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848467", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848465, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88003", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to paragraph 5 of the Fifty First Report of the Committee of Public Accounts of Session 2024-26 on The UK\u2019s F-35 stealth fighter capability, HC 1232, published on 31 October 2025, for what reason t", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "F-35 Aircraft: Procurement", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848465", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848464, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88002", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate has he made of the additional whole-life costs of operating the F-35A as a Dual-Capable Aircraft.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "F-35 Aircraft: Procurement", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848464", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848463, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88001", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to paragraph 23 of the Fifty First Report of the Committee of Public Accounts of Session 2024-26 on The UK\u2019s F-35 stealth fighter capability, HC 1232, published on 31 October 2025, what progress ha", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "F-35 Aircraft: Procurement", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848463", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848461, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "88000", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what elements are included within the whole-life cost estimate of \u00a357 billion for the F-35 programme.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "F-35 Aircraft: Procurement", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848461", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848434, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87999", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 15 October 2025 to Question 82447 on Ministry of Justice: ICT, how many of the 1026 devices lost were (a) secure laptops, (b) secure mobile phones and (c) authentication devices.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ministry of Justice: ICT", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848434", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848424, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87998", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the answer of 20th October 2025 to question 79734 on Prison Accommodation: Procurement, by when a programme is planned to be developed to recommence delivery.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prison Accommodation: Procurement", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848424", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848423, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87997", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the answer of 20th October 2025, to question 79734 on Prison Accommodation: Procurement, which projects previously supplied by ISG have now been taken over.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prison Accommodation: Procurement", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848423", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848411, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87996", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans she has to update data used to construct indicators for the calculation of Police Main Grant.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Police: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848411", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848217, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87995", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to paragraph 13 of the Fifty-First Report of the Committee of Public Accounts of Session 2024-26 on The UK\u2019s F-35 stealth fighter capability, HC1232, published on 31 October 2025, what progress he ", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "F-35 Aircraft: Procurement", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848217", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848216, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87994", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many (a) letters and (b) emails the Prime Minister has received from the Member for Great Yarmouth.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prime Minister: Correspondence", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848216", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848214, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87993", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what progress he has made in building the sovereign Air Signature Assessment Facility.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "F-35 Aircraft: Procurement", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848214", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848213, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87992", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he will set out a timetable for the purchase of the remaining 90 F-35 aircraft his Department committed to purchasing.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "F-35 Aircraft: Procurement", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848213", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848212, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87991", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the timeline is for completion of new service accommodation at RAF Marham.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "RAF Marham", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848212", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848211, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87990", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what interim solutions he has identified to fill the capability gap left by delays to the SPEAR 3 missile programme.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Guided Weapons: Procurement", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848211", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848210, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87989", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to page 3 of the Fifty First Report of the Committee of Public Accounts of Session 2024-26 on The UK\u2019s F-35 stealth fighter capability, HC 1232, published on 31 October 2025, (a) what steps and (b)", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "F-35 Aircraft: Procurement", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848210", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848209, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87988", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many and what percentage of flying instructor roles are currently gapped within the F-35 programme.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "F-35 Aircraft: Procurement", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848209", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848506, "askingMemberId": 5086, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87987", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans the department has to improve retention of level 3 staff within the NHS.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "NHS: Labour Turnover", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848506", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848505, "askingMemberId": 5086, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87986", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans there are to widen pay bands for Level 3 Staff in the NHS.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "NHS: Staff", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848505", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848504, "askingMemberId": 5086, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87985", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps the government is taking to abolish leasehold tenures for (a) flats and (b) other properties.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Leasehold", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848504", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848503, "askingMemberId": 5086, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87984", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps the government is taking to cap service and estate management charges paid by residents.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Property Management Companies: Fees and Charges", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848503", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848601, "askingMemberId": 5085, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87983", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, on what date his Department will announce plans for the deployment of new nuclear generation projects at (a) Wylfa and (b) Oldbury.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Nuclear Power", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848601", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848451, "askingMemberId": 5084, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87982", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when his Department plans to undertake formal evaluation of the Trailblazer schemes currently in operation; and when that will be published.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Employment Schemes: Young People", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848451", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848450, "askingMemberId": 5084, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87981", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what (a) performance metrics and (b) outcome indicators his Department is using to assess Trailblazer schemes; and what role (i) improving mental health, (ii) tackling social isolation and (ii) supporti", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Employment Schemes: Young People", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848450", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848449, "askingMemberId": 5084, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87980", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his Department plans to publish details of (a) findings, (b) good practice and (c) value-for-money assessments from Trailblazer schemes.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Employment Schemes: Young People", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848449", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848566, "askingMemberId": 5081, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87979", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to improve support for veterans in (a) Hexham constituency, (b) Northumberland, (c) Newcastle and (d) the North East.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Veterans: North East", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848566", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848564, "askingMemberId": 5081, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87978", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to reform estate adoption in (a) Hexham constituency, (b) Northumberland, (c) Newcastle, and (d) the North East.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Housing Estates: North East", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848564", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848553, "askingMemberId": 5081, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87977", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, pursuant to the Answer of 4 November 2025 to Question 85401 on Public Houses: Rural Areas, what his planned timeframe is for publishing the outcome from the Call for Evidence on Reforming the licensing", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Public Houses: Rural Areas", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848553", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848531, "askingMemberId": 5081, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87976", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions her Department has had with stakeholders to improve tennis facilities in (a) Hexham constituency, (b) Northumberland, (c) Newcastle, (d) the North East and (e) England.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Tennis: Facilities", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848531", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848529, "askingMemberId": 5081, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-24T00:00:00", "uin": "87975", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions her Department has had with Northumberland County Council on the adequacy of support for children with special educational needs and disabilities in Hexham constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848529", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848380, "askingMemberId": 5081, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-26T00:00:00", "uin": "87974", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps the Department is taking to support public libraries in (a) Hexham constituency, (b) Northumberland, (c) Newcastle and (d) the North East.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848380", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848375, "askingMemberId": 5081, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-25T00:00:00", "uin": "87973", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the effectiveness of suicide prevention training for staff working in police custody suites in the North East.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848375", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848316, "askingMemberId": 5081, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-25T00:00:00", "uin": "87971", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what steps the Department is taking to improve mobile telephone signal in (a) Hexham constituency, (b) Northumberland, (c) Newcastle, (d) the North East and (e) England.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848316", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848167, "askingMemberId": 5081, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87970", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what steps his Department has taken to improve parental rights for workers in the North East.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Conditions of Employment: North East", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848167", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848359, "askingMemberId": 5078, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87969", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of planning restrictions on noise levels for heat pumps on installation of those pumps.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Heat Pumps: Planning Permission", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848359", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848366, "askingMemberId": 5072, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "87968", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether West Lindsey District Council has raised legal objections with her Department on housing asylum seekers at RAF Scampton.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848366", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848414, "askingMemberId": 5070, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87967", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the impact of waiting times at the First-tier Tribunal (Social Security and Child Support Chamber) on claimants\u2019 financial wellbeing.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Social Security and Child Support Tribunal", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848414", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848412, "askingMemberId": 5070, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87966", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department is taking to reduce waiting times for hearings at the First-tier Tribunal (Social Security and Child Support Chamber).", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Social Security and Child Support Tribunal", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848412", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848334, "askingMemberId": 5070, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87965", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she has made an assessment of the potential impact of gender bias in policing responses to allegations of domestic abuse or related offences; and what steps she is taking to ensure parity of t", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Domestic Abuse", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848334", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848321, "askingMemberId": 5070, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87964", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of the Online Safety Act 2023 to protect internet users from (a) suicide and (b) self-harm content on artificial intelligence platforms", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Internet: Self-harm and Suicide", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848321", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848318, "askingMemberId": 5070, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87963", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate her Department has made of the number of (a) children and (b) adults who are accessing mental health support through artificial intelligence platforms after being unable to access sta", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Mental Health Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848318", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848524, "askingMemberId": 5068, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87962", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that NHS Blood and Transplant donor exclusion policies (a) reflect up-to-date medical evidence and (b) do not unnecessarily restrict donor participatio", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Blood: Donors", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848524", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848523, "askingMemberId": 5068, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87961", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when his Department last reviewed NHS Blood and Transplant\u2019s donor eligibility policy on the use of unlicensed injectable substances.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Blood: Donors", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848523", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848522, "askingMemberId": 5068, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87960", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether the permanent exclusion of people who have used tanning injections is consistent with the current evidence base on the persistence of bloodborne infection risks.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Blood: Donors", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848522", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848521, "askingMemberId": 5068, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87959", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of replacing the lifetime blood donation deferral for people who have used tanning injections with a fixed-term exclusion period similar to tho", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Blood: Donors", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848521", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848520, "askingMemberId": 5068, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87958", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether NHS Blood and Transplant has made an assessment of the potential impact of the use of tanning injections more than (a) 12 months (b) three months prior to donating on blood safety.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Blood: Donors", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848520", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848519, "askingMemberId": 5068, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87957", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, for what reason people who have used tanning injections are permanently unable to donate blood.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Blood: Donors", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848519", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848502, "askingMemberId": 5068, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87956", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of the proposed international students levy on economic growth in (a) Leicester, (b) the East Midlands and (c) the United Kingdom; and if she will ensure the", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Overseas Students: Fees and Charges", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848502", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848501, "askingMemberId": 5068, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87955", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of the proposed international students levy on the competitiveness of UK universities.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Overseas Students: Fees and Charges", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848501", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848525, "askingMemberId": 5067, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87954", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to establish a timeline of when the new private rented sector database will be implemented.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Private Rented Housing: Databases", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848525", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848441, "askingMemberId": 5066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87953", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much Better Care Fund funding has been provided to each health and wellbeing board to support unpaid carers in each of the last three financial years.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Better Care Fund: Carers", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848441", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848410, "askingMemberId": 5066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87952", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will publish the evaluation commissioned by the National Institute for Health and Care Research on support for unpaid carers funded through the Better Care Fund undertaken in 2023-24.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Better Care Fund: Carers", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848410", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848408, "askingMemberId": 5066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87951", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much and what proportion of the Better Care Fund will be spent on supporting unpaid family carers in the 2025-26 financial year; and how much was provided for (a) short breaks and (b) respite f", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Better Care Fund: Carers", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848408", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848402, "askingMemberId": 5066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87950", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what was the cost to the public purse of supporting unpaid carers in England through the Better Care Fund in each of the last three financial years.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Better Care Fund: Carers", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848402", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848401, "askingMemberId": 5066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87949", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to his Department's plan Fit for the Future: 10 Year Health Plan for England, when he plans to publish more information about the intended reforms to the Better Care Fund.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Better Care Fund: Reform", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848401", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848399, "askingMemberId": 5066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87948", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to his Department's plan Fit for the Future: 10 Year Health Plan for England, whether the plans to reform the Better Care Fund will impact on the level of funding intended to support", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Better Care Fund: Reform", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848399", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848391, "askingMemberId": 5062, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87947", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate her Department has made of the (a) total cost and (b) average cost per asylum seeker of adopting Crowborough Training Camp to house asylum seekers; and how much funding her Department pl", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Asylum: Crowborough Training Camp", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848391", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848394, "askingMemberId": 5058, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87946", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will make it her policy to exempt small businesses from paying VAT on birthday parties in line with the arrangements that currently exist for local leisure centres.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Small Businesses: VAT", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848394", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848508, "askingMemberId": 5055, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87945", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many times a court has cited (a) Article 3 and (b) Article 8 of the European Convention on Human Rights as a reason for the non-deportation of an asylum seeker in the last 12 months.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Asylum: Deportation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848508", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848396, "askingMemberId": 5055, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87944", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many different transactions or processes between members of the public and DVLA can only be completed if payment is made by a member of the public by (a) cash, (b) cheque and (c) postal order.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Driver and Vehicle Licensing Agency: Payments", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848396", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848440, "askingMemberId": 5051, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87943", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of introducing a certification system to help prevent the (a) selling and (b) purchasing of pets that have not been neutered.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Pets: Sales", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848440", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848320, "askingMemberId": 5047, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87942", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of increasing funding for the specialist (a) care, (b) advice and (c) assessment provided by hospices.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Hospices: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848320", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848319, "askingMemberId": 5047, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87941", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure that hospice contracts reflect the (a) cost of the services they provide and (b) needs of their local populations.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Hospices: Contracts", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848319", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848561, "askingMemberId": 5040, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87940", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when her Department expects all eligible retired members of the Teachers\u2019 Pension Scheme to receive their McCloud remedy payments; and what steps she is taking to expedite payments to retired teachers impacted ", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Teachers: Workplace Pensions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848561", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848550, "askingMemberId": 5040, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87939", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to reduce waiting times for complaints submitted to the Housing Ombudsman to be (a) processed and (b) resolved.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Housing Ombudsman Service: Standards", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848550", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848538, "askingMemberId": 5030, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87938", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the potential implications for his policies of allegations of foreign interference in recent elections in Romania and Germany through social media;", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Elections: Social Media", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848538", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848537, "askingMemberId": 5030, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87937", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether he plans to bring forward legislative proposals to protect election candidates from anonymous abuse on social media through the forthcoming Elections Bill.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Elections: Social Media", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848537", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848536, "askingMemberId": 5030, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87936", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether he plans to bring forward legislative proposals to help protect UK citizens from (a) foreign influence and (b) manipulation operations using fake accounts on social media", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Elections: Social Media", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848536", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848535, "askingMemberId": 5030, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87935", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of Ofcom's Online Safety Act Illegal Content Codes of Practice on levels of fraud against UK consumers.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Fraud: Internet", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848535", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848534, "askingMemberId": 5030, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87934", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of Ofcom's Online Safety Act Illegal Content Codes of Practice on levels of online violence against women and girls.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Gender Based Violence", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848534", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848533, "askingMemberId": 5030, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87933", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions her Department has had with Ofcom on ensuring that the steps it is taking to implement the Online Safety Act (2023) contribute to the delivery of its target to halve the level of viol", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Gender Based Violence", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848533", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848614, "askingMemberId": 5010, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87932", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether her Department has conducted a review of (a) the effectiveness of police enforcement of and (b) the level of compliance with the ban on live hunting under the Hunting Act 2004.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Hunting", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848614", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848604, "askingMemberId": 5010, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87931", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 1 September 2025 to Question 69695, what are the timescales for improving access to palliative care at home for children nearing the end of life; and what assessment he ha", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Palliative Care: Children", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848604", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848603, "askingMemberId": 5010, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87930", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to reduce the time taken to process Access to Work applications.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Access to Work Programme", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848603", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848602, "askingMemberId": 5010, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87929", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what steps her Department is taking to promote alternative testing methods that reduce the use of animals in scientific research.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Animal Experiments", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848602", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848600, "askingMemberId": 5010, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87928", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what regulatory framework his Department has in place to oversee AI systems capable of autonomously (a) developing and (b) modifying their own programming.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Artificial Intelligence: Regulation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848600", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848599, "askingMemberId": 5010, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87927", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to reduce waiting times for ear, nose, and throat (ENT) specialist appointments.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ear, Nose and Throat Conditions: Health Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848599", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848598, "askingMemberId": 5010, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87926", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of mandating the use of alternatives to snares for animal control practices.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Animal Welfare: Trapping", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848598", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848597, "askingMemberId": 5010, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87925", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what steps his Department plans to take to support the expansion of residential solar panel installations.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Solar Power: Housing", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848597", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848596, "askingMemberId": 5010, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87924", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to ensure parents of children with SEND are informed of (a) their rights and (b) the protections available to them.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Special Educational Needs", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848596", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848593, "askingMemberId": 5010, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87923", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment his Department has made of the value for money of the Future Strategic Tanker Aircraft contract since its commencement in 2008.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Voyager Aircraft", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848593", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848591, "askingMemberId": 5010, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87922", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the forthcoming Defence Investment Plan will specify future air-to-air refuelling requirements.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Military Aircraft: In-flight Refuelling", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848591", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848589, "askingMemberId": 5010, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87921", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment she has made of the potential impact of pavement parking on levelks of (a) wellbeing, (b) social isolation and (c) economic opportunities of disabled people.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Parking: Pedestrian Areas", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848589", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848588, "askingMemberId": 5010, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87920", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of walking, wheeling and cycling routes on disused railways to access to new housing sites.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Housing: Cycleways and Public Footpaths", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848588", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848587, "askingMemberId": 5010, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87919", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps she is taking to reduce the cost of creating new walking, wheeling and cycling routes on disused railways.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Railways: Active Travel", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848587", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848472, "askingMemberId": 4934, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87918", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will take steps to help improve access to public transport for disabled patients at Shrewsbury and Telford Hospital Trust.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Disability: Public Transport", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848472", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848469, "askingMemberId": 4934, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87917", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the availability of disabled parking at hospitals.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Hospitals: Parking", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848469", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848384, "askingMemberId": 4934, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87916", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to increase access to pharmacies in North Shropshire.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Pharmacy: North Shropshire", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848384", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848345, "askingMemberId": 4934, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87915", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what resources she has committed to tackling rural crime in Shropshire.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Crime: Rural Areas", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848345", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848337, "askingMemberId": 4934, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87914", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to increase levels of awareness of tongue ties, also called ankyloglossia, of (a) midwives and (b) expectant mothers.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Tongue-tie: Health Education", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848337", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848336, "askingMemberId": 4934, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87913", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the (a) speed and (b) quality of (i) detection and (ii) treatment of tongue ties, also called ankyloglossia, in babies.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Tongue-tie: Babies", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848336", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848335, "askingMemberId": 4934, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87912", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to help improve care for bottle-fed babies with tongue ties.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Tongue-tie: Babies", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848335", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848306, "askingMemberId": 4934, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87911", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether the funding settlement for Start for Life services will reflect (a) the widened age range from 0-2 to 0-5 and the (b) increases in the number of local authorities covered by the programme; ", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Family Hubs: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848306", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848268, "askingMemberId": 4934, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87910", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps she is taking to reflect the costs of (a) digital connectivity and (b) public transport in (i) rural and (ii) urban areas in funding formulas.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Public Expenditure: Digital Technology and Transport", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848268", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848333, "askingMemberId": 4932, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87909", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 3 November 2025 to Question 85053 on the Animals (Low-Welfare Activities Abroad) Act 2023, if she will set out a timeline including milestones for the introdu", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Animals (Low-Welfare Activities Abroad) Act 2023", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848333", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848182, "askingMemberId": 4932, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87908", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 3 November 2025 to Question 84975 on Dance and Music: Finance, what data her Department holds on the number of pupils that have left the independent school sector following the (a) applicat", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Private Education: VAT", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848182", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848181, "askingMemberId": 4932, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87907", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 3 November 2025 to Question 84975 on Dance and Music: Finance, if she will undertake an updated impact assessment on the (a) application of VAT to private school fees and (b) removal of bus", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Private Education: VAT", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848181", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848180, "askingMemberId": 4932, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87906", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 30 October 2025 to Question 83371 on Abiraterone: Finance, what steps he is taking to secure recurrent budget allocation for abiraterone for use in cases of high-risk non-", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Abiraterone: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848180", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848179, "askingMemberId": 4932, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87905", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether he has made an assessment of the potential merits of amending the process for allotment disposal by local authorities.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Allotments: Sales", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848179", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848144, "askingMemberId": 4932, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87904", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of levels of (a) taxation and (b) regulatory costs on growth in the retail sector.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Retail Trade: Costs", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848144", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848143, "askingMemberId": 4932, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87903", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what comparative assessment she has made of the potential impact of the proposed higher business rates multiplier for properties with a rateable value above \u00a3500,000 on (a) physical retailers and (b) online business", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Business Rates: Valuation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848143", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848141, "askingMemberId": 4932, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87902", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will publish data on the number of (a) criminal penalties issued, (b) prosecutions undertaken and (c) successful convictions secured for illegal working since 4 July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Undocumented Workers: Convictions and Prosecutions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848141", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848140, "askingMemberId": 4932, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87901", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will make it her policy to increase the property value threshold for using a Lifetime ISA in line with either inflation or the annual increase in house prices.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Individual Savings Accounts", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848140", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848139, "askingMemberId": 4932, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87900", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps she is taking to support grassroots music venues which will have higher business rates under the new multiplier.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Music Venues: Business Rates", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848139", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848137, "askingMemberId": 4932, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87899", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions she has had with gig economy operators on (a) trends in the level of people (i) driving and (ii) delivering through their platforms without appropriate driving licences and (b) steps they are t", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Delivery Services: Driving Licences", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848137", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848136, "askingMemberId": 4932, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87898", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether she has made an assessment of the potential merits of increasing (a) the regulation of and (b) enforcement against people driving vehicles for (i) delivery and (ii) courier work with L plates but withou", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Delivery Services: Driving Licences", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848136", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848135, "askingMemberId": 4932, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87897", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of people without valid (a) work and (b) driving documentation being engaged in delivery work on road safety.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Roads: Delivery Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848135", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848134, "askingMemberId": 4932, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87896", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what discussions he has had with gig economy operators on ensuring consumer safety from people working illegally.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Sharing Economy: Undocumented Workers", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848134", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848133, "askingMemberId": 4932, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87895", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many enforcement actions have been taken against gig economy companies found to have engaged workers without the legal right to work in the United Kingdom since 4 July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Undocumented Workers: Sharing Economy", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848133", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848132, "askingMemberId": 4932, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87894", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent estimate she has made of the prevalence of illegal working among people using app-based delivery platforms.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Undocumented Workers: Delivery Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848132", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848131, "askingMemberId": 4932, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87893", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate her Department has made of the number of grassroots music venues that will be affected by the new higher multiplier rate of retail, hospitality and leisure relief; and what assessment her Department ha", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Music Venues: Business Rates", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848131", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848381, "askingMemberId": 4872, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "87892", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether Wealden District Council has raised legal objections to the use of Crowborough Training Camp to house asylum seekers.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848381", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848560, "askingMemberId": 4869, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87891", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will require local authorities to consider the needs of young people as a specific group in their local housing needs assessments.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Housing: Young People", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848560", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848558, "askingMemberId": 4869, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87890", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to implement early identification models in schools to (a) identify and (b) help those at risk of homelessness.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Homelessness", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848558", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848491, "askingMemberId": 4860, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87889", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the additional number of offenders will be entitled to release from prison on each day of the 28 days and then each month of the subsequent 11 months following the day of enactment of", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prisoners' Release", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848491", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848367, "askingMemberId": 4860, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87888", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether (a) Wealden District Council and (b) Wealden District Council's (i) leadership and (ii) councillors have made legal challenges to (i) prevent or (ii) delay the use of Crowborough Training Camp", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Asylum: Crowborough Training Camp", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848367", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848254, "askingMemberId": 4853, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87887", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether her Department has made an assessment of the effectiveness of the (a) Property Flood Resilience Scheme and (b) Flood Re in supporting people affected by flooding.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Floods: Housing", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848254", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848253, "askingMemberId": 4853, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87886", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to increase public awareness of the statutory duties of public bodies with relation to flooding.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Flood Control", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848253", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848252, "askingMemberId": 4853, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87885", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to increase public awareness of the steps people whose homes are at risk of flooding should take to help mitigate that risk.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Flood Control: Housing", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848252", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848251, "askingMemberId": 4853, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87884", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether her Department has made an assessment of the potential merits of creating a statutory duty for fire and rescue services to respond to flooding.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Floods: Fire and Rescue Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848251", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848250, "askingMemberId": 4853, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87883", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether her Department has made an assessment of the potential merits of commissioning a national audit of flood resilience assets.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Flood Control", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848250", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848273, "askingMemberId": 4850, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87882", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether was she informed by the Office for Budget Responsibility in advance of the (a) Autumn Budget 2024 and (b) Spring Statement 2025 that it was likely to conduct a review of productivity forecasts at a forthcomi", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Office for Budget Responsibility: Forecasts", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848273", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848269, "askingMemberId": 4850, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87881", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, when she was first informed by officials in her Department that the Office for Budget Responsibility was likely to conduct a review of their productivity forecasts.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Office for Budget Responsibility: Forecasts", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848269", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848267, "askingMemberId": 4850, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87880", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, when was she first informed by the Office for Budget Responsibility that they planned to review the Government's productivity forecasts.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Office for Budget Responsibility: Forecasts", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848267", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848370, "askingMemberId": 4827, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87879", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will take steps to support (a) hospitality, (b) consumers, (c) pubs and (d) breweries by (i) reducing (A) VAT and (B) draught beer and cider duty and (ii) introducing targeted relief for (1) energy and (2) em", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Hospitality Industry: VAT", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848370", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848290, "askingMemberId": 4827, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87878", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether the Timms Review plans to (a) hold discussions with (i) carers and (ii) disabled people from and (b) considers the potential impact of proposed changes in Northern Ireland.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Personal Independence Payment Assessment Review: Northern Ireland", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848290", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848405, "askingMemberId": 4824, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87877", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many visas have been issued to Gazan children seeking medical evacuation to the UK since 5 July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Refugees: Gaza", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848405", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848249, "askingMemberId": 4818, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87876", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of excluding (a) general practitioners and (b) other frontline medical staff from the covid-19 booster vaccination programme in autumn 2025 on (i", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Coronavirus: Vaccination", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848249", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848392, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87875", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether she plans to retain the rail freight growth target of 75% growth in freight carried by rail by 2050; and whether she plans to (a) put that target on a statutory footing, (b) introduce interim milestones", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Railways: Freight", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848392", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848164, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87874", "questionText": "To ask the Solicitor General, how much (a) their Department and (b) its arm\u2019s length bodies have spent on (i) installing electric vehicle charging facilities and (ii) purchasing electric vehicles since 4 July 2024; and what estimate their Department has m", "answeringBodyId": 88, "answeringBodyName": "Attorney General", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Attorney General: Electric Vehicles", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848164", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848163, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87873", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how much (a) their Department and (b) its arm\u2019s length bodies have spent on (i) installing electric vehicle charging facilities and (ii) purchasing electric vehicles since 4 July 2024; and what estimate ", "answeringBodyId": 21, "answeringBodyName": "Northern Ireland Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Northern Ireland Office: Electric Vehicles", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848163", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848162, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87872", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how much (a) their Department and (b) its arm\u2019s length bodies have spent on (i) installing electric vehicle charging facilities and (ii) purchasing electric vehicles since 4 July 2024; and what estimate their Depar", "answeringBodyId": 28, "answeringBodyName": "Wales Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Wales Office: Electric Vehicles", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848162", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848161, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87871", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how much (a) their Department and (b) its arm\u2019s length bodies have spent on (i) installing electric vehicle charging facilities and (ii) purchasing electric vehicles since 4 July 2024; and what estimate their De", "answeringBodyId": 2, "answeringBodyName": "Scotland Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Scotland Office: Electric Vehicles", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848161", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848160, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87870", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, how much (a) their Department and (b) its arm\u2019s length bodies have spent on (i) installing electric vehicle charging facilities and (ii) purchasing electric vehicles since 4 July 2024; ", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology: Electric Vehicles", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848160", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848159, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87869", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how much (a) their Department and (b) its arm\u2019s length bodies have spent on (i) installing electric vehicle charging facilities and (ii) purchasing electric vehicles since 4 July 2024; and what e", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport: Electric Vehicles", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848159", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848158, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87868", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, how much (a) their Department and (b) its arm\u2019s length bodies have spent on (i) installing electric vehicle charging facilities and (ii) purchasing electric vehicles since 4 July 2024; and what estimat", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Department for Business and Trade: Electric Vehicles", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848158", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848157, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87867", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, how much (a) their Department and (b) its arm\u2019s length bodies have spent on (i) installing electric vehicle charging facilities and (ii) purchasing electric vehicles since 4 July 2024; and wh", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero: Electric Vehicles", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848157", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848156, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87866", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much (a) their Department and (b) its arm\u2019s length bodies have spent on (i) installing electric vehicle charging facilities and (ii) purchasing electric vehicles since 4 July 2024;", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs: Electric Vehicles", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848156", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848155, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87865", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how much (a) their Department and (b) its arm\u2019s length bodies have spent on (i) installing electric vehicle charging facilities and (ii) purchasing electric vehicles since 4 July", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government: Electric Vehicles", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848155", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848154, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87864", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much (a) their Department and (b) its arm\u2019s length bodies have spent on (i) installing electric vehicle charging facilities and (ii) purchasing electric vehicles since 4 July 2024; and what estimate their D", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Department for Transport: Electric Vehicles", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848154", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848153, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87863", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much (a) their Department and (b) its arm\u2019s length bodies have spent on (i) installing electric vehicle charging facilities and (ii) purchasing electric vehicles since 4 July 2024; and what estimate their D", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Department for Education: Electric Vehicles", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848153", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848152, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87862", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much (a) their Department and (b) its arm\u2019s length bodies have spent on (i) installing electric vehicle charging facilities and (ii) purchasing electric vehicles since 4 July 2024; and what est", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Department of Health and Social Care: Electric Vehicles", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848152", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848151, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87861", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much (a) their Department and (b) its arm\u2019s length bodies have spent on (i) installing electric vehicle charging facilities and (ii) purchasing electric vehicles since 4 July 2024; and what estimate their Dep", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ministry of Justice: Electric Vehicles", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848151", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848150, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87860", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much (a) their Department and (b) its arm\u2019s length bodies have spent on (i) installing electric vehicle charging facilities and (ii) purchasing electric vehicles since 4 July 2024; and what estima", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Home Office: Electric Vehicles", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848150", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848147, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87859", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate his Department has made of the annual cost to the public purse for NHS of treating (a) congenital and (b) genetic disorders arising from consanguineous unions.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Hereditary Diseases", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848147", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848146, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87858", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to (a) improve data collection and (b) integrate indicators related to (i) parental consanguinity and (ii) genetic risk into future (A) public health strategy and (B) NHS re", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Hereditary Diseases", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848146", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848145, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87857", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether the Government has (a) commissioned and (b) plans to commission studies using (i) genomic datasets, (ii) UK Biobank and (iii) Genomics England to estimate levels of (A) inbreeding and (B) r", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Genetics: Research", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848145", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848142, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87856", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 27 October 2025 to Question 84309 on High Speed 2, what her Department\u2019s latest estimate is of (a) the additional cost arising from the four-year deferral of works between Delta Juncti", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "High Speed 2 Line: Staffordshire", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848142", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848309, "askingMemberId": 4811, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87855", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what discussions her Department has had with Ofcom on mid-contract price increases by O2, in the context of levels of rises set out in customers\u2019 contracts.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "O2: Contracts", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848309", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848307, "askingMemberId": 4811, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87854", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to support (a) housing providers, (b) housing associations and (c) arms-length management organisations with meeting the costs of regulatory s", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Supported Housing: Standards", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848307", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848297, "askingMemberId": 4811, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87853", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if his Department will take steps to help increase the number of 16-30 year olds who are registered to donate stem cells.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Stem Cells: Donors", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848297", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848295, "askingMemberId": 4811, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87852", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what recent assessment his Department has made of trends in levels of (a) Hinduphobia and (b) anti-Hindu sentiment.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Religious Hatred: Hinduism", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848295", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848293, "askingMemberId": 4811, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87851", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to support Jamaica following Hurricane Melissa.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Jamaica: Hurricanes and Tornadoes", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848293", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848291, "askingMemberId": 4811, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87850", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to support Cuba following Hurricane Melissa.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cuba: Hurricanes and Tornadoes", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848291", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848559, "askingMemberId": 4805, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "87849", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, when he will announce Government plans for community benefit funds for solar developments following the Community Benefits and Shared Ownership for Low Carbon Infrastructure consultation whic", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848559", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848281, "askingMemberId": 4805, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "87848", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether existing (a) district and (b) borough council area borders can be changed as part of local government reorganisation.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848281", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848360, "askingMemberId": 4803, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87847", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will publish any detailed assessments carried out (a) by and (b) on behalf of her Department on the use of Crowborough Training Camp to house asylum seekers; and whether Wealden District Counci", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Asylum: Crowborough Training Camp", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848360", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848612, "askingMemberId": 4799, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87846", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make an assessment of the potential impact of the reclassification of ketamine as a class B drug on (a) the rate of its usage among (i) 16 to 59-year-olds and (ii) 16 to 24-year-olds, (b) ", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ketamine", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848612", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848327, "askingMemberId": 4799, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87845", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, whether his Department has made an economic assessment of the potential impact of the Nuclear Decommissioning Authority estate's current voluntary exit scheme on the regional economy in (a) W", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Nuclear Decommissioning Authority", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848327", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848326, "askingMemberId": 4799, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87844", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, whether his Department has assessed the potential impact of the Nuclear Decommissioning Authority estate's current voluntary exit scheme on the achievement of that organisation's mission.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Nuclear Decommissioning Authority", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848326", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848325, "askingMemberId": 4799, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87843", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what is the estimated cost to the public purse of the current voluntary exit scheme at the Nuclear Decommissioning Authority's estate.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Nuclear Decommissioning Authority: Redundancy Pay", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848325", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848623, "askingMemberId": 4778, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87842", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of real-terms reductions in core funding on the delivery of statutory services by Buckinghamshire Council.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Local Government Finance: Buckinghamshire", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848623", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848358, "askingMemberId": 4777, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87841", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to ensure fire safety for new (a) high rise buildings, (b) complex or mixed use developments and (c) sites with known access or water-supply c", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Housing: Fire Prevention", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848358", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848528, "askingMemberId": 4769, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87840", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether funding is available for schools to purchase (a) defibrillators and (b) CPR training equipment.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Schools: CPR and Defibrillators", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848528", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848527, "askingMemberId": 4769, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87839", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she plans to issue guidance to schools on how to access training resources to help deliver the CPR Smart programme.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Schools: CPR", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848527", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848526, "askingMemberId": 4769, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87838", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he has made an assessment as part of the New Hospital Programme of the adequacy of the number of helipads available for air ambulance use.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Hospitals: Air Ambulance Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848526", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848379, "askingMemberId": 4742, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87837", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps she is taking to support the visitor economy in South Shropshire constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Tourism: South Shropshire", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848379", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848378, "askingMemberId": 4742, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87836", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what discussions he has had with the Royal Mail on tackling postal delays in rural communities.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Royal Mail: Rural Areas", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848378", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848377, "askingMemberId": 4742, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87835", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to ensure the provision of childcare in all rural areas.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Childcare: Rural Areas", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848377", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848376, "askingMemberId": 4742, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87834", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what guidance his Department has issued to closed mortuaries on family visiting arrangements.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Mortuaries: Visits", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848376", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848430, "askingMemberId": 4739, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87833", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether Wealden District Council have raised legal objections to the use of Crowborough Training Camp to house asylum seekers.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Asylum: Crowborough Training Camp", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848430", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848624, "askingMemberId": 4736, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-13T00:00:00", "uin": "87832", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 29 October 2025 to Question 84339 on RAF Brize Norton: Palestine Action, what delivery forecast is for the return of each engine to serviceability.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848624", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848490, "askingMemberId": 4679, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87831", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many employment tribunal claims have been lodged against his Department for (a) unfair dismissal and (b) claims under the Equality Act 2010 in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cabinet Office: Employment Tribunals Service", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848490", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848489, "askingMemberId": 4679, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87830", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many staff in his Department are recorded as having a (a) mental health condition and (b) physical disability by grade.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cabinet Office: Disability", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848489", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848488, "askingMemberId": 4679, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87829", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many staff left his Department by grade in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cabinet Office: Termination of Employment", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848488", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848487, "askingMemberId": 4679, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87828", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many staff in his Department (a) did not retain employment following the completion of their probationary period and (b) had their probationary period extended in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cabinet Office: Conditions of Employment", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848487", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848486, "askingMemberId": 4679, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87827", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many performance reviews were undertaken for staff in (a) his Department and (b) its agencies in each of the last five years; in how many such cases performance was rated as unsatisfactory or below; how many", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cabinet Office: Performance Appraisal", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848486", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848393, "askingMemberId": 4673, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87826", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate she has made of the number of retail businesses that will be affected by the (a) business rates reduction for Retail, Hospitality and Leisure properties and (b) higher business rates multiplier in Leig", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Business Rates: Leigh and Atherton", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848393", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848362, "askingMemberId": 4673, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87825", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether he plans to introduce a National Development Management Policy for older people\u2019s housing.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Housing: Older People", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848362", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848324, "askingMemberId": 4673, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87824", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps her Department is taking to support the continued inclusion of UK (a) film and (b) television content within the definition of European works in the forthcoming revision of the EU\u2019s Au", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Film and Television: EU Law", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848324", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848388, "askingMemberId": 4651, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87823", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether he plans to (a) review and (b) amend carer's allowance.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Carer's Allowance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848388", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848517, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87822", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment his Department has made of the availability of treatment for those with Friedreich\u2019s Ataxia.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Friedreich's Ataxia: Medical Treatments", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848517", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848493, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87821", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made of the availability of lactose free Olanzapine in (a) Slough and (b) Berkshire.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Olanzapine: Berkshire", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848493", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848620, "askingMemberId": 4630, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87820", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether future compensation funding provided to the Welsh Government for increased National Insurance contributions costs for the public sector in Wales will cover this cost in full.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Employers' Contributions: Wales", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848620", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848271, "askingMemberId": 4630, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87819", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of increasing the level of the Digital Services Tax.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Digital Technology: Taxation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848271", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848246, "askingMemberId": 4571, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87818", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of delayed access to specialist heart valve treatment on (a) avoidable unscheduled hospitalisations, (b) deaths on the waiting lists, and (c) oth", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Heart Diseases: Medical Treatments", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848246", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848242, "askingMemberId": 4571, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "87817", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure earlier (a) detection and (b) treatment of heart valve disease is prioritised within NHS long-term planning.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848242", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848241, "askingMemberId": 4569, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87816", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of the mandatory displaying of food hygiene ratings on (a) shop fronts and (b) online food ordering platforms.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Food: Hygiene", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848241", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848232, "askingMemberId": 4569, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87815", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the potential impact of HMRC mileage rates on health and care workers undertaking home visits.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Home Visits: Mileage Allowances", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848232", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848231, "askingMemberId": 4569, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87814", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment she has made of the adequacy of HMRC mileage rates.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Mileage Allowances", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848231", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848226, "askingMemberId": 4569, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87813", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what was the cost of asylum properties procured for dispersed accommodation in (a) England, (b) Greater Manchester and (c) Oldham for each financial year from 2015/16 to date.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Asylum: Housing", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848226", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848223, "askingMemberId": 4569, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87812", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the impact of criminal records amassed in the course of exploitation and abuse on victims of child (a) sexual exploitation and (b) criminal exploitation.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Exploitation: Children", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848223", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848222, "askingMemberId": 4569, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-13T00:00:00", "uin": "87811", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the effectiveness of child criminal exploitation interventions in England.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848222", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848317, "askingMemberId": 4511, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87810", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to make treatment available to people with Irritable bowel syndrome.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Irritable Bowel Syndrome: Medical Treatments", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848317", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848283, "askingMemberId": 4511, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87809", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of providing the covid-19 vaccination to pensioners under 75; and how he made that estimate.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Coronavirus: Vaccination", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848283", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848371, "askingMemberId": 4510, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87808", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, when he expects to publish the results of the Heat Network Efficiency Scheme Round 10.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Heat Network Efficiency Scheme", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848371", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848369, "askingMemberId": 4510, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87807", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the level of grant available under the Heat Network Efficiency Scheme to cover the estimated costs of remediation to bring older networks in lin", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Heat Network Efficiency Scheme: Lambeth and Southwark", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848369", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848442, "askingMemberId": 4500, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87806", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 4 November 2025 to Question 85834 on Water Companies: Criminal Proceedings, if she will confirm the number of live proceedings which are subject to reporting ", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Water Companies: Criminal Proceedings", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848442", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848421, "askingMemberId": 4491, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87805", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment her Department has made of the impact of (a) VAT and (b) Insurance Premium Tax exemptions on the affordability of Motability Scheme advance payments.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Motability: Insurance Premium Tax and VAT", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848421", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848416, "askingMemberId": 4491, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87804", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his Department holds data on (a) the number and (b) the proportion of Access to Work awards terminated within (i) six months and (ii) a year of reassessment for each of the financial years from ", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Access to Work Programme", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848416", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848415, "askingMemberId": 4491, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87803", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his Department holds data on the (a) number and (b) proportion of Access to Work applications terminated in each financial year from 2022-2023 to 2025-26 to date by (i) stage of the claim and (i", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Access to Work Programme", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848415", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848398, "askingMemberId": 4491, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87802", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department has made of the (a) number and (b) percentage of Access to Work applicants who have lost their employment after a reassessment resulted in a reduction in the support they ", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Access to Work Programme", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848398", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848397, "askingMemberId": 4491, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87801", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what data his Department holds on the number of Access to Work reassessments conducted in (a) 2022-2023, (b) 2024-2025 and (c) the financial year 2025-26 to date which resulted in (i) a reduction in fun", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Access to Work Programme", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848397", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848460, "askingMemberId": 4475, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87800", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to help reduce the potential impact of PIP reassessments for chronic conditions on the mental health of families affected.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Personal Independence Payment: Chronic Illnesses", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848460", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848459, "askingMemberId": 4475, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87799", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his Department has considered exemptions or streamlined processes for PIP claimants with (a) Type 1 diabetes and (b) other lifelong and progressively complex conditions.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Personal Independence Payment: Chronic Illnesses and Diabetes", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848459", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848458, "askingMemberId": 4475, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87798", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department has made of the potential impact of PIP\u00a0reassessments on (a) teenagers with Type 1 diabetes and (b) their carers.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Personal Independence Payment: Diabetes", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848458", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848457, "askingMemberId": 4475, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87797", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his Department plans to reform the Personal Independence Payment reassessment process for people with (a) Type 1 diabetes and (b) other lifelong conditions.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Personal Independence Payment: Chronic Illnesses and Diabetes", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848457", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848456, "askingMemberId": 4475, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87796", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department has considered implementing routine screening for Type 1 diabetes in children.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Diabetes: Children", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848456", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848455, "askingMemberId": 4475, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87795", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans his Department has to improve public awareness of the early signs of Type 1 diabetes.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Diabetes: Health Education", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848455", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848454, "askingMemberId": 4475, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87794", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what guidance his Department issues to GPs on immediate blood glucose testing when symptoms of Type 1 diabetes are reported.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Diabetes: Blood Tests", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848454", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848453, "askingMemberId": 4475, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87793", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department\u00a0is taking to ensure that general practitioners receive training on recognising symptoms of Type 1 diabetes in children and young people.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Diabetes: Children and Young People", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848453", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848382, "askingMemberId": 4371, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87792", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assessment she has made of the potential implications of her policies of the recent detention of 70 Vietnamese refugees in Thailand.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Thailand: Refugees", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848382", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848148, "askingMemberId": 4371, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87791", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assessment she has made of the potential implications for her policies of reports of (a) torture and (b) other human rights violations by T\u00f4 L\u00e2m .", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "T\u00f4 L\u00e2m", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848148", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848280, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87790", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 29 August 2025 to Question 68418 on Business Rates: Valuation, how many hereditaments in the flexible workplace and serviced office sector have had their rateable values increased following", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Business Rates: Valuation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848280", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848279, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87789", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the answer of 15 October 2025 to Question 78960 on Hospitals and Schools: Solar Power, how many (a) schools and (b) hospitals have had their Rateable Values amended by the Valuation Office Agency due to ", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Hospitals and Schools: Solar Power", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848279", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848278, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87788", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 26 February 2025 to Question 32153 on Airports: Business Rates, whether the Valuation Office Agency has made other changes to the methodology of airport valuations since the last revaluatio", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Airports: Business Rates", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848278", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848276, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87787", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people have received a Lifetime ISA 25% withdrawal charge in the last 12 months for which figures are available.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Individual Savings Accounts: Fees and Charges", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848276", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848275, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87786", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the policy paper entitled Transforming Business Rates: Interim Report, updated 17 September 2025, whether the proposed reforms on moving from a slab to slice system will be implemented for the intr", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Business Rates: Valuation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848275", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848266, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87785", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the answer of 28 October 2025, to Question 81310, on Universal Studios: Bedfordshire, if he will make it his policy to publish all online written representations to p", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Planning Permission: Applications", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848266", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848263, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87784", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the HMRC guidance, Local authorities and similar bodies (VAT Notice 749), whether local authorities will be able to recover VAT on private hire for school transport.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Schools: Transport", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848263", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848248, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87783", "questionText": "To ask the Solicitor General, pursuant to the Answer of 21 October 2025 to Question 81790 on Democracy, what her Department's budget is for direct engagement with (a) civil society groups and (b) young people; and which organisations her Department has me", "answeringBodyId": 88, "answeringBodyName": "Attorney General", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Attorney General: Civil Society and Young People", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848248", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848245, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87782", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the written statement of 28 October 2025, HCWS998, on Local government reorganisation, and with reference to the debt write-off of Woking Borough Council, wheth", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Local Government: Reorganisation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848245", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848244, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87781", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 20 October 2025 to Question 78178 on City of London Corporation, for what reason the City of London will continue to operate under a committee-based sys", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "City of London Corporation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848244", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848243, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87780", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether (a) his Department and (b) the Valuation Tribunal Service has issued (i) guidance and (ii) advice to local billing authorities on the changing of designations of secondar", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Second Homes: Council Tax", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848243", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848240, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87779", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 20 October 2025 to Question 78227 on Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government: Standards, if he will provide the data for each of those met", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government: Standards", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848240", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848239, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87778", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 24 October 2025 to Question 81951 on Affordable Housing: Construction, whether grant funding will be provided under the Affordable Housing Programme for", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Affordable Housing: Construction", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848239", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848238, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87777", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 28 October 2025 to Question 83343 on Elections: Pilot Schemes, what his planned timetable is for announcing which local authority areas will be selected", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Local Government: Elections", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848238", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848237, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87776", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 28 October 2025 to Question 83285 on Private Rented Housing: Energy, whether he plans to provide guidance to (a) renters, (b) landlords and (c) tribunal", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Private Rented Housing: Energy", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848237", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848236, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87775", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Written Statement of 28 October 2025 entitled Local Government Reorganisation, HCWS998, what discussions his Department has had with councils in Surrey on e", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Local Government: Reorganisation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848236", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848235, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87774", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Written Statement of 28 October 2025 entitled Local Government Reorganisation, HCWS998, what estimate his Department has made of the upfront costs to (a) lo", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Local Government: Reorganisation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848235", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848234, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87773", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether he plans to allow local referendums on (a) local government restructuring, (b) changes to the governance model of local councils and (c) the establishment of combined aut", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Local Government: Reorganisation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848234", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848584, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87772", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assessment her Department has made of the effectiveness of the UK's role in supporting private sector investment in global health initiatives.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Development Aid: Investment", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848584", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848582, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87771", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what steps she is taking to increase levels of (a) transparency and (b) accountability in the reporting to Parliament of British International Investment\u2019s performance.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "British International Investment", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848582", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848581, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87770", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, how her Department measures the (a) economic and (b) social return on investment from British International Investment projects in partner countries.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "British International Investment", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848581", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848580, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87769", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that private investment in development funding is effectively leveraged.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Development Aid: Investment", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848580", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848579, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87768", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what plans her Department has to publish (a) performance data and (b) impact evaluations of programmes funded through Official Development Assistance.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Development Aid: Disclosure of Information", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848579", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848578, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87767", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what mechanisms her Department uses to assess the effectiveness of Official Development Assistance programmes.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Development Aid", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848578", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848576, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87766", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 24 July 2025 to Question 67377, what plans he has for the Ministerial Women Peace and Security National Action Plan (WPS NAP) steering board to meet", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Conflict Resolution: Women", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848576", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848575, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87765", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 24 July 2025 to Question 67377, which (a) Departments and (b) civil servants are represented at the (i) the Cross-Whitehall Working Group and (ii) t", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Conflict Resolution: Women", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848575", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848574, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87764", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that the UK\u2019s commitments at the 2025 Nutrition for Growth Summit are implemented through integration with (a) education, (b) im", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Humanitarian Aid: Nutrition", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848574", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848573, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87763", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what recent discussions she has had with her Nigerian counterparts on ongoing reports of (a) abduction and (b) forced marriage of Christian women and girls; and what steps sh", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Nigeria: Religious Freedom", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848573", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848304, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87762", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 29 October 2025 to Question 83833 on Schools: Employers' Contributions, what estimate she has made of the proportion of the \u00a33.7 billion increase in school funding for 2025-26 that wil", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Schools: Employers' Contributions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848304", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848303, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87761", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of the rail nationalisation programme on passenger rail prices.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Railways: Fares", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848303", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848302, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87760", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of nationalising South Western Railway on passenger rail prices since 25 May 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "South Western Railway: Nationalisation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848302", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848301, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87759", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate she has made of the total value of (a) debts, (b) leases and (c) other liabilities per railway operator the Government will be taking on following completion of the railway nationalisation program", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Railways: Nationalisation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848301", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848300, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87758", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the (a) role and (b) functions of the Passenger Standards Authority will be.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Passenger Standards Authority", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848300", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848299, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87757", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what her planned timeframe is for establishing the Passenger Standards Authority.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Passenger Standards Authority", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848299", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848298, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87756", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate she has made of the annual cost to the public purse of leasing train carriages per railway operator once the nationalisation programme is complete.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Rolling Stock", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848298", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848296, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87755", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment has he made of the potential impact of requiring local authorities to make separate food waste collections by 31 March 2026 on (a) council budgets and (b) the pro", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Food: Waste Disposal", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848296", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848294, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87754", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether she has considered reforming the Habitat Regulations in as far as they relate to planning.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Planning Permission: Reform", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848294", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848292, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87753", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether he plans to bring forward further legislative proposals on planning reform.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Planning Permission: Reform", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848292", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848171, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87752", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Written Statement of 23 October 2025 on Housing Delivery, HCWS991, whether he has made an assessment of the potential impact of the new time-limited plannin", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Housing: Planning Permission", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848171", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848611, "askingMemberId": 4357, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87751", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the impact of fully implementing the provisions of the Building Societies Act 1986 (Amendment) Act 2024 via secondary legislation on (a) new lending capacity and (b) economic growth.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Building Societies: Investment", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848611", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848610, "askingMemberId": 4357, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87750", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, when her Department plans to bring forward the secondary legislation required under the Building Societies Act 1986 (Amendment) Act 2024 to enact provisions around further alignment with Companies Law on execution o", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Building Societies: Company Law", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848610", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848609, "askingMemberId": 4357, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87749", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, when her Department plans to bring forward the secondary legislation required under the Building Societies Act 1986 (Amendment) Act 2024 to enact provisions around the disapplication of the wholesale funding limit f", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Building Societies: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848609", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848595, "askingMemberId": 4320, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87748", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the press release entitled Major safety boost for frontline prison staff, published on 21 September 2025, how many stab vests have been issued to frontline prison staff since that announcement.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prison Officers: Protective Clothing", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848595", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848572, "askingMemberId": 4320, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87747", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will publish an update on plans to trial chemical castration for sexual offenders.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Sexual Offences: Medical Treatments", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848572", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848571, "askingMemberId": 4320, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87746", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what visits he has conducted to (a) HMP Pentonville and (b) HMP Manchester since he became Justice Secretary and Lord Chancellor.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "HMP Manchester and HMP Pentonville: Domestic Visits", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848571", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848570, "askingMemberId": 4320, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87745", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether his Department has made an assessment of the potential merits of subjecting prison officers to security checks upon entering prisons.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prison Officers", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848570", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848569, "askingMemberId": 4320, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87744", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether his Department has made an estimate of the number of instances of prisoners bring transferred from prison to court late in the last 12 months.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prisoner Escorts", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848569", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848193, "askingMemberId": 4267, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87743", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what discussion she has had with her counterparts at the UN on the resettlement of Rohingya refugees.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Rohingya: Refugees", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848193", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848357, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87742", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what discussions she has had with Bangladeshi counterpart on the (a) proposed Islamist rally in Dhaka on 15 November and (b) protection of the Ahmadiyya community in that cou", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Bangladesh: Ahmadiyya", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848357", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848277, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87741", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to support families with food poverty in winter 2025-26.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Families: Food Poverty", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848277", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848274, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87740", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to increase funding for breast cancer research.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Breast Cancer: Research", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848274", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848272, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87739", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to help tackle underage drug use.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Drugs: Misuse", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848272", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848265, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87738", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps she is taking to support grassroots sports.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Sports: Government Assistance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848265", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848264, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87737", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions she has had with her counterparts in Northern Ireland on electric vehicle charging provision.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Electric Vehicles: Northern Ireland", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848264", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848262, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87736", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps she is taking to promote more positive mental wellbeing in the workplace.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Employment: Mental Health", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848262", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848258, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87735", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what information her Department holds on the number of people who have been arrested for knife crime-related incidents in the last 12 months.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Knives: Crime", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848258", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848257, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87734", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to encourage healthier eating in schools.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Schools: Food", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848257", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848256, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87733", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to uphold free speech in universities.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Universities: Freedom of Expression", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848256", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848255, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87732", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps she is taking to increase the number of early interventions for prostate cancer.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prostate Cancer: Health Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848255", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848204, "askingMemberId": 4124, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87731", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, how many British nationals are serving in the Israeli Defence Forces.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Israel: Armed Forces", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848204", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848203, "askingMemberId": 4124, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87730", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assessment has she made of the implications for her policies of the UN Human Rights Office of the High Commissioner press release entitled \u201cMore than a human can bear\u201d: ", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Israel: Gender Based Violence", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848203", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848202, "askingMemberId": 4124, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87729", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, pursuant to the Answer of 3 November 2025 to Question 85759 on Imports: Israel, how his Department determines whether there are doubts about the declared origin of goods.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Imports: Israel", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848202", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848432, "askingMemberId": 4107, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87728", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, whether the Independent Commission for Reconciliation and Information Recovery will have the power to compel witnesses.", "answeringBodyId": 21, "answeringBodyName": "Northern Ireland Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Independent Commission for Reconciliation and Information Recovery", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848432", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848365, "askingMemberId": 4107, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87727", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment her Department has made of the potential impact of the increase to the Energy Profits Levy announced in the Autumn Statement 2024 on (a) investment, (b) employment and (c) operations in the oil and g", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Energy: Taxation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848365", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848363, "askingMemberId": 4107, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87726", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, how many people impacted by the Horizon IT system failure received settlements lower than their original claims.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Horizon IT System: Compensation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848363", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848361, "askingMemberId": 4107, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87725", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, how much the Government paid in its settlement to Sir Alan Bates.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Sir Alan Bates", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848361", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848356, "askingMemberId": 4107, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87724", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the uplifted Network Charging Compensation Scheme on the UK\u2019s industrial electricity price competitiveness relative to other G7 economies.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Energy Intensive Industries: Government Assistance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848356", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848608, "askingMemberId": 4084, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87723", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to help ensure that rape support charities receive adequate funding.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Rape: Victim Support Schemes", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848608", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848606, "askingMemberId": 4084, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87722", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what plans he has to review the funding model for rape crisis centres.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Rape Crisis Centres: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848606", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848605, "askingMemberId": 4084, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87721", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of funding for rape crisis centres.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Rape Crisis Centres: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848605", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848466, "askingMemberId": 4084, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87720", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will take steps to ensure that HMRC does not impose (a) penalties and (b) interest on (i) people and (ii) businesses who make inadvertent errors on their tax returns.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Self-Assessment: Fines", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848466", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848483, "askingMemberId": 4051, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87719", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the answer of 4th November 2025 to question 84180 on Alpacas: Bluetongue Disease, what restrictions there are on the export of alpacas to (a) Ireland and (b) mainland Europ", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Alpacas: Bluetongue Disease", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848483", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848554, "askingMemberId": 4005, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87718", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government,  if he will meet with the Fire Brigades Union to discuss the safety of firefighters when tackling wildfires.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Fire and Rescue Services: Safety", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848554", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848627, "askingMemberId": 3969, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87717", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to the Government's ambition that every primary school should have a library, what funding will be available (a) for the staffing of the additional libraries, (b) for the provision", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Primary Education: School Libraries", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848627", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848626, "askingMemberId": 3969, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87716", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to the Government's ambition that every primary school should have a library, how much funding will be available for (a) the building of libraries and (b) the conversion of existin", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Primary Education: School Libraries", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848626", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848625, "askingMemberId": 3969, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87715", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if she will publish interim indicators of progress towards the Government's ambition to add 1,700 primary school libraries.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Primary Education: School Libraries", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848625", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848233, "askingMemberId": 3969, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87714", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the press release entitled UK and Albania agree groundbreaking new arrangement on prisoner transfers, published on 24 May 2023, how many prisoners have been transferred under the agreement with ", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prisoners: Repatriation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848233", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848565, "askingMemberId": 1576, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87713", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will lower business rates for (a) high street businesses, (b) businesses without a physical storefront on a street and (c) other small and medium sized businesses.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Small Businesses: Business Rates", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848565", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848563, "askingMemberId": 1576, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87712", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will withdraw the planned changes to (a) Agricultural Property Relief and (b) Business Property Relief.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Agriculture and Business: Inheritance Tax", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848563", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848562, "askingMemberId": 1576, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87711", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will commit not to introduce any new taxes which increase the cost of doing business.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Business: Taxation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848562", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848200, "askingMemberId": 1512, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87710", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when she expects temporary restrictions on the carrying of liquids by passengers using airports that fully operate Next Generation Security Checkpoints to be lifted.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Airports: Security", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848200", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848485, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87709", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he plans to consult UK maritime stakeholders on the implementation of the UN Agreement on Marine Biological Diversity of Areas beyond National Jurisdiction.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Biodiversity Beyond National Jurisdiction Agreement", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848485", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848484, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87708", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what representations his Department has made to his counterpart in Ukraine on the capture of North Korean soldiers fighting alongside Russian forces and their reported desire", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ukraine: Armed Conflict", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848484", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848482, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87707", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what discussions she has had with the Nigerian Government on (a) arbitrary detentions and (b) due process.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Nigeria: Detainees", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848482", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848481, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87706", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assessment she has made of the potential implications for her policies of the treatment of members of the Indigenous Peoples of Biafra in Nigeria.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Nigeria: Indigenous Peoples", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848481", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848480, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87705", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, whether she has raised the case of British citizen Nnamdi Kanu with the Nigerian authorities.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Nnamdi Kanu", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848480", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848479, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87704", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what steps she is taking with international partners to help tackle (a) religious persecution and (b) violence in (i) northern and (ii) central Nigeria.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Nigeria: Religious Freedom", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848479", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848478, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87703", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assessment she has made of the potential implications for her policies of the designation of Nigeria as a country of particular concern by the United States.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Nigeria and USA: Foreign Relations", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848478", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848477, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87702", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, whether she plans to support representations for an independent investigation into alleged extrajudicial killings in Tanzania since October 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Tanzania: Violence", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848477", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848476, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87701", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, whether she plans to review UK aid to Tanzania, in the context of the human rights situation.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Tanzania: Development Aid", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848476", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848475, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87700", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what representations she has made to the Government of Tanzania on the (a) detention and (b) trial of opposition leader Tundu Lissu.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Tundu Lissu", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848475", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848474, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87699", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, whether she plans to recognise the outcome of the Tanzanian general election of 29 October 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Tanzania: Elections", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848474", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848473, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87698", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assessment she has made of the legitimacy of the general election in Tanzania in October 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Tanzania: Elections", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848473", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848364, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87697", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will ensure that betting duty on greyhound racing (a) online, (b) in betting shops and (c) on course remains the same as for bets on horseracing.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Betting: Greyhound Racing", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848364", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848541, "askingMemberId": 1409, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87696", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what estimate he has made of the number of Advanced Modular Reactors that will be functional and fully operational by 2035.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Nuclear Reactors", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848541", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848374, "askingMemberId": 1409, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87695", "questionText": "To ask the hon. Member for Blaenau Gwent and Rhymney, representing the House of Commons Commission, how many complaints have been received from hon. Members relating to (a) laptops, (b) other IT equipment supplied under the Hardware Refresh programme and ", "answeringBodyId": 18, "answeringBodyName": "House of Commons Commission", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Members: ICT", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848374", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848215, "askingMemberId": 1409, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87694", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if she will hold discussions with the Director General of the BBC on allegations of mis-editing of President Trump by Panorama.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Panorama: Donald Trump", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848215", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848201, "askingMemberId": 1409, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87693", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps she is taking to encourage people aged under 30 to (a) save and (b) invest for retirement.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Young People: Personal Savings", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848201", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848629, "askingMemberId": 1211, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87692", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what support his Department is providing to NHS trusts to increase (a) crisis support services in the local community (b) mental health inpatient beds in the West Midlands.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Health Services: West Midlands", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848629", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848628, "askingMemberId": 1211, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87691", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps she is taking to promote (a) Sutton Coldfield (b) the West Midlands as destinations for British holidaymakers.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Tourism: West Midlands", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848628", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848289, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87690", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many (a) single sex and (b) gender neutral bathroom facilities her Department provides in its main Whitehall building.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Treasury: Sanitation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848289", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848287, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87689", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many (a) single sex and (b) gender neutral bathroom facilities his Department provides in its main Whitehall building.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cabinet Office: Sanitation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848287", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848225, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87688", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will list the titles of all the events organised by Civil Service networks in his Department since 2017.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Department for Work and Pensions: Equality", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848225", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848224, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87687", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will list the titles of all the events organised by Civil Service networks in her Department since 2017.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Treasury: Equality", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848224", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848174, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87686", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many (a) single sex and (b) gender neutral bathroom facilities his Department provides in its main Whitehall building.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government: Sanitation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848174", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848173, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87685", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many (a) single sex and (b) gender neutral bathroom facilities her Department provides in its main Whitehall building.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Department for Education: Sanitation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848173", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848170, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87684", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many (a) single sex and (b) gender neutral bathroom facilities her Department provides in its main Whitehall building.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport: Sanitation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848170", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848178, "askingMemberId": 221, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87683", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what steps his Department is taking to support (a) pubs, (b) bars and (c) venues.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Licensed Premises", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848178", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848592, "askingMemberId": 54, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-04T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87682", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, whether the British Embassy in Beijing has been affected by intermittent water supplies; and whether that Embassy has experienced similar issues that have affected its operat", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "China: Embassies", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848592", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848044, "askingMemberId": 5198, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87681", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether she has made an assessment the adequacy of the enforcement basis of drop-off charge systems operated by airports; and what steps her Department is taking to help ensure that motorists receive (a) clear ", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Airports: Fees and Charges", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848044", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848045, "askingMemberId": 4647, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87680", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether she has made an assessment of the potential impact of introducing VAT to to medicines provided free under Early Access Medicines Scheme programmes on pharmaceutical companies.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Drugs: VAT", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848045", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848004, "askingMemberId": 5362, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87675", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what recent discussions he has had with the Scottish Government on the adequacy of utility infrastructure in rural Highland communities.", "answeringBodyId": 2, "answeringBodyName": "Scotland Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Utilities: Infrastructure", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848004", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848003, "askingMemberId": 5362, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87674", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether she has made an assessment of the potential economic merits of public investment in essential utility infrastructure in remote rural communities.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Utilities: Investment", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848003", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848002, "askingMemberId": 5362, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87673", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to support essential infrastructure in rural communities at risk of depopulation.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Infrastructure: Rural Areas", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848002", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848001, "askingMemberId": 5362, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87672", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the relationship between access to core utilities and population retention in remote rural areas.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Utilities: Rural Areas", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848001", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848000, "askingMemberId": 5362, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87671", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what discussions he has had with Ofgem on ensuring that grid investment strategies take into account the long-term sustainability of remote rural communities.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Energy Supply: Rural Areas", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848000", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847999, "askingMemberId": 5362, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87670", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of introducing a support mechanism for electricity infrastructure projects in rural areas that face high connection costs.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Electricity: Rural Areas", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847999", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847998, "askingMemberId": 5362, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87669", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, whether he has made an assessment of the potential impact of difficulties in connecting remote communities to the national electricity grid on rural depopulation.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "National Grid: Rural Areas", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847998", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847997, "askingMemberId": 5362, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87668", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what steps his Department is taking to support electricity network operators to deliver connection upgrades in remote rural communities.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Electricity: Rural Areas", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847997", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847996, "askingMemberId": 5362, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87667", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of regulatory frameworks in ensuring that rural communities have access to electricity grid connections.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Energy Supply: Rural Areas", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847996", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847793, "askingMemberId": 5362, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87666", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what estimate his Department has made of the number of households not on the national grid for (a) gas and (b) electricity in each constituency in Scotland.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Energy Supply: Scotland", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847793", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847792, "askingMemberId": 5362, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87665", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what estimate his Department has made of the number of households not on the national grid for (a) gas and (b) electricity in Scotland.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Energy Supply: Scotland", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847792", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847790, "askingMemberId": 5362, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87664", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what estimate his Department has made of the number of households not on the national grid for (a) gas and (b) electricity in the UK.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Energy Supply: Rural Areas", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847790", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847738, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87663", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of the alignment between degree subject provision and priority occupations identified by Skills England.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Degrees", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847738", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847737, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87662", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether she plans to collect regional data on the use of the Lifetime ISA.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Individual Savings Accounts", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847737", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847735, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87661", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of graduate earning outcomes in the UK relative to other OECD countries.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Graduates: Pay", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847735", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847734, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87660", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to help ensure that students studying subjects with historically low graduate earning outcomes receive value for money from their degree.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Graduates: Pay", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847734", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847733, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87659", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the potential implications for her Department's policies of degree subjects associated with persistently (a) low employment and (b) earning outcomes; and what steps is she taking", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Graduates: Employment and Pay", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847733", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847732, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87658", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the potential implications for her Department's policies of differences in high-skilled employment rates by degree subject.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Graduates: Employment", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847732", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847731, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87657", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans she has to publish data on graduate career progression to assess the long-term impact of higher education on entry into high-skilled employment.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Graduates: Career Development", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847731", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847729, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87656", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of financial pressures on universities on their international recruitment practices.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Overseas Students: Admissions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847729", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847727, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87655", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether the Office for Students (a) collects and (b) publishes data on the (i) continuation, (ii) completion and (iii) attainment rates for international students by (A) provider and (B) ranking.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Overseas Students", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847727", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847726, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87654", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether there are regional variations in the planned allocation of Pride in Place programme funding to high street regeneration projects.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Pride in Place Programme", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847726", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847725, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87653", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether he plans to publish regular data on Pride in Place Programme spending by intervention type.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Pride in Place Programme", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847725", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847724, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87652", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of trends in the level of regional variation in the (a) progress, (b) attendance and (c) exclusion rates of pupils with SEND in schools receiving RISE intervention.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Special Educational Needs", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847724", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847650, "askingMemberId": 5359, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87651", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment her Department has made of the potential impact of banning the (a) import and (b) sale of fur on the economy.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Furs: Imports and Sales", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847650", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847684, "askingMemberId": 5353, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87650", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment her Department has made of the potential impact of changes to international student policy on the finances of universities.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Universities: Overseas Students", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847684", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847683, "askingMemberId": 5353, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87649", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, whether she plans to take steps to help (a) maintain and (b) increase research capacity in universities in the context of (i) academic staff time, (ii) funding and (iii) other matters.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Universities: Research", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847683", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847682, "askingMemberId": 5353, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87648", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to help support higher education providers that have financial challenges in the next academic year.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Higher Education: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847682", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847681, "askingMemberId": 5353, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87647", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of inflation on the Small Business Rate Relief threshold; and whether she plans to bring forward proposals to uprate the threshold in line with inflation.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Small Businesses: Business Rates", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847681", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847679, "askingMemberId": 5353, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87646", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to help support (a) the Echo Centre in Liskeard and (b) other community-based neuro-rehabilitation services.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Neurological Diseases: Community Health Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847679", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847678, "askingMemberId": 5353, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87645", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many at-sea boarding inspections of (a) UK and (b) EU flagged fishing vessels took place outside of six nautical miles in each year between 2015 and 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Fishing Vessels: Inspections", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847678", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847676, "askingMemberId": 5353, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87643", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether his Department plans to increase the pension rights of retired firefighters who retired before 2000 on the retained duty system through their modified pension scheme.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Fire and Rescue Services: Pension Rights", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847676", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847675, "askingMemberId": 5353, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87642", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to help support the (a) health and (b) wellbeing of the NHS workforce.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "NHS: Staff", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847675", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847674, "askingMemberId": 5353, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87641", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to improve facilities for healthcare workers.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Health Professions: Facilities", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847674", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847673, "askingMemberId": 5353, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87640", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to support the adoption of new technologies for the diagnosis of pancreatic cancer.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Pancreatic Cancer: Diagnosis", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847673", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847897, "askingMemberId": 5350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87638", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of the application of Vehicle Excise Duty on (a) new and (b) existing electric vehicles from 1 April 2025 on the (i) affordability and (ii) trends in the level of", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Electric Vehicles: Excise Duties", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847897", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847886, "askingMemberId": 5350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87637", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners have been wrongly released from prison since July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prisoners' Release", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847886", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847711, "askingMemberId": 5345, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87636", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, when the independent review into civil unrest in Leicester in 2022 is due to report.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Independent Review into Civil Unrest in Leicester", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847711", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847971, "askingMemberId": 5343, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87635", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the potential implications for her policies of trends in the number of pub closures in the last 12 months; and what fiscal measures she plans to take to support that sector.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Public Houses: Fiscal Policy", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847971", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847970, "askingMemberId": 5343, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87634", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will take steps to reduce business rates for (a) hospitality businesses, (b) pubs and (c) breweries.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Hospitality Industry: Business Rates", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847970", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847907, "askingMemberId": 5343, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87633", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to ensure that freeholders of leasehold properties comply with their legal obligations to maintain asbestos management plans; and what penalties apply to ", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Leasehold: Asbestos", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847907", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847900, "askingMemberId": 5343, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87632", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what plans he has to promote awareness among leaseholders of their right under the Leasehold and Freehold Reform Act 2024 to extend their lease to 990 years at a peppercorn groun", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Leasehold: Ground Rent", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847900", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847836, "askingMemberId": 5343, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87631", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he plans to allow inhalers to be sold over the counter without a prescription.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Asthma: Medical Equipment", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847836", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847723, "askingMemberId": 5340, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87630", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of introducing legislation equivalent to New Zealand\u2019s Retirement Villages Act 2003 to support the growth of the Integrated Re", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Sheltered Housing", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847723", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847776, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87629", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, how much and what proportion of UK emissions came from refrigerated transport in the latest period for which data is available.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Large Goods Vehicles: Refrigeration", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847776", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847773, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87628", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many e-scooters have been imported from China in (a) 2022, (b) 2023, (c) 2024 and (d) 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Electric Scooters: China", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847773", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847772, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87627", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many e-bikes have been imported from China in (a) 2022, (b) 2023, (c) 2024 and (d) 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Electric Bicycles: China", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847772", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847765, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87626", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many concessionary bus journeys were available in (a) 2018-19, (b) 2023-24 and (c) 2024-25.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Bus Services: Concessions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847765", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847764, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87625", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment she has made of trends in the level of concessionary bus journeys undertaken by (a) elderly and (b) disabled people.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Bus Services: Concessions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847764", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847763, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87624", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many concessionary bus journeys were taken by (a) elderly and (b) disabled people in (i) 2018-19, (ii) 2023-24 and (iii) 2024-25.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Bus Services: Concessions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847763", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847758, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87620", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of mandating zero-emission transport refrigeration units for refrigerated transport to replace diesel units.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Large Goods Vehicles: Refrigeration", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847758", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847757, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87619", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many refrigerator vehicles are currently used in the UK.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Large Goods Vehicles: Refrigeration", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847757", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847756, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87618", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential implications for his Department's policies of the relationship between deprivation and lung cancer diagnosis.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Lung Cancer: Diagnosis", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847756", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847755, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87617", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is staking to increase survival rates amongst lung cancer patients.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Lung Cancer: Health Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847755", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847754, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87616", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the UK\u2019s cancer survival rate was in (a) 2021-2022, (b) 2022-2023, (c) 2023-2024 and (d) 2024-2025.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cancer: Mortality Rates", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847754", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847753, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87615", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people were admitted to A&E in England after 5pm in (a) 2021-2022, (b) 2022-2023, (c) 2023-2024 and (d) 2024-2025.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Accident and Emergency Departments", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847753", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847752, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87614", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people were admitted to A&E in England on weekends in (a) 2021-2022, (b) 2022-2023, (c) 2023-2024 and (d) 2024-2025.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Accident and Emergency Departments", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847752", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847751, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87613", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many cancer drugs have been approved for use in (a) 2021-2022, (b) 2022-2023, (c) 2023-2024 and (d) 2024-2025.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cancer: Drugs", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847751", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847750, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87612", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to increase awareness amongst (a) GPs and (b) NHS clinicians of Ehlers-Danlos Syndrome.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ehlers-Danlos Syndrome", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847750", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847749, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87611", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential implications for his Department's policies of the link between access to independent advice and improved health and wellbeing outcomes.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Health: Disadvantaged", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847749", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847719, "askingMemberId": 5329, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87609", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department has made an assessment of the effectiveness of utilising shareable health data to help (a) fire and rescues services and (b) local authorities identify vulnerable residents.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Medical Records: Vulnerable Adults", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847719", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847717, "askingMemberId": 5329, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87607", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to ensure hunting laws are applied.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Hunting", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847717", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847716, "askingMemberId": 5329, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "87606", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment her Department has made of the potential merits of reducing VAT on labour costs to 10% for the hair and beauty sector.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847716", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847686, "askingMemberId": 5329, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87605", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his Department plans to increase the availability of the test digital service for applicants for (a) the Personal Independence Payment and (b) other benefits in (i) Horsham constituency and (ii)", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Social Security Benefits: Internet", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847686", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847669, "askingMemberId": 5327, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87604", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether he plans to amend the (a) Building Safety Act 2022 and (b) Building Regulations to ensure (i) building owners and (ii) nominated building design professionals can access ", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Buildings: Safety", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847669", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847600, "askingMemberId": 5327, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87603", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he has made an assessment with the Home Secretary of the potential merits of funding a wider rollout of long-acting Injectable Buprenorphine as a treatment option for people using opioids i", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Buprenorphine: Dorset", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847600", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847599, "askingMemberId": 5327, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87602", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether her Department holds data on families with home-educated children who are unable to (a) secure a place in a GCSE examination centre and (b) afford exam entry fees.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Home Education: Assessments", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847599", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847585, "askingMemberId": 5327, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87601", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of requiring water companies to demonstrate efficient land asset management before price increases are approved on customers.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Water Companies: Assets", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847585", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847705, "askingMemberId": 5319, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87600", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 23 October 2025 to Question 81693 on General Practitioners: Insurance, answered on 12th October 2025, how many GPs are covered under the professional indemnity insurance; ", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "General Practitioners: Insurance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847705", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847993, "askingMemberId": 5317, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87599", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential implications for his policies of the (a) level of rollout completion and (b) uptake rates of lung cancer screening programmes in each area where those s", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Lung Cancer: Screening", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847993", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848039, "askingMemberId": 5311, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87598", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many applications to the Criminal Injuries Compensation Authority are outstanding for more than (a) 12 months, (b) 18 months and (c) two years.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Criminal Injuries Compensation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848039", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848038, "askingMemberId": 5311, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87597", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average waiting time is for the Criminal Injuries Compensation Authority to (a) process and (b) determine claims for compensation.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Criminal Injuries Compensation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848038", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847710, "askingMemberId": 5311, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87596", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, when her Department plans to publish its response to proposals submitted by the fuels sector on the inclusion of refined oil products in the scope of the UK Carbon Border Adjustment Mechanism.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Carbon Emissions: Taxation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847710", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847709, "askingMemberId": 5311, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87595", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what progress her Department has made on considering the inclusion of refined oil products in the scope of the UK Carbon Border Adjustment Mechanism.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Carbon Emissions: Taxation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847709", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847704, "askingMemberId": 5304, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87594", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will host the Global Ministerial Meeting on Antimicrobial Resistance in 2028.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Antimicrobials: Drug Resistance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847704", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847703, "askingMemberId": 5304, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87593", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 23 October 2025 to Question 80723 on Stray Dogs, with which stakeholders her Department has met.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Stray Dogs", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847703", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847640, "askingMemberId": 5304, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-17T00:00:00", "uin": "87592", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, whether her Department has taken steps to help prevent the use of British weapons by the Rapid Support Forces in Sudan.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847640", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847960, "askingMemberId": 5298, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87591", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 10 October 2025 to Question 80707 on Hospitals: Special Educational Needs, if he will publish a breakdown by region of the over three million people who have completed the", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Hospitals: Special Educational Needs", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847960", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847967, "askingMemberId": 5296, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87590", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made of the efficacy of the implementation by Local Authorities of the Food Standards Agency's Food Hygiene Rating Scheme process from investigation to action.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Food: Hygiene", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847967", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847814, "askingMemberId": 5295, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87589", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, if she will make an assessment of the adequacy of consumer protections for mobile phone users impacted by long term service outages; and whether she plans to introduce additional regula", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Mobile Phones: Outages", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847814", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847813, "askingMemberId": 5295, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87588", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of the resilience of mobile networks in rural areas; and whether her Department plans to review (a) planning and (b) infrastructure requirem", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Mobile Phones: Outages", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847813", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847812, "askingMemberId": 5295, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87587", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what discussions her Department has had with mobile network operators on the timetable for restoring mobile coverage in Calder Valley constituency; and what steps she is taking to help ", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Mobile Phones: Outages", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847812", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847811, "askingMemberId": 5295, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87586", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, whether she plans to extend Ofcom\u2019s Automatic Compensation Scheme to cover prolonged mobile network outages.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Mobile Phones: Outages", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847811", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847809, "askingMemberId": 5295, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87585", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many NHS Local Improvement Finance Trust facilities there are in each region of England; and what proportion of those contracts are due to expire before 2030.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "NHS Local Improvement Finance Trust: Contracts", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847809", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847808, "askingMemberId": 5295, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87584", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he is applying lessons learned from the expiry of hospital Private Finance Initiative contracts to the management of NHS Local Improvement Finance Trust contract expiries.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "NHS Local Improvement Finance Trust: Contracts", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847808", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847807, "askingMemberId": 5295, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87583", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the expiry of NHS Local Improvement Finance Trust contracts on the finances of Integrated Care Boards over the next 10 years.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "NHS Local Improvement Finance Trust: Contracts", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847807", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847794, "askingMemberId": 5295, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87582", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to prepare for the expiry of NHS Local Improvement Finance Trust contracts, including the continuity of (a) primary care and (b) community health services.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "NHS Local Improvement Finance Trust: Contracts", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847794", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847715, "askingMemberId": 5288, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87581", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent discussions her Department has had with (a) local authorities and (b) schools on promoting careers in the fire and rescue service in Surrey Heath constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Fire and Rescue Services: Surrey", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847715", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847712, "askingMemberId": 5288, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87579", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps her Department is taking to support adults with debt difficulties in Surrey Heath constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Debts: Surrey Heath", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847712", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847659, "askingMemberId": 5288, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87577", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment her Department has made of the potential merits of reviewing the treatment of electric vehicles under the benefit-in-kind system.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Electric Vehicles: Taxation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847659", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847658, "askingMemberId": 5288, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87576", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment her Department has made of the potential impact of salary sacrifice schemes on the (a) affordability and (b) uptake of electric vehicles among (i) lower and (ii) middle-income drivers.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Electric Vehicles: Tax Allowances", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847658", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847645, "askingMemberId": 5288, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87575", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of compelling companies that provide services to the public to maintain (a) clear and (b) accessible channels for customer complaints.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Companies: Complaints", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847645", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847878, "askingMemberId": 5283, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87574", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate his Department has made of the value of Carer\u2019s Allowance overpayment debts in relation to earnings.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Carer's Allowance: Overpayments", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847878", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847876, "askingMemberId": 5283, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87573", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many Carer\u2019s Allowance overpayments in relation to earnings there are.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Carer's Allowance: Overpayments", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847876", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847875, "askingMemberId": 5283, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87572", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what progress his Department has made on processing Carer's Allowance overpayments; and when that process will be completed.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Carer's Allowance: Overpayments", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847875", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847874, "askingMemberId": 5283, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87571", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his Department\u2019s plans to process all Carer\u2019s Allowance overpayments in relation to earnings.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Carer's Allowance: Overpayments", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847874", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847873, "askingMemberId": 5283, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87570", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what progress his Department has made on clearing the backlog of Carer\u2019s Allowance overpayment debts in relation to earnings.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Carer's Allowance: Overpayments", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847873", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847838, "askingMemberId": 5279, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87569", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to support Royal Cornwall Hospitals NHS Trust in addressing the long waits for ambulances and emergency care at the acute hospital in Cornwall.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": " Royal Cornwall Hospitals NHS Trust", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847838", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847831, "askingMemberId": 5279, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87568", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what steps he is taking with energy suppliers to help prevent large increases in energy bill direct debits.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Energy: Billing", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847831", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847708, "askingMemberId": 5278, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87567", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what steps she is taking to ensure (a) atrocity prevention capabilities and (b) civilian protection expertise are used during the UK\u2019s response to events in El Fasher, Darfur", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Darfur: Armed Conflict", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847708", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847957, "askingMemberId": 5263, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87565", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to support young people in supported accommodation.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Supported Housing: Young People", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847957", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847823, "askingMemberId": 5262, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87564", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assessment she has made of the potential implications for her policies of the recent attack on Druze civilians in Suwayda Province, Syria; and what diplomatic steps she ", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Syria: Violence", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847823", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847578, "askingMemberId": 5248, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87563", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his Department has made an assessment of the potential impact of lone working practices introduced under the Co-op\u2019s Project Lunar scheme on employee (a) safety and (b) wellbeing.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Co-operative Group: Staff", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847578", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847791, "askingMemberId": 5247, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87562", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when his Department plans to announce the new membership of the National Quality Board.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "National Quality Board", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847791", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847706, "askingMemberId": 5240, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87561", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of her Department's Mass Atrocity Prevention Hub for supporting the UK\u2019s response to the situation in El Fasher, Darfur.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Darfur: Armed Conflict", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847706", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847707, "askingMemberId": 5229, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87560", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assessment she has made of the potential implications for her policies on preventing (a) mass atrocities and (b) genocide of the violence perpetrated by the Rapid Suppor", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Darfur: Armed Conflict", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847707", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847852, "askingMemberId": 5223, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87559", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, which (a) individuals and (b) organisations have been appointed to governance structures responsible for developing the Modern Service Frameworks for Dementia and Frailty.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Health Services: Dementia and Older People", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847852", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847661, "askingMemberId": 5219, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87558", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department is taking steps to (a) review and (b) update the guidance entitled Children and young people\u2019s continuing care national framework, published on 22 January 2016.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Continuing Care: Children and Young People", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847661", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847922, "askingMemberId": 5208, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87557", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to improve service provision for people with sarcoma in Cornwall.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cancer: Cornwall", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847922", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847908, "askingMemberId": 5208, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87556", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when the Education and Skills Funding Agency plans to publish updated guidance on the conditions under which academy trusts may operate electric vehicle salary-sacrifice schemes.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Academies: Electric Vehicles", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847908", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847670, "askingMemberId": 5201, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87555", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of increasing fuel duty on (a) consumer price inflation and (b) household living costs.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Fuels: Excise Duties", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847670", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847668, "askingMemberId": 5201, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87554", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she plans to issue guidance to police forces on responding to (a) thefts from vans and (b) tool theft, in the context of the implementation of the Equipment Theft (Prevention) Act 2023.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Equipment: Theft", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847668", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847667, "askingMemberId": 5201, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87553", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department plans to bring forward legislative proposals to extend the Equipment Theft (Prevention) Act 2023 to include tradespeople\u2019s power tools.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Tools: Theft", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847667", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847666, "askingMemberId": 5201, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87552", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department has made an assessment of the potential merits of introducing mandatory suicide preventing training for emergency service workers.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Suicide", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847666", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847665, "askingMemberId": 5201, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87551", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether her Department plans to provide funding for (a) indoor and (b) covered tennis facilities in Harpenden and Berkhamsted constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Tennis: Harpenden and Berkhamsted", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847665", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847664, "askingMemberId": 5201, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87550", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what plans her Department has to support the development of (a) affordable and (b) accessible padel courts in (i) Harpenden and Berkhamsted constituency and (ii) England.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Tennis: Facilities", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847664", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847663, "askingMemberId": 5201, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87549", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether her Department plans to take steps to help support the development of covered (a) tennis, (b) padel and (b) multi-sport facilities in Harpenden and Berkhamsted constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Sports: Harpenden and Berkhamsted", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847663", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847980, "askingMemberId": 5193, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87548", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department plans to introduce mandatory reporting on productivity improvements linked to capital investment.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Health Services: Productivity", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847980", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847979, "askingMemberId": 5193, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87547", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department has undertaken analysis of productivity variation across integrated care systems.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Integrated Care Systems: Productivity", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847979", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847978, "askingMemberId": 5193, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87546", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to support NHS trusts to increase same-day elective procedure capability.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Surgery", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847978", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847977, "askingMemberId": 5193, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87545", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department has assessed the potential effectiveness of digital scheduling tools in improving outpatient capacity.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Outpatients", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847977", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847976, "askingMemberId": 5193, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87544", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans his Department has to enhance digital access support for Pension Credit applications for older people.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Pension Credit: Internet", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847976", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847975, "askingMemberId": 5193, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87543", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what data his Department holds on local authority engagement with Pension Credit take-up campaigns.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Pension Credit", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847975", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847973, "askingMemberId": 5193, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87542", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department has made of potential factors limiting Pension Credit take-up among eligible low-income pensioners in rural areas.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Pension Credit: Rural Areas", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847973", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847972, "askingMemberId": 5193, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87541", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what assessment his Department has made of the potential impact of reduced electricity costs for employers in Buckingham and Bletchley constituency on employment growth in energy-intensive sectors.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Energy Intensive Industries: Buckingham and Bletchley", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847972", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847742, "askingMemberId": 5190, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87540", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what steps she is taking to help provide (a) atrocity prevention and (b) civilian protection support in El Fasher, Darfur.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Darfur: Armed Conflict", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847742", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847797, "askingMemberId": 5186, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87539", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what steps her Department is taking to help ensure that people who cannot afford mobile data can access (a) the NHS app and (b) other government digital services without incurring perso", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Electronic Government", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847797", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847748, "askingMemberId": 5186, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87538", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment her Department has made of the adequacy of (a) the Music and Dance Scheme and (b) other school funding schemes in the context of current levels of inflation.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Schools: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847748", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847884, "askingMemberId": 5172, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87537", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when he plans to publish the Modern Service Framework for Frailty and Dementia.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Health Services: Dementia and Older People", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847884", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847825, "askingMemberId": 5172, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87536", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she has made an assessment of the potential merits of freezing the accrual of interest on student loans for individuals on maternity or paternity leave.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Students: Loans", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847825", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847894, "askingMemberId": 5160, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87535", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what support is available to physician associate students approaching qualification (a) in general and (b) who have self-funded training to help them enter employment in the NHS.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Physician Assistants: Training", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847894", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847959, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87534", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many individuals released through the early release scheme were foreign nationals.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prisoners' Release: Foreign Nationals", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847959", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847938, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87533", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many complaints have been made to the Judicial Conduct Investigations Office on (a) bias against and (b) unfair treatment of fathers in family law\u00a0proceedings in the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Judicial Conduct Investigations Office: Complaints", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847938", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847937, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87532", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what information his Department holds on the average cost to fathers of pursuing access to children through the family court system; and whether he plans to make that process more\u00a0affordable.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Family Proceedings", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847937", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847936, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87531", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if his Department will make an estimate of the number of fathers prevented from seeing their\u00a0children following court proceedings in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Custody", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847936", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847935, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87530", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if the Government will commission a cross-departmental review across (a) justice, (b) education and (c) welfare on (i) improving support for and (ii) empowering fathers in maintaining active roles in children\u2019s\u00a0l", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Fathers: Government Assistance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847935", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847934, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87529", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that NHS (a) maternity wards and (b) perinatal services treat fathers as active participants in the birth process.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Maternity Services: Fathers", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847934", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847933, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87528", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether his Department has made an assessment of the (a) prevalence and (b) potential impact of parental alienation on fathers\u2019 ability to maintain a relationship with\u00a0their\u00a0children.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Custody", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847933", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847932, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87527", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of (a) fathers and (b) mothers received legal aid support in family court proceedings relating to child custody and access in the last\u00a0five\u00a0years.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Family Proceedings: Legal Aid Scheme", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847932", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847931, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87526", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average waiting time is for fathers seeking access to their children through the family courts after\u00a0a\u00a0separation.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Custody", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847931", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847930, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87525", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what information his Department holds on the number of custody arrangements ordered by family courts that resulted in the father being granted equal or majority care\u00a0of\u00a0the\u00a0child in the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Custody", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847930", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847924, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87524", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 26 March 2025 to Question 38250 on Health Services: Foreign Nationals, what the ten nationalities with the highest total unpaid invoices were in 2023-24.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Health Services: Foreign Nationals", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847924", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847917, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87523", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether her Department has made an estimate of annual tax loss from untaxed remittances sent abroad by non-UK\u00a0nationals.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Remittances: Taxation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847917", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847914, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87522", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many and what proportion of police officers are qualitied to use firearms in each year since 2018.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Police: Firearms", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847914", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847906, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87521", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much income was generated through charges for category f patients in each financial year since 2018-19; and how much aggregate income identified for the 2018-19 financial year was written off.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Health Services: Foreign Nationals", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847906", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847902, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87520", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) translators and (b) interpreters have worked in the prison estate since 2018; and what the total cost to the public purse was for their services.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prisons: Translation Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847902", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847899, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87519", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will publish (a) all recreational activities provided to inmates and (b) the total cost to the public purse for providing those activities in (i) HMP Maidstone, (ii) HMP Huntercombe and (iii) HMP Morton Hal", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prisons: Leisure", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847899", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847898, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87518", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the cost to the public purse was of the NHS Muslim network in each of the last five years for which data is available.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "NHS: Muslims", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847898", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847722, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87517", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of splitting charging category A patients ordinarily resident in the UK and (a) asylum seeker and (b) failed asylum seeker under section 95 of ", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "NHS: Foreign Nationals", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847722", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847984, "askingMemberId": 5138, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87515", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what research his Department has commissioned on (a) reproductive health outcomes and (b) other long-term health effects of occupational exposure to hazardous medicinal products among nursing staff", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Health Professions: Hazardous Substances", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847984", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847982, "askingMemberId": 5138, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87514", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to promote the use of (a) biological safety cabinets, (b) closed-system drug-transfer devices and (c) other engineering controls during (i) preparation and (ii) admin", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Health Services: Hazardous Substances", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847982", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847981, "askingMemberId": 5138, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87513", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if his Department will review the adequacy of the Control of Substances Hazardous to Health Regulations to ensure that hazardous medicinal products with reprotoxic effects are controlled to the same sta", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Health Services: Hazardous Substances", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847981", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847966, "askingMemberId": 5134, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87512", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of opening paths on disused railway lines to increase public access to nature.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Public Footpaths", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847966", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847965, "askingMemberId": 5134, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87511", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to make it easier to create more routes (a) to and (b) through green spaces.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Recreation Spaces", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847965", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847895, "askingMemberId": 5112, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87510", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, which (a) Department and (b) Minister will lead on the online guidance hub for parents and carers on children and young people\u2019s online safety and the Media Literacy Vision Statement.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Internet: Children and Young People", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847895", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847954, "askingMemberId": 5111, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87509", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what team in her Department produced the Product Security and Telecommunications Infrastructure (Security Requirements for Relevant Connectable Products) (Amendment) (No. 2) Regulations", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Product Security and Telecommunications Infrastructure (Security Requirements for Relevant Connectable Products) (Amendment) (No. 2) Regulations 2025", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847954", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847953, "askingMemberId": 5111, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87508", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, how much paid civil service time did it take to create The Product Security and Telecommunications Infrastructure (Security Requirements for Relevant Connectable Products) (Amendment) (", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Product Security and Telecommunications Infrastructure (Security Requirements for Relevant Connectable Products) (Amendment) (No. 2) Regulations 2025", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847953", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847896, "askingMemberId": 5111, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87507", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of a framework model for functional neurological disorder (FND) care, including (a) FND care pathways, (b) the requirement for multidisciplinary ", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Functional Neurological Disorder: Health Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847896", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848005, "askingMemberId": 5102, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87506", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to her letter to the Chair of the Education Select Committee dated 22 October 2025, when she will begin (a) to seek views through listening sessions in every region of the country and (b) fortnig", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Special Educational Needs", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848005", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847586, "askingMemberId": 5092, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87505", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he has had discussions with ICBs on minimum waiting times for NHS services.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": " NHS: Health Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847586", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847714, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87504", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of online misinformation spread by AI Large Language Models on social media platforms.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Social Media: Disinformation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847714", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848017, "askingMemberId": 5088, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87503", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many County Court Judgements were related to vehicle infringements in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "County Courts: Road Traffic Offences", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848017", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848011, "askingMemberId": 5088, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87502", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if she will publish a breakdown of the number of registered number plate suppliers registered to each of the most commonly used PO boxes.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Vehicle Number Plates: Postal Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848011", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848006, "askingMemberId": 5088, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87501", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many and what proportion of registered number plate suppliers have addresses registered to PO boxes.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Vehicle Number Plates: Postal Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848006", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847952, "askingMemberId": 5085, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87500", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what estimate his Department has made of (a) the percentage of electricity supplied to the national grid from renewable forms of energy and (b) how much of this is generated from sources in W", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Electricity Generation: Wales", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847952", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847951, "askingMemberId": 5085, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87499", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, if he will make an estimate of the proportion of electricity supplied to the national grid that was generated in Wales.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Electricity Generation: Wales", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847951", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847950, "askingMemberId": 5085, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87498", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, with reference to the National Audit Office Report entitled Energy efficiency installations under the Energy Company Obligation, published on 14 October 2025, what the cost to the public purs", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Energy Company Obligation: Wales", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847950", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847949, "askingMemberId": 5085, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87497", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, with reference to the National Audit Office Report entitled Energy efficiency installations under the Energy Company Obligation, published on 14 October 2025, how many homes in Wales have had", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Energy Company Obligation: Wales", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847949", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847947, "askingMemberId": 5085, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87496", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment her Department has made of the potential impact of the increase in employers' National Insurance contributions on levels of business (a) investment and (b) closures in Wales.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Employers' Contributions: Wales", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847947", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847995, "askingMemberId": 5081, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87495", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what discussions her Department has had with stakeholders in the North East on the protection children and young people from harmful content online.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Internet: Children and Young People", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847995", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847992, "askingMemberId": 5081, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87494", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what steps she is taking to help tackle digital exclusion in (a) Hexham constituency, (b) Northumberland, (c) Newcastle, (d) the North East and (e) England.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Digital Technology: Disadvantaged", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847992", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847991, "askingMemberId": 5081, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87493", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what assessment the her Department has made of the potential impact of the AI Growth Zone in the North East on economic growth in the Hexham constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Artificial Intelligence: North East", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847991", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847983, "askingMemberId": 5081, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87492", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what steps his Department is taking to support tech innovation in (a) Hexham constituency and (b) the North East.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Technology: Innovation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847983", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847969, "askingMemberId": 5081, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87491", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what discussions he has had with the Sentencing Council on the use of community sentences (a) Hexham constituency, (b) Northumberland, (c) Newcastle and (d) the North East.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Community Orders: North East", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847969", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847968, "askingMemberId": 5081, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87490", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps the Department is taking to support victims of rape and sexual violence through the court system in (a) Hexham constituency, (b) Northumberland, (c) Newcastle and (d) the North East.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Sexual Offences: Criminal Proceedings", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847968", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847641, "askingMemberId": 5081, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87489", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what estimate his Department has made of the potential impact of foreign direct investment projects on economic growth in the North East in the last (a) five years and (b) ten years.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Foreign Investment in UK: North East", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847641", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847639, "askingMemberId": 5081, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87488", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether her Department has had recent discussions with relevant stakeholders on financial education in schools in (a) Hexham constituency, (b) Northumberland, (c) Newcastle and (d) the North East.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Financial Services: Education", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847639", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847638, "askingMemberId": 5081, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87487", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent discussions her Department has had with relevant stakeholders on relationships education in schools in (a) Hexham constituency, (b) Northumberland, (c) Newcastle and (d) the North East.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Relationships and Sex Education: North East", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847638", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847637, "askingMemberId": 5081, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87486", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many Sure Start centres have closed in (a) Hexham constituency, (b) Northumberland, (c) Newcastle, (d) the North East and (e) England since May 2010.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Children's Centres: Closures", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847637", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847636, "askingMemberId": 5081, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87485", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many police stations have closed in (a) Hexham constituency, (b) Northumberland, (c) Newcastle and (d) the North East since May 2010.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Police Stations: Closures", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847636", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847635, "askingMemberId": 5081, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87484", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions her Department has had with relevant stakeholders in the North East on developments to Active Travel England.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Active Travel: North East", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847635", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848015, "askingMemberId": 5072, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87483", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will make representations to HM Treasury on the potential impact of VAT on the affordability of (a) Remembrance wreaths and (b) other commemorative items provided by charities.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Charities: VAT", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848015", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848014, "askingMemberId": 5072, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87482", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that VAT policy does not discourage participation in Remembrance events organised by (a) charities and (b) local authorities.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Remembrance Day: VAT", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848014", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848013, "askingMemberId": 5072, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87481", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate she has made of the annual revenue raised through VAT charged on Remembrance wreaths purchased by (a) local authorities, (b) schools and (c) community organisations.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Remembrance Day: VAT", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848013", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848012, "askingMemberId": 5072, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87480", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will review VAT rules to ensure that (a) the purchase of wreaths and (b) other purchases made in support of charitable remembrance activities are not subject to VAT.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Remembrance Day: VAT", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848012", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848010, "askingMemberId": 5072, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87479", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, whether her Department plans to review the use of (a) confidentiality clauses and (b) NDAs in consumer redress agreements involving alleged (i) harm or (ii) injury to animals.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Animals: Injuries", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848010", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848009, "askingMemberId": 5072, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87478", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what recent assessment she has made of the adequacy of consumer protections for customers whose animals are injured during paid (a) grooming or (b) veterinary services.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Animals: Injuries", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848009", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848008, "askingMemberId": 5072, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87477", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what guidance his Department has provided to local authorities on the investigation of injuries sustained by companion animals during commercial grooming appointments.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Pets: Shops", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848008", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848007, "askingMemberId": 5072, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87476", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to help ensure that grooming services offered by pet retail chains are subject to adequate (a) welfare standards and (b) inspection regimes.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Pets: Shops", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848007", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847680, "askingMemberId": 5072, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87475", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what mechanisms his Department has put in place to allow people to report (a) poor performance and (b) untidy workmanship from Government contractors.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Government Departments: Contract Compliance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847680", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847672, "askingMemberId": 5072, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87474", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, if he will make an assessment of the potential implications for his policies of trends in the level of public confidence in Government-backed net zero projects.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Carbon Emissions: Public Opinion", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847672", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847850, "askingMemberId": 5030, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87473", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, for what reasons the UK has opposed proposals at the UN to guarantee at least one year of free pre-primary education and free secondary education in international law.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "International Law: Education", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847850", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847849, "askingMemberId": 5030, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87472", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what discussions she has had with (a) the Secretary of State for Education and (b) other Cabinet colleagues on the UK's position on proposals at the UN to negotiate an Option", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "UN Convention on the Rights of the Child: Education", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847849", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847943, "askingMemberId": 5001, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87471", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of establishing an independent regulator or ombudsman to support pet-owning households not currently covered by an existing regulat", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Pets", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847943", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847939, "askingMemberId": 4995, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87470", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions she has had with the Financial Conduct Authority on ensuring that people with disabilities and without access to mobile phones are not excluded from accessing online quotations and other financial s", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Financial Services: Internet", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847939", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847822, "askingMemberId": 4995, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87469", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much of the Small Abattoir Fund\u00a0was\u00a0spent by her Department prior to it's closure in 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Slaughterhouses: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847822", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847821, "askingMemberId": 4995, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87468", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many veterinary students are currently enrolled in veterinary public health courses in the UK.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Veterinary Medicine: Training", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847821", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847815, "askingMemberId": 4995, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87467", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many remedial action notices the Food Standards Agency have handed out to abattoirs in England and Wales over the last (a) year, (b) 5 years and (c) 10 years.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Slaughterhouses: Hygiene", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847815", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847743, "askingMemberId": 4995, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87466", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to increase access to dentistry for vulnerable residents in care homes.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Dental Services: Care Homes", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847743", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847653, "askingMemberId": 4934, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87465", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps her Department is taking to improve sporting facilities for young people in North Shropshire constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Sports: North Shropshire", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847653", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847651, "askingMemberId": 4934, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87464", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to provide an adequate allocation of funding through the Youth Guarantee Scheme for people not in work, employment or training in North Shropshire constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Employment Schemes: Young People", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847651", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847649, "askingMemberId": 4934, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87463", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to help improve pathways for school leavers without (a) GCSE Maths and (b) GCSE English qualifications.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "School Leaving: GCSE", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847649", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847648, "askingMemberId": 4934, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87462", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, whether she plans to provide guidance to (a) businesses, (b) schools and (c) universities on AI-driven recruitment processes.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Recruitment: Artificial Intelligence", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847648", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847626, "askingMemberId": 4934, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87461", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how much funding was provided to the creative industry in the West Midlands by (a) capital and (b) project grants and by (i) county and (ii) county per head in each year since 2015.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Arts: West Midlands", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847626", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847624, "askingMemberId": 4934, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87460", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how much and what proportion of the funding provided through the Creative Industries Fund to the West Midlands will be allocated to (a) Shropshire and (b) North Shropshire constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Arts: Shropshire", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847624", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847685, "askingMemberId": 4869, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87459", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will make an assessment of whether the membership of the Food Strategy Advisory Board includes adequate expertise in (a) public health, (b) nutrition, (c) environmental science,", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Food Strategy Advisory Board", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847685", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847788, "askingMemberId": 4844, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87457", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment her Department has made of the availability of permitted landfill capacity for industrial waste in the North East.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Industrial Waste: North East", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847788", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847787, "askingMemberId": 4844, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87456", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of reforms to the Landfill Tax on businesses engaged in environmentally-responsible waste (a) treatment and (b) recycling.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Landfill Tax: Waste Management", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847787", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847786, "askingMemberId": 4844, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87455", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment her Department has made of the potential impact of recent changes to Landfill Tax rates on chemical manufacturing operations in Teesside.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Landfill Tax: Tees Valley", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847786", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847785, "askingMemberId": 4844, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87454", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many number payments were made to people (i) deported and (ii) voluntarily returned under Home Office schemes since July 2024; and what the value of those payments were.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Undocumented Migrants: Deportation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847785", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847784, "askingMemberId": 4844, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87453", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of deported individuals received financial assistance to leave since July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Undocumented Migrants: Deportation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847784", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847783, "askingMemberId": 4844, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87452", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what mechanisms are in place to recover public funds from people who return to the UK unlawfully after receiving financial support to leave.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Undocumented Migrants: Deportation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847783", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847782, "askingMemberId": 4844, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87451", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent discussions she has had with the Chancellor of the Exchequer on funding for (a) voluntary and (b) enforced removal schemes of foreign national offenders in the 2025-26 financial year.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Offenders: Deportation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847782", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847781, "askingMemberId": 4844, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87450", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate her Department has made of the cost to the public purse of (a) voluntary return and (b) deportation schemes since July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Deportation and Repatriation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847781", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847619, "askingMemberId": 4844, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87448", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an estimate of the number of practicing clinicians who have received specialist training in (a) diagnosing and (b) treating Avoidant/Restrictive Food Intake Disorder.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Avoidant/Restrictive Food Intaker Disorder: Diagnosis", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847619", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847618, "askingMemberId": 4844, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87447", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department have made of potential (a) savings to the NHS and (b) improved or increased quality of life for patients from the early diagnosing of people with Avoidant/Restrictive", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Avoidant/Restrictive Food Intaker Disorder: Diagnosis", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847618", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847617, "askingMemberId": 4844, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87446", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what guidance and information his Department issues to clinicians to assist in early diagnosis of Avoidant/Restrictive Food Intake Disorder.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Avoidant/Restrictive Food Intaker Disorder: Diagnosis", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847617", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847616, "askingMemberId": 4844, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87445", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if his Department will take steps to improve the assessment and diagnosis for Avoidant/Restrictive Food Intake Disorder in (i) Teesside and (ii) the North East of England.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Avoidant/Restrictive Food Intaker Disorder: North East", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847616", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847613, "askingMemberId": 4844, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87444", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department plans to take to encourage an increased uptake of coronial post-mortems by pathologists.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Post-mortems", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847613", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847607, "askingMemberId": 4844, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87443", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average time taken was for (a) Teesside Coroner's Officer and (b) Coroner's Offices in England and Wales to issue a final death certificate from the date of when deaths are referred to them in each of th", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Death Certificates", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847607", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847606, "askingMemberId": 4844, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87442", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what (a) number and (b) proportion of final death certificates remained unissued by Coroner's Offices in England and Wales after (i) 3 months (ii) 6 months, (iii) 12 months, (iv) 18 months and (v) 24 months after", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Death Certificates", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847606", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847605, "askingMemberId": 4844, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87441", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what (a) number and (b) proportion of final death certificates remained unissued by the Teesside Coroner's Office for (i) 3 months (ii) 6 months, (iii) 12 months, (iv) 18 months and (v) 24 months after the deaths", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Death Certificates: Tees Valley", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847605", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847623, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87440", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether she plans to require MOT tests to check that (a) front windows and (b) windscreens comply with legal light transmission limits.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Motor Vehicles: Glass", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847623", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847622, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87439", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what information her Department holds on (a) enforcement and (b) prosecution rates by police force following reports from members of the public of road traffic offences captured on (i) dashcams and (i", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Road Traffic Offences: Video Recordings", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847622", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847621, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87438", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to help protect (a) police officers, (b) immigration officers and (c) other public sector workers from online harassment by people who film and publish deliberately confrontat", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Harassment: Social Media", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847621", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847615, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87437", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to improve the enforcement of ecological conditions attached to planning consents; and whether he has had recent discussions with (a) Natural ", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Planning Permission: Biodiversity", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847615", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847614, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87436", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what information his Department holds on compliance with ecological mitigation and enhancement conditions attached to planning permissions; and if he will publish post-occupancy ", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Planning Permission: Biodiversity", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847614", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847598, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87435", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether NHS trusts in areas with higher prevalence of consanguineous unions receive additional (a) funding, (b) training and (c) genetic counselling resources to help tackle related health needs.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Hereditary Diseases", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847598", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847597, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87434", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether any NHS trusts (a) collect and (b) are required to collect data on (i) child and infant mortality, (ii) congenital anomalies and (iii) other health outcomes attributable to parental consang", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Hereditary Diseases", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847597", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847596, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87433", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information his Department holds on the incidence of (a) genetic and (b) congenital disorders associated with parental consanguinity in England and Wales since 1997; if he will make an assessm", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Hereditary Diseases", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847596", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847595, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87432", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether he has taken steps with Cabinet colleagues to make an assessment of the potential impact of trends in the level of inbreeding on (a) socioeconomic, (b) educational and (c) health outcomes in each region ", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Congenital Abnormalities", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847595", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847594, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87431", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what information his Department holds on the (a) geographical and (b) demographic distribution of (i) consanguineous unions and (ii) high genomic inbreeding coefficients in each region; and whether these data ar", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Congenital Abnormalities", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847594", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847593, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87430", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what information his Department holds on the number of (a) marriages and (b) other unions between (i) first cousins and (ii) closer relatives in each nation of the UK in each year since 1997; and whether the Off", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Marriage: Relatives", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847593", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847592, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87429", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 24 October 2025 to Question 82733 on Mobility Scooters: Pedestrian Areas, when her Department plans to commence the powered mobility device review; and what its objectives will be.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Mobility Scooters: Pedestrian Areas", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847592", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847591, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87428", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 24 October 2025 to Question 82740 on Electric Vehicles: Grants, what information his Department holds on the number of people who were employed in the automotive manufacturing sector on", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Electric Vehicles: Grants", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847591", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847590, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87427", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether she plans to bring forward legislative proposals to implement a national ban on pavement parking; and whether she has held recent discussions with (a) Guide Dogs and (b) other relevant charities on this", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Parking: Pedestrian Areas", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847590", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847589, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87426", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 27 October 2025 to Question 82990 on Railways: Essex, what estimate her Department has made of the capital cost of that proposal; and what assessment her Department has made of the pot", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Railways: Essex", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847589", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847588, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87425", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 27 October 2025 to Question 82992 on Railways: Freight, which schemes set out in the Spending Review were identified as having potential for increasing the capacity for freight on the ", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Railways: Freight", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847588", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847587, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87424", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 27 October 2025 to Question 82998 on HGV Parking and Driver Welfare Grant Scheme, what plans she has for (a) unspent and (b) returned grant funding; and whether those monies will be (i", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "HGV Parking and Driver Welfare Grant Scheme", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847587", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847582, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87423", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment her Department has made of the potential impact of the establishment of Great British Railways on the cost of rail services for passengers.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Great British Railways", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847582", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847581, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87422", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the net Government funding of the rail sector was per passenger, per journey in the (a) 2023-24 and (b) 2024-25 financial year; and what estimate her Department has made of the net Government funding of th", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Railways: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847581", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847577, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87421", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 17 October 2025 to Question 77156 on Rolling Stock: Leasing, whether any of the train operating companies transferred into public ownership since July 2024 have seen rolling stock leas", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Rolling Stock: Leasing", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847577", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847835, "askingMemberId": 4805, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87420", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will review the offer of two seat convertible Mazda MX-5 cars as part of the Motability Scheme.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Motability", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847835", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847810, "askingMemberId": 4805, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87419", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what form consultation on local government reorganisation proposals will take.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Local Government: Reorganisation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847810", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847803, "askingMemberId": 4805, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87418", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if his Department will engage in a public consultation with the residents of Leicestershire prior to deciding which Local Government Reorganisation plans\u00a0to\u00a0approve.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Local Government: Reorganisation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847803", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847802, "askingMemberId": 4805, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87417", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if his Department with engage in a public consultation with the residents of South Kesteven before deciding which Local Government Reorganisation plan\u00a0to\u00a0approve.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Local Government: South Kesteven", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847802", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847800, "askingMemberId": 4805, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87416", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if his Department will engage in a public consultation with residents of Rutland before deciding which Local Government Reorganisation plan\u00a0to\u00a0approve.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Local Government: Reorganisation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847800", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847688, "askingMemberId": 4787, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87415", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, how much solar power generating capacity is (a) operational, (b) under construction and (c) awaiting a planning decision.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Solar Power", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847688", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847687, "askingMemberId": 4787, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87414", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of adding energy nationally significant infrastructure projects to the renewable energy planning database.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Renewable Energy: Planning", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847687", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847963, "askingMemberId": 4781, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87413", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 8 August 2025 to Question 67474 on NHS England: Redundancy, when his Department will provide an update on the cost impact of integrating NHS England with the DHSC.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "NHS England: Redundancy", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847963", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847962, "askingMemberId": 4781, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87412", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what representations his Department has received from Integrated Care Boards on (a) the abolition of NHS England and (b) subsequent planned redundancies.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "NHS England: Redundancy", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847962", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847961, "askingMemberId": 4781, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87411", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions his Department has had with Integrated Care Boards on the source of funding for redundancy packages resulting from the abolition of NHS England.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "NHS England: Redundancy", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847961", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847824, "askingMemberId": 4776, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87410", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when she expects the (a) economic and (b) environmental analysis of Heathrow Airport expansion to (i) commence and (ii) be completed.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Heathrow Airport: Construction", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847824", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847778, "askingMemberId": 4776, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87409", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether his Department includes purpose-built student accommodation in it's counting of affordable housing.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Affordable Housing: Students", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847778", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847620, "askingMemberId": 4776, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87408", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children will lose transitional protection funding for free school meals by each key stage group in 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Free School Meals: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847620", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847872, "askingMemberId": 4764, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87407", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether his Department plans to compensate providers for additional work created by the cyber security incident at the Legal Aid Agency.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Legal Aid Agency: Cybersecurity", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847872", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847871, "askingMemberId": 4764, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87406", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what his planned timeline is for the implementation of the uplift of (a) housing and (b) immigration legal aid.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Legal Aid Scheme: Housing and Immigration", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847871", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847870, "askingMemberId": 4764, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87405", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to implement the recommendations on council tax in the\u00a0consultation entitled Modernising and improving the administration of council tax, published on 20 ", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Council Tax: Reform", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847870", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847869, "askingMemberId": 4764, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87404", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she has taken to prevent the exploitation of workers on the Seasonal Worker visa in food supply chains following BBC\u2019s File on 4 Abused for our Food investigation.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Visas: Seasonal Workers", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847869", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847868, "askingMemberId": 4764, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87403", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if she will make it her policy to work with the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care to (a) improve awareness of cardiac risk among young athletes and (b) ensure sports clubs have access", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Sports: Heart Diseases", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847868", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847867, "askingMemberId": 4764, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87402", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to Breast Cancer Awareness Month, what steps he is taking in November 2025 to promote inclusive (a) wig and (b) prosthetic services.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prosthetics and Wigs: Health Education", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847867", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847866, "askingMemberId": 4764, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87401", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions he has had with NHS England to ensure the procurement of suitable (a) prosthetics and (b) wigs suitable for ethnic minority patients meets diverse patient needs.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prosthetics and Wigs: Ethnic Groups", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847866", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847865, "askingMemberId": 4764, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87400", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of a limited access to suitable (a) prosthetics and (b) wigs on ethnic minority patients; and what steps he is taking to improve access.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prosthetics and Wigs: Ethnic Groups", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847865", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847580, "askingMemberId": 4735, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87399", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, whether she has made an assessment of the potential merits of holding a consultation on reforming the Electronic Communications Code 2017 to help increase the way it reflects Scotland\u2019s", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Telecommunications: Codes of Practice", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847580", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847779, "askingMemberId": 4716, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-17T00:00:00", "uin": "87398", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what recent discussions she has had with her international counterparts on the protection of civilians following the capture of El Fasher by the Rapid Support Forces on 26 Oc", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847779", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848037, "askingMemberId": 4679, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87397", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, how many employment tribunal claims (a) for unfair dismissal and (b) under the Equality Act 2010 have been brought against her Department in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology: Employment Tribunals Service", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848037", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848036, "askingMemberId": 4679, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87396", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, how many staff in her Department are recorded as having a (a) mental health condition and (b) physical disability, listed by grade.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology: Disability", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848036", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848035, "askingMemberId": 4679, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87395", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, how many staff left her Department in each of the last five years, listed by grade.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology: Termination of Employment", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848035", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848034, "askingMemberId": 4679, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87394", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, how many staff in her Department (a) did not retain employment following completion of their probationary period and (b) had their probationary period extended in each of the last five ", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology: Conditions of Employment", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848034", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848033, "askingMemberId": 4679, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87393", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, how many performance reviews were undertaken for staff in (a) her Department and (b) its agencies in each of the last five years; in how many of those cases was performance rated as uns", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology: Performance Appraisal", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848033", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848031, "askingMemberId": 4679, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87392", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many employment tribunal claims (a) for unfair dismissal and (b) under the Equality Act 2010 have been brought against his Department in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government: Employment Tribunals Service", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848031", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848030, "askingMemberId": 4679, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87391", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many staff in his Department are recorded as having a (a) mental health condition and (b) physical disability, listed by grade.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government: Disability", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848030", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848029, "askingMemberId": 4679, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87390", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many staff have left his Department in each of the last five years, listed by grade.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government: Termination of Employment", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848029", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848028, "askingMemberId": 4679, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87389", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many staff in his Department (a) did not retain employment following completion of their probationary period and (b) had their probationary period extended in each of the las", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government: Conditions of Employment", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848028", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848027, "askingMemberId": 4679, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87388", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many performance reviews were undertaken for staff in (a) his Department and (b) its agencies in each of the last five years; in how many cases performance was rated as unsat", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government: Performance Appraisal", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848027", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848024, "askingMemberId": 4679, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87387", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, how many employment tribunal claims relating to (a) unfair dismissal and (b) claims under the Equality Act 2010 have been lodged against her Department in each of the last fi", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office: Employment Tribunals Service", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848024", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848023, "askingMemberId": 4679, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87386", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, how many staff in her Department are recorded as having a (a) mental health condition and (b) physical disability by the grade of those staff.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office: Disability", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848023", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848021, "askingMemberId": 4679, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87385", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, how many staff left her Department by the grade of those staff in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office: Termination of Employment", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848021", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848020, "askingMemberId": 4679, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87384", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, how many staff in her Department (a) did not retain employment following completion of their probationary period and (b) had their probationary period extended in each of the", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office: Conditions of Employment", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848020", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848019, "askingMemberId": 4679, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87383", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, how many performance reviews were undertaken for staff in (a) her Department and (b) its agencies in each of the last five years; in how many cases performance was rated as u", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office: Performance Appraisal", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848019", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847630, "askingMemberId": 4679, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87382", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many employment tribunal claims have been lodged against her Department by (a) unfair dismissal and (b) claims under the Equality Act 2010 in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Treasury: Employment Tribunals Service", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847630", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847629, "askingMemberId": 4679, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87381", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many staff in her Department are recorded as having a (a) mental health condition and (b) physical disability by grade.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Treasury: Disability", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847629", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847628, "askingMemberId": 4679, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87380", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many staff left her Department by grade in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Treasury: Termination of Employment", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847628", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847627, "askingMemberId": 4679, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87379", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many staff in her Department (a) did not retain employment following completion of their probationary period and (b) had their probationary period extended in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Treasury: Conditions of Employment", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847627", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847625, "askingMemberId": 4679, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87378", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many performance reviews were undertaken for staff in (a) her Department and (b) its agencies in each of the last five years; in how many cases performance was rated as unsatisfactory or below; how many staff le", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Treasury: Performance Appraisal", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847625", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847948, "askingMemberId": 4656, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87376", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to introduce screening for asymptomatic heart conditions in young people in sports settings.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Heart Diseases: Young People", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847948", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847946, "askingMemberId": 4656, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87375", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to help raise awareness among young people of the risks of sudden cardiac death in (a) grassroots sports clubs and (b) higher education settings.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Heart Diseases: Young People", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847946", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847862, "askingMemberId": 4656, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87374", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what the planned timetable is for transferring tenants currently on shorthold tenancies to periodic assured tenancies.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Private Rented Housing: Tenancy Agreements", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847862", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847883, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87373", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 3 March 2025 to Question 35028 on LGBT Veterans Independent Review, what progress he has made on recommendations (a) 31, (b) 35, (c) 36, (d) 38 and (e) 42.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "LGBT Veterans Independent Review", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847883", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847834, "askingMemberId": 4630, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87372", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, pursuant to the Answer of 22 October to Question 82973 on Broadband: Rural Areas, if she will make her policy to include direction to Ofcom on revising the Physical Infrastructure Acces", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Broadband: Rural Areas", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847834", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847864, "askingMemberId": 4595, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87371", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many and what percentage of small cider producers produce less than five hectolitres of pure alcohol and are exempt from alcohol duty payments.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cider: Excise Duties", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847864", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847863, "askingMemberId": 4595, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87370", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of equalising cider and beer duty.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Beer and Cider: Excise Duties", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847863", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847955, "askingMemberId": 4591, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87369", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many stage (a) one, and (b) two, complaints were submitted to HM Courts and Tribunals Service in (i) 2024 and (ii) 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "HM Courts and Tribunals Service: Complaints", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847955", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847893, "askingMemberId": 4591, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87368", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, with reference to the Competition and Markets Authority's press release entitled CMA confirms Apple and Google have strategic market status in mobile platforms, published on 22 October 2025, what steps", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Contactless Payments", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847893", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847804, "askingMemberId": 4569, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87366", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many vehicles were leased through the mobility scheme in each year since 2020; and how many of those vehicles were British made.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Motability", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847804", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847833, "askingMemberId": 4527, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87365", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many GP surgeries will have employment advisors; and what his planned timetable is for rollout.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Employment: Advisory Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847833", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847832, "askingMemberId": 4527, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87364", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many (a) work coaches and (b) vacancies there were at Jobcentres in each month since July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Jobcentres: Staff", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847832", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847830, "askingMemberId": 4527, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87363", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the (a) number of people Connect to Work is expected to support into work and (b) expected cost of the scheme per person successfully employed at the end of the programme.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Connect to Work", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847830", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847829, "askingMemberId": 4527, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87362", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Business and Trade on preparing Jobcentres for the potential impact of the Employment Rights Bill.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Jobcentres", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847829", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847828, "askingMemberId": 4527, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87361", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what engagement he has had with (a) the BMA and (b) GP surgeries on embedding employment advisers in GP surgeries.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Employment: Advisory Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847828", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847827, "askingMemberId": 4527, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87360", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of employment advisers that will be employed to work in community healthcare settings.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Employment: Advisory Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847827", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847826, "askingMemberId": 4527, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87359", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether he has a target for the number of work coaches employed by his Department.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Employment: Advisory Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847826", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847657, "askingMemberId": 4527, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87358", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of Personal Independence Payment (a) assessments and (b) reassessments were carried out (i) face-to-face, (ii) remotely and (iii) on paper in each month since July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Personal Independence Payment: Medical Examinations", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847657", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847964, "askingMemberId": 4523, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87357", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to (a) improve care and treatment for people with eating disorders and (b) reduce the number of lives lost to eating disorders.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Eating Disorders", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847964", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847958, "askingMemberId": 4523, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87356", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to improve employer (a) awareness and (b) training on autism-inclusive workplace practices.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Employment: Autism", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847958", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847647, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87355", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate her Department has made of the annual economic contribution of volumetric concrete mixers to the economy.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Large Goods Vehicles: Concrete", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847647", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847646, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87354", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if she will make a comparative assessment of the potential impact of (a) 44-tonne, five-axle volumetric concrete mixers and (b) traditional drum mixers on (i) the number of vehicle movements, (ii) road wear and", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Large Goods Vehicles: Concrete", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847646", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847612, "askingMemberId": 4515, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87353", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of amending the Animals (Scientific Procedures) Act 1986 to include decapod crustaceans.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Animal Experiments: Shellfish", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847612", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847610, "askingMemberId": 4515, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87352", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to implement provisions in the Environment Act 2021 to impose due diligence regulations for forest risk commodities.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Forests: Commodities", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847610", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847609, "askingMemberId": 4515, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87351", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of providing funding to the Tropical Forest Forever Facility.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Rainforests: International Assistance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847609", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847608, "askingMemberId": 4515, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87350", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will make an assessment of the potential implications for her policies of the report by Kinship entitled Handle with Care: Annual survey of kinship carers 2025, published on 2 October 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Kinship Care", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847608", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847885, "askingMemberId": 4403, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87349", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, if he will hold discussions with his US counterpart on removing the 10% levy on Scottish whisky during forthcoming discussions on the UK-US trade deal.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Whisky: Import Duties", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847885", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847632, "askingMemberId": 4403, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87347", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people who were detained in illegal working raids were entered into the National Referral Mechanism in the last 12 months.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Undocumented Workers: Human Trafficking", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847632", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847631, "askingMemberId": 4403, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87346", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent steps she has taken to help prevent the exploitation of workers on the Seasonal Worker Visa in food supply chains.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Visas: Seasonal Workers", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847631", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847806, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87345", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the answer of 16 September 2025, to Question 75999, on Submarines: Nuclear Weapons, whether the UK\u2019s new F-35A air-launched nuclear capability will use sovereign warheads.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "F-35 Aircraft: Nuclear Weapons", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847806", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847805, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87344", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 8 September 2025 to Question 71248 on Military Aircraft: Ministers, which aircraft were used for the Prime Minister\u2019s seven domestic tasks.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Military Aircraft: Ministers", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847805", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847801, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87343", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he has plans for a social value model for defence.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Defence: Procurement", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847801", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847799, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87342", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 14 October 2025 to Question 77638 on Defence and National Security: Finance, whether the expenditure under the Chagos Islands Treaty will be deemed by the Government to be within the 5% ", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Chagos Islands: Sovereignty", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847799", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847798, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87341", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 12 February 2025 to Question 28585 on Admiralty House, whether the Secretary of State for Defence occupied the residence as a (a) primary or (b) secondary residence from September to Nov", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Admiralty House", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847798", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847796, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87340", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether the Deputy Prime Minister\u2019s official residence in Carlton Gardens is registered with Westminster City Council as a second home.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ministers: Official Residences", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847796", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847777, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87339", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how his Department's lieutenancy policy team engages with the Association of Lord-Lieutenants; and whether any (a) formal agreement and (b) memorandum of understanding exists between them.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cabinet Office: Lord-Lieutenants", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847777", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847775, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87338", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 23 September 2025 to Question 76050 on Lobbying: Official Hospitality, whether the donation in kind of (a) a venue and (b) hospitality from a lobbying firm hosting a Departmental recept", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Lobbying: Official Hospitality", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847775", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847774, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87337", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether the findings of the One Big Thing 2024 evaluation will be compared with the Civil Service People Survey results in (a) 2024 and (2025) to test whether any change in (i) culture and (ii) innovation capabi", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Civil Servants: Training", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847774", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847771, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87336", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the Cabinet Office annual report and accounts 2024-25, HC1372, published on 23 October 2025, and the HMT Guidance on Public Sector Exit Payments: Use of Special Severance Payments, updated on 2", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Alex Chisholm and Simon Case", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847771", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847770, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87335", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to footnotes 25 and 26 of the Cabinet Office annual report and accounts 2024-2025, HC 1372, published on 23 October 2025, for what reason the current Cabinet Secretary has a lower salary than the ", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cabinet Office: Pay", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847770", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847767, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87334", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether Irish citizens in Northern Ireland will be required to have digital ID cards.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Identity Cards: Northern Ireland and Republic of Ireland", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847767", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847766, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87333", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 24 October 2025 to Question 82672 on 9 Downing Street: Repairs and Maintenance, for what reason the room was not politically neutral.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "9 Downing Street: Repairs and Maintenance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847766", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847762, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87332", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether due diligence undertaken by his Department for the appointment of Lord Mandelson as Ambassador considered (a) Lord Mandelson\u2019s relationship with Jeffrey Epstein and (b) Global Counsel\u2019s work in China.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Lord Mandelson", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847762", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847643, "askingMemberId": 4368, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87330", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether the Timms Review into Personal Independence Payments will include assessments of the potential impact of proposed changes on levels of homelessness.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Personal Independence Payment Assessment Review", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847643", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847642, "askingMemberId": 4368, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87329", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department plans to take to help reduce the number of children living in temporary accommodation.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Temporary Accommodation: Children", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847642", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847702, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87328", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the answer of 27 October 2025 to Question 83810 on Pride in Place Programme: Finance, how much funding has been allocated to each nation in the Spending Review period", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Pride in Place Programme: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847702", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847701, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87327", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the answer of 22 October 2025 to Question 81315 on National Identity, whether his Department is taking steps to promote (a) English and (b) British identities in peop", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "National Identity", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847701", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847700, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87326", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 16 September 2025 to Question 75616 on Business Rates: Local Press, what estimate her Department has made of the cost of the relief for local newspapers in the 2024-25 financial year; and w", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Business Rates: Local Press", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847700", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847699, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87325", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 27 October 2025 to Question 83816 on Devolution: Cornwall, whether he plans to require Cornwall to (a) join a combined authority with Devon and (b) have", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Devolution: Cornwall", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847699", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847698, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87324", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether the Affordable Housing Programme will have a funding stream for (a) renovating and (b) getting long-term empty homes back into use as affordable housing.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Affordable Housing: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847698", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847697, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87323", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 21 October 2025 to Question 78194 on Affordable Housing: Expenditure, where this information can be found in the annual reports and accounts.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Affordable Housing: Expenditure", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847697", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847696, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87322", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 21 October 2025 to Question 78216 on Community Relations: Expenditure, what each of those 300 projects were; and what reporting requirements there were ", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Community Relations: Expenditure", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847696", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847695, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87321", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the answer of 21 October 2025 to Question 78216 on Community Relations: Expenditure, which places received funding; and how much each received.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Community Relations: Expenditure", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847695", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847694, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87320", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what correspondence his Department has received from Cumbria Conservatives on the date of the Cumbria mayoral elections; when that correspondence was received; and whether each i", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Mayors: Elections", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847694", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847693, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87319", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 20 October 2025 to Question 78232 on MHCLG: Remote Working, how many (a) assigned staff and (b) allocated desks there are in each of his Department\u2019s of", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government: Remote Working", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847693", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847611, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87317", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether his Department consulted mayors on the proposed Supplementary Vote change for (a) mayors and (b) Police and Crime Commissioners prior to the announcement on 10 July 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Mayors and Police and Crime Commissioners: Elections", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847611", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847861, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87316", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what discussions he has had with the West Midlands Combined Authority on increasing the availability of apprenticeships in the West Midlands.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Apprentices: West Midlands", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847861", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847860, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87315", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, pursuant to the Answer of 29 October 2025 to Question 83837 on Broadband: Rural Areas, what progress she has made on Project Gigabit in the West Midlands; how many premises in Aldridge\u2013", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Broadband: Rural Areas", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847860", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847859, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87314", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 2 September 2025 to Question 69838 on Railway Stations: Aldridge, if she will publish details of any (a) discussions and (b) correspondence that (i) she and (ii) her Department has had", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Railway Stations: Aldridge", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847859", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847858, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87313", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what fiscal steps she is taking to help (a) reduce inflation and (b) increase average annual earnings in the West Midlands.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Average Earnings and Inflation: West Midlands", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847858", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847857, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87312", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of (a) average annual earnings and (b) prices on household disposable income in 2024-25.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Disposable Income", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847857", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847856, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87311", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether she plans to provide additional funding for the Warm Homes Plan.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Warm Homes Plan", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847856", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847855, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87310", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of the Midlands Rail Hub on (a) capacity on the West Coast Main Line and (b) passenger services into central Birmingham; and what discussions she has had wit", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Railways: West Midlands", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847855", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847854, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87309", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 28 October 2025 to Question 83840 on Railways: West Midlands, if her Department will explore the use of the Sutton Park freight line for passenger services; and whether its inclusion i", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Railways: West Midlands", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847854", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847853, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87308", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of closing asylum accommodation hotels on (a) levels of demand for Houses of Multiple Occupation(HMOs), (b) local housing stock and (c) local publi", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Asylum: Housing", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847853", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847851, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87307", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will make it his Department's policy to (a) guarantee that green belt protections in the West Midlands will be maintained under the devolution of planning powers to the reg", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Green Belt: West Midlands", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847851", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847848, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87306", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what plans his Department has to extend new planning powers and investment flexibilities being provided to the Mayor of London under the Housing Delivery package announced in Wri", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Housing: Construction", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847848", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847847, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87305", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of houses of multiple occupation being used to accommodate illegal migrants on (a) the wider private rented housing sector (b)", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Multiple Occupation: Undocumented Migrants", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847847", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847846, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87304", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what recent assessment he has made of (a) the potential impact of houses in multiple occupation (HMOs) on (i) community cohesion and (ii) levels of anti-social behaviour, (b) the", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Multiple Occupation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847846", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847845, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87303", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what guidance he has issued to the Planning Inspectorate on considering potential environmental impacts of decisions to designate land as grey belt.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Green Belt", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847845", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847844, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87302", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what guidance he has issued to the Planning Inspectorate on deciding whether a site is considered grey belt when a decision by a local authority has been appealed.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Green Belt", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847844", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847843, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87301", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will issue guidance to local authorities to ensure mobile network operators are notified for large-scale residential developments.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Housing: Construction", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847843", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847841, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87300", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of updating the National Planning Policy Framework to include guidance on the importance of telecommunications infrastructur", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Housing: Construction", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847841", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847840, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87299", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the judgement in C G Fry & Son Limited v Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government UKSC/2024/0108 on", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Housing: Construction", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847840", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847839, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87298", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many times he has met with the leader of Birmingham City Council to discuss resolving the ongoing bin strikes.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Waste Disposal: Birmingham", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847839", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847739, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87297", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assessment she has made of the potential implications for her policies of the recent murder of an Alawite school teacher in Homs, Syria.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Syria: Homicide", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847739", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847579, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87296", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what discussions he has had with PowerNI on electricity prices in autumn 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Electricity: Prices", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847579", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847575, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87294", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to ensure police officers are able to perform day to day duties during protests outside hotels housing migrants.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Asylum: Hotels", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847575", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847891, "askingMemberId": 4107, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87293", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what steps he is planning to take to (a) monitor and (b) evaluate the effectiveness of the 90% compensation rate in supporting (i) decarbonisation and (ii) energy efficiency in energy intensive industr", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Energy Intensive Industries: Government Assistance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847891", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847890, "askingMemberId": 4107, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87292", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, whether his Department has conducted a regional impact assessment of the Network Charging Compensation Scheme uplift on industrial competitiveness across the devolved nations.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Energy Intensive Industries: Government Assistance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847890", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847889, "askingMemberId": 4107, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87291", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that the uplift in compensation for energy intensive industries does not lead to increased costs for other electricity consumers.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Energy Intensive Industries: Government Assistance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847889", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847888, "askingMemberId": 4107, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87290", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, whether he plans to publish a list of (a) sectors and (b) companies eligible for the 90% relief under the revised Network Charging Compensation Scheme.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Energy Intensive Industries: Government Assistance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847888", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847887, "askingMemberId": 4107, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87289", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the uplift in Network Charging Compensation Scheme relief on small and medium-sized manufacturers not eligible for EII status.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Energy Intensive Industries: Government Assistance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847887", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847721, "askingMemberId": 4074, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87288", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether it is her policy to protect accrued pension rights when changing the tax treatment of pensions.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Pensions: Tax Allowances", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847721", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847720, "askingMemberId": 4074, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87287", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate she has made of the number of customers accessing pensions prior to the Autumn Budget 2025; and whether she has made an assessment of the potential impact of media coverage of the Budget on pension ade", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Pensions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847720", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847768, "askingMemberId": 4051, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87286", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assessment she has made of the potential implications for her policies of the airstrike on a Buddhist festival in Sagaing Region, Myanmar; and what diplomatic steps she ", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Myanmar: Violence", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847768", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847746, "askingMemberId": 4032, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87285", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Education on cross-Government implementation of (a) proposals for a national evidence-based digital parenting offer and (b) other ", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Family Hubs: Local Government", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847746", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847745, "askingMemberId": 4032, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87284", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of supporting the roll-out of evidence-based parenting programmes through the Start for Life offer to all local authorities.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Child Rearing", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847745", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847656, "askingMemberId": 4032, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87283", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to help tackle travel costs for (a) children and (b) young people under 25 with cancer; and whether he plans to include policies on this matter within the national cancer pl", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cancer: Children and Young People", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847656", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847655, "askingMemberId": 4032, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87282", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what policies on (a) children and (b) young people under 25 he plans to include within the national cancer plan for England.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cancer: Children and Young People", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847655", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847654, "askingMemberId": 4032, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87281", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent work the Children and Young People\u2019s Cancer Taskforce has undertaken in relation to the national cancer plan; and how recommendations from the Taskforce will be reflected in that plan.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Children and Young People Cancer Taskforce", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847654", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847882, "askingMemberId": 4005, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87280", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether she has made an assessment of the potential impact of fuel duty increases on (a) the cost of living and (b) consumer prices in London.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Fuels: Excise Duties", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847882", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847881, "askingMemberId": 4005, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87279", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of (a) fuel duty, (b) Clean Air Zone charges and (c) Direct Vision Standard requirements on London-based (a) haulage and (b) coach operators.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Buses and Freight: Greater London", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847881", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847820, "askingMemberId": 4005, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87278", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how his Department plans to work with relevant stakeholders to resolve potential issues affecting the delivery of social housing through Section 106 on early engagement between d", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Social Rented Housing: Construction", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847820", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847819, "askingMemberId": 4005, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87277", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what alternative options for helping to deliver (a) affordable and (b) social housing in London have been considered by his Department.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Affordable Housing and Social Rented Housing: Greater London", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847819", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847818, "askingMemberId": 4005, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87276", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps he plans to take to (a) maintain social housing commitments in existing planning permissions in London and (b) ensure that levels of social housing are not reduced in ", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Social Rented Housing: Greater London", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847818", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847817, "askingMemberId": 4005, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87275", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of lowering affordable housing requirements on levels of social housing supply in London in the (a) long and (b) short term.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Social Rented Housing: Greater London", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847817", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847816, "askingMemberId": 4005, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87274", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps she plans to take to ensure that the 60% of affordable homes provided through the new route at social rent are not renegotiated out at a later stage in the development", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Social Rented Housing: Construction", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847816", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847741, "askingMemberId": 4005, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87273", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps is the Department taking to promote earlier detection, ensure dentists, GPs and other frontline health professionals are trained to identify early warning signs, and improve timely diagn", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Mouth Cancer: Diagnosis", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847741", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847740, "askingMemberId": 4005, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87272", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what discussions she has had with her Iranian counterpart on the detention of Baha\u2019i Shahram Fallah since August 2025; and what diplomatic steps she is taking to help ensure ", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Shahram Fallah", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847740", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847728, "askingMemberId": 1593, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87271", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what recent discussions she has had with her international counterparts on reports of the (a) detention and (b) killing of the Falun Gong in China.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "China: Falun Gong", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847728", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847928, "askingMemberId": 1591, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87270", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the review of refugee family reunion will consider the optimisation of decision making to reduce the need for appeals.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Refugees: Families", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847928", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847927, "askingMemberId": 1591, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87269", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the potential impact of (a) gathering documentation and (b) submitting biometrics on people submitting refugee family reunion applications; and whether she p", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Refugees: Families", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847927", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847926, "askingMemberId": 1591, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87268", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department plans to exempt (a) unaccompanied children seeking to reunite with parents already in the UK and (b) families facing (i) conflict, (ii) persecution and (iii) medical emergencies", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Refugees: Families", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847926", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847921, "askingMemberId": 1591, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87267", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the report entitled Independent Water Commission: review of the water sector, updated on 29 July 2025, whether she plans to strengthen the requirements on companies t", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Water Companies: Assets", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847921", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847920, "askingMemberId": 1591, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87266", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the report entitled Independent Water Commission: review of the water sector, updated on 29 July 2025, whether she plans to consult on the introduction of a national ", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Water Charges: Social Tariffs", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847920", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847919, "askingMemberId": 1591, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87265", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the report entitled Independent Water Commission: review of the water sector, updated on 29 July 2025, whether she plans to provide a regulatory framework to drive th", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Water", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847919", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847918, "askingMemberId": 1591, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87264", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the report entitled Independent Water Commission: review of the water sector, updated on 29 July 2025, whether she plans to ensure future water monitoring programmes ", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Water", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847918", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847916, "askingMemberId": 1591, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87263", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the report entitled Independent Water Commission: review of the water sector, updated on 29 July 2025, whether she plans to make an assessment of how effectively publ", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Water", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847916", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847915, "askingMemberId": 1591, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87262", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the report entitled Independent Water Commission: review of the water sector, updated on 29 July 2025, whether she plans to introduce a comprehensive systems planning", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Water Supply", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847915", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847913, "askingMemberId": 1591, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87261", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the report entitled Independent Water Commission: review of the water sector, updated on 29 July 2025, whether she plans to revise the legal framework for the Strateg", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Water", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847913", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847912, "askingMemberId": 1591, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87260", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what progress her Department has made on publishing a national water strategy.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Water", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847912", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847911, "askingMemberId": 1591, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87259", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what progress her Department has made on establishing a new integrated water industry regulator.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Water Companies: Regulation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847911", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847910, "askingMemberId": 1591, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87258", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what progress her Department has made on abolishing Ofwat.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ofwat", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847910", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847909, "askingMemberId": 1591, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87257", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the report entitled Independent Water Commission: review of the water sector, updated on 29 July 2025, what progress her Department has made on responding to the reco", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Water", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847909", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847905, "askingMemberId": 1521, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87256", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much funding his Department has allocated for prospective studies into anti-seizure medications other than Sodium Valproate in pregnancy since 2018.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Pregnancy: Drugs", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847905", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847904, "askingMemberId": 1521, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87255", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what (a) grants and 9b) funding her Department has allocated to the Medical Research Council for research into anti-seizure medications in pregnancy since 2018.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Pregnancy: Drugs", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847904", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847903, "askingMemberId": 1521, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87254", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much funding his Department has allocated for research of anti-seizure medications in pregnancy (a) in total and (b) to the MHRA since 2020.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Pregnancy: Drugs", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847903", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847901, "askingMemberId": 1521, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87253", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when research funding was last given for anti-seizure medications in pregnancy.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Pregnancy: Drugs", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847901", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847879, "askingMemberId": 1491, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-13T00:00:00", "uin": "87252", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 22 October 2025 to Question 78048 on General Practitioners: Recruitment, whether he plans to recruit more experienced GPs whose Certificate of Completion of Training Date ", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847879", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847660, "askingMemberId": 1491, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-12T00:00:00", "uin": "87251", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps his Department has taken to help ensure that the Infected Blood Compensation Authority claims process is accessible to people whose historic NHS records are difficult to locate.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847660", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847837, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87250", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what recent diplomatic discussions she has had with her Chinese counterparts on the detention of Church leader Zhang Chunlei; and what steps she is taking to ensure his relea", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Zhang Chunlei", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847837", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847602, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87248", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what assessment he has made of the contribution of the UK to national security in Northern Ireland.", "answeringBodyId": 21, "answeringBodyName": "Northern Ireland Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "National Security: Northern Ireland", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847602", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847584, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87247", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to her Department's report entitled Scientific procedures on living animals, Great Britain: 2024, published on 23 October 2025, what assessment she has made of (a) the number of animals", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Animal Experiments", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847584", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847583, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87246", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to her Department's report entitled Scientific procedures on living animals, Great Britain: 2024, published on 23 October 2025, what assessment she has made of (a) the number of animals", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Animal Experiments", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847583", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848040, "askingMemberId": 1409, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87244", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 3 November 2025 to Question 85702 on Electric Vehicles: Charging Points, what information his Department holds on whether the 127 additional electric vehicle charging points will be (a", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Electric Vehicles: Charging Points", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848040", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847604, "askingMemberId": 1409, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87243", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, if she will hold discussions with Innovate UK on holding Innovate Local events in the north west of Northern Ireland.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Innovate UK: Northern Ireland", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847604", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848016, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87242", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if she will list the titles of all the events organised by Civil Service networks in her Department since 2017.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport: Civil Service", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848016", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847974, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87241", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what data his Department holds on the number of fire service call outs in response to fires involving solar panels in England for each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Fires: Solar Power", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847974", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847769, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87240", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment she has made of the adequacy of the availability of grants for farmers to support (a) sustainable and (b) regenerative agricultural practices in Lincolnshire.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Agriculture: Lincolnshire", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847769", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847747, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87239", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information his Department holds on the number of men treated for prostate cancer in (a) South Holland and the Deeping constituency and (b) Lincolnshire in 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prostate Cancer: Medical Treatments", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847747", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847744, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87238", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she plans to house asylum seekers in South Holland and the Deepings constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Asylum: Housing", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847744", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847736, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87237", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what recent steps he has taken with local councils to tackle the illegal use of fireworks in Lincolnshire.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Fireworks: Lincolnshire", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847736", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847601, "askingMemberId": 242, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87234", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when she plans to dispose of the redundant site of the former Parkfield School at Hurn; and what estimate she has made of the (a) security and (b) opportunity costs of the premises remaining unused.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Parkfield School Christchurch", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847601", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847574, "askingMemberId": 242, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87233", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 21 July 2025 to Question 68347 on Immigration: Appeals, when the recruitment exercise commenced in 2024 for the First Tier Tribunal will be completed; and how many vacant posts at the Im", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "First-tier Tribunal: Judges", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847574", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847573, "askingMemberId": 242, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87232", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the status is of the recruitment exercise which closed in November 2024 for Judges of the First-Tier Tribunal; how many applications were received; and how many appointments have been made (a) in total, (b) ", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "First-tier Tribunal: Judges", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847573", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847877, "askingMemberId": 227, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87230", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment her Department has made of the potential impact of imported pork produced using farrowing crates on the competitiveness of UK farmers that do not use farrowing crates.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Pigs: Animal Welfare", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847877", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847945, "askingMemberId": 221, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87228", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to increase access to higher technical qualifications and degree courses by low-income students.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Higher Education: Admissions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847945", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847944, "askingMemberId": 221, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87227", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what progress his Department has made in developing an evidence base to consider whether decapods should have greater protection.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Shellfish: Conservation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847944", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847942, "askingMemberId": 221, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87226", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what plans he has to extend the rollout of Young Futures Hubs.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Young Futures Hubs", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847942", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847929, "askingMemberId": 193, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87224", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what discussions she has had with her counterparts in Bangladesh on the (a) anti-Ahmadi protests planned in Bangladesh for 15 November and (b) upholding freedom of religion f", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Bangladesh: Freedom of Religion", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847929", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847990, "askingMemberId": 178, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87223", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps he has taken to ensure that planned reforms to the Local Government Pension Scheme are compliant with not aiding or assisting serious breaches of international law.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Local Government Pension Scheme", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847990", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847989, "askingMemberId": 178, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87222", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what his Department\u2019s planned timeline is for responding to the Local Government Pension Scheme Advisory Board's letter, dated 13 October 2025, requesting guidance on investments", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Local Government Pension Scheme", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847989", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847987, "askingMemberId": 178, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87221", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether he is taking steps to ensure that Local Government Pension Scheme investments are compliant with the UK\u2019s duty (a) not to aid and (b) assist serious breaches of internati", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Local Government Pension Scheme", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847987", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847986, "askingMemberId": 178, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87220", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether his Department provides guidance to local authorities administering Local Government Pension Scheme on ensuring their investments are compliant with the UK\u2019s duty (a) not", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Local Government Pension Scheme", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847986", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847985, "askingMemberId": 178, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87219", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what guidance his Department provides to local authorities administering Local Government Pension Scheme funds to assist them in ensuring their investments are compliant with the", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Local Government Pension Scheme", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847985", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847652, "askingMemberId": 177, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87218", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will make an assessment of the adequacy of access to affordable credit for (a) people and (b) small businesses in the 100 most deprived communities according to the English indices of multiple deprivation 202", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Credit", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847652", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847988, "askingMemberId": 152, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87217", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment she has made of the level of threat posed by people motivated by Jihadi ideology to (a) public safety and (b) the safety of (i) synagogues, (ii) Jewish educational establishment", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Radicalism: Islam", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847988", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847994, "askingMemberId": 55, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-05T00:00:00", "uin": "87216", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, following the Memorandum of Understanding with the Palestinian Authority of April 2025, what step she is taking to help to ensure that content which promotes (a) hatred and (", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Palestine: Curriculum", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847994", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847956, "askingMemberId": 55, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87215", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, if she will make it her policy to reduce the Passive Infrastructure Access charges to broadband providers installing their own cabling parallel to existing Openreach broadband infrastru", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Broadband: Fees and Charges", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847956", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847940, "askingMemberId": 55, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87214", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, whether she has had discussions with her counterpart in Nigeria on the detention of eight children from the Du Merci Christian orphanage; and whether she is taking diplomatic", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Nigeria: Detainees", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847940", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848043, "askingMemberId": 54, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87213", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will publish the number of hotels that (a) were used and (b) will be used to house asylum seekers in New Forest East constituency in 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Asylum: Hotels", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848043", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1848042, "askingMemberId": 54, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87212", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 30 October 2025 to Question 83220 on Army: Public Records, with regards to the criteria of (a) national security, (b) international relations and (c) sensitive personal data,", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Army: Public Records", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1848042", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847691, "askingMemberId": 54, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87211", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent representations he has received from ENT UK on the decision by NHS Hampshire and Isle of Wight Integrated Care Board to refuse all future referrals for (a) septoplasty and (b) other sep", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ear, Nose and Throat Conditions: Surgery", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847691", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847690, "askingMemberId": 54, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87210", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, on what evidential basis the minimum age for free covid-19 inoculations to be offered by the NHS, other than for people with particular vulnerabilities, was set at 75; and what information his Depa", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Coronavirus: Vaccination", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847690", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1847689, "askingMemberId": 54, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-11-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-11-11T00:00:00", "uin": "87209", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment his Department has made of the reasons for the difference in availability of Omaveloxolone (Skyclarys) as a treatment for Friedrich's ataxia in (a) Scotland and (b) England a", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Omaveloxolone", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1847689", "method": "GET"}]}]